<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Items><Item ItemID="4963"><Name>Halloween Party Bats owl Witch Girl Mouse Pad</Name><Category>Computers</Category><Category>Input Peripherals</Category><Category>Mousepads</Category><Currently>$5.5</Currently><Buy_Price>$7.15</Buy_Price><First_Bid>$5.5</First_Bid><Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids><Bids/><Location Latitude="39.006963" Longitude="-119.94762">Western NY</Location><Country>USA</Country><Started>Dec-16-01 17:02:39</Started><Ends>Dec-23-01 17:02:39</Ends><Seller Rating="4919" UserID="ca44@cecomet.net"/><Description>Halloween Party Bats owl Witch Girl Mouse Pad Description This is a new, soft top, 1/4" rubber backed mouse pad ,with an easy-roll poly woven surface. These are very colorfull. , measuring 7 1/2" x 9" All of our mouse pads come poly-bagged. The image is printed with a waterproof, fade resistant medium under high pressure at 400 degrees. AS BEAUTIFUL AS IT IS PRACTICAL! Winning bidders to pay$ 2.50 shipping (domestic first class mail) International bidders email for a shipping quote Good Luck! A Wonderful Gift Idea for Any Collector Or Friend Or Boss Mouse Pad. Payment and Shipping Buyer to pay $2.50 SHIPPING eBay's most successful sellers use Auctionworks sales management services!</Description></Item><Item ItemID="5408"><Name>IBM DCHS-04F 4.5G 50 PIN SCSI-2 HARD DRIVE</Name><Category>Computers</Category><Category>Apple, Macintosh</Category><Category>Drives-Internal</Category><Currently>$34.15</Currently><First_Bid>$34.15</First_Bid><Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids><Bids/><Location Latitude="37.189396" Longitude="-121.705327">San Jose, CA</Location><Country>USA</Country><Started>Dec-04-01 16:45:56</Started><Ends>Dec-11-01 16:45:56</Ends><Seller Rating="8" UserID="fulogic"/><Description>IBM DCHS-04F IBM ULTRASTAR 4.55 GB SCSI Hard Drive Product description and its detail summary Hard Drive Name: ULTRASTAR 2XP Model Number : DCHS-04F Capacity: 4.55 GB Formatted Rotational Speed: 7,200 RPM Average Seek Time: 7.5 ms Part Number: 93G3001 Interface: SCSI-2 Fast, 50-PIN Single-Ended Form Factor: 3.5", 1/3 high (low profile). Only 1" tall! Description: TANDEM, OEM unit, used Warranty: Click here for Warranty information Installation: Step-by-Step Installation Guide Product Home Page: IBM Storage Product Comments : It provides you a fast and stable storage media, and it is also ideal to build RAID0/RAID1/RAID5/RAID10 arrays. * I BM OEM has introduced a new range of disk drives intended for advanced storage applications which demand fast access to large amounts of data. The drive spins at 7,200 RPM have and EPRML channel, embedded sector servo, S.M.A.R.T. and media data rate 10.3-15.4 MB/Sec. * Shipping and Insurance is fixed $9.25 in USA. Elsewhere actual . International order is subject to $4.75 special handling fee. * If you need multiple units , please see our other auctions. Should you have any questions , email us. Guaranteed shipping cut on combined orders. Payment Details U.S. Shipping and Handling $9.25 Shipping Insurance per item - Sales Tax (none) _ Learn more about checkout Payment Instructions See item description</Description></Item><Item ItemID="5410"><Name>POWERBOOK 3400 6X CD-ROM DRIVE</Name><Category>Computers</Category><Category>Apple, Macintosh</Category><Category>Drives-Internal</Category><Currently>$19.99</Currently><First_Bid>$19.99</First_Bid><Number_of_Bids>1</Number_of_Bids><Bids><Bid><Bidder Rating="2559" UserID="macknick1"><Location>Venezia</Location><Country>Italy</Country></Bidder><Time>Dec-07-01 07:11:15</Time><Amount>$19.99</Amount></Bid></Bids><Location Latitude="34.175205" Longitude="-118.382212">los Angeles, CA</Location><Country>USA</Country><Started>Dec-05-01 13:11:15</Started><Ends>Dec-12-01 13:11:15</Ends><Seller Rating="0" UserID="kelstu"/><Description>This is for an internal 6x CD-ROM drive for an Apple Powerbook 3400. Used but in perfect condition. Pay by Visa or MC using PAYPAL. Please add $5 shipping within U.S. Happy bidding! Free Honesty Counters powered by Andale! Payment Details U.S. Shipping and Handling $5.00 Shipping Insurance per item (optional) $2.00 Sales Tax (none) _ Learn more about checkout Payment Instructions See item description or contact seller for more information.</Description></Item><Item ItemID="5417"><Name>Apple PowerMac Floppy Drive 2mb Drive &amp; Cable</Name><Category>Computers</Category><Category>Apple, Macintosh</Category><Category>Drives-Internal</Category><Currently>$0.99</Currently><First_Bid>$0.99</First_Bid><Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids><Bids/><Location Latitude="40.087835" Longitude="-105.373507">Broomfield, CO</Location><Country>USA</Country><Started>Dec-06-01 16:19:11</Started><Ends>Dec-11-01 16:19:11</Ends><Seller Rating="178" UserID="mtymr"/><Description>.titledata { font-family: verdana, sans-serif; font-size:17px; color:#ffffff; font-weight : bold; } .description { font-family: verdana, sans-serif; color:#336699; background-color : #ffffff; } .link { font-family: verdana, sans-serif; font-size:12px; underline; } HR { color: #336699; } Apple PowerMac Floppy Drive 2mb Drive &amp; Cable _ _ _ You are bidding on a Apple PowerMac Floppy Drive 2mb Drive &amp; Cable . It is perfectly working, and is in good cosmetic shape. _ _ __Specifications _ _ _ _ __Type _ _ _ _ _ _ __2mb Sony Floppy Drive _ _ _ _ __Model # _ _ _ _ _ _ 9506/031 __ MPF52A _ _ __Compatible Systems _ _ _ __Apple PowerMac Series Computers Radius Mactionsh Clones Motarola Mactintosh Clones And Others_ _ __Condition _ _ _ __Working_ Pulled Working From A Radius 81/110 _ __Accessorys Included _ _ _ __Radius 81/110 Rails Floppy Cable _ _ Buyer is responsible for a flat rate of $12.00 for priority USPS (insured), anywhere in the 48 contiguous states. Other shipping options available upon request. Payment must be made within 7 days with Paypal, Billpoint, Cashiers Check, or by a Money Order If you have any questions, please email me! Happy bidding! I accept PayPal, the #1 payment service in online auctions! Payment I accept the following forms of payment: PayPal, Billpoint, Visa/Master Card, Money Order, Cashier's Check. Additional Information _ Low cost image hosting and full service auction management solutions: AuctionWatch Visit Atom-Matix Computers today! Payment Details See item description and Payment Instructions, or contact seller for more information. Payment Instructions See item description or contact seller for more information.</Description></Item><Item ItemID="5449"><Name>Seagate 2.5 SCSI HD &amp; NEC CD-ROM Combo</Name><Category>Computers</Category><Category>Apple, Macintosh</Category><Category>Drives-Internal</Category><Currently>$31.77</Currently><First_Bid>$31.77</First_Bid><Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids><Bids/><Location Latitude="40.298988" Longitude="-76.847194">Harrisburg PA</Location><Country>USA</Country><Started>Dec-09-01 00:25:18</Started><Ends>Dec-12-01 00:25:18</Ends><Seller Rating="623" UserID="mlujanac@paonline.com"/><Description>Seagate 2.5 SCSI HD &amp; NEC CD-ROM Combo Nice clean units are tested, working, and as always, guaranteed not DOA. Seagate Barracuda model ST32550N 50 pin 7200RPM SCSI hard drive and NEC 8X SCSI 50 pin CD-ROM are both nice clean working pulls and as a pair, will save you a bundle on shipping! Buyer pays just 8.95 shipping USA, and 12.00 to Canada. Thanks, and happy bidding! NO RESERVE We accept Paypal, Ebay Payments, Bidpay, money orders, and US personal checks. MAILING ADDRESS IS MICHAEL LUJANAC 1777 SHEEPFORD RD MECHANICSBURG PA 17055 USA. Please include item number and ship to address on separate sheet. Thanks for looking and happy bidding! Buyer to pay $8.95 for shipping and handling. Click here to view my other auctions. This listing created by eBay Seller's Assistant Pro</Description></Item><Item ItemID="5450"><Name>NEC 8 X SCSI CD-ROM Apple or PC</Name><Category>Computers</Category><Category>Apple, Macintosh</Category><Category>Drives-Internal</Category><Currently>$8.88</Currently><First_Bid>$8.88</First_Bid><Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids><Bids/><Location Latitude="40.298988" Longitude="-76.847194">Harrisburg PA</Location><Country>USA</Country><Started>Dec-09-01 00:59:19</Started><Ends>Dec-12-01 00:59:19</Ends><Seller Rating="623" UserID="mlujanac@paonline.com"/><Description>NEC 8 X SCSI CD-ROM Apple or PC Nice clean units are tested, working, and as always, guaranteed not DOA. NEC model CDR-1410A is nice clean working pull. Tested and backed by our 10 day replacement guarantee. Buyer pays 6.50 shipping USA , 9.00 to Canada. Thanks for looking, and happy bidding! NO RESERVE We accept Paypal, Ebay Payments, Bidpay, money orders, and US personal checks. MAILING ADDRESS IS MICHAEL LUJANAC 1777 SHEEPFORD RD MECHANICSBURG PA 17055 USA. Please include item number and ship to address on separate sheet. Thanks for looking and happy bidding! Buyer to pay $6.50 for shipping and handling. Click here to view my other auctions. This listing created by eBay Seller's Assistant Pro</Description></Item><Item ItemID="5453"><Name>16mb SO-DIMM Latitude LM XP XPi; Zeinth &amp; CTX</Name><Category>Computers</Category><Category>Laptops &amp; Accessories</Category><Category>Accessories</Category><Category>Memory Upgrades</Category><Currently>$17.5</Currently><First_Bid>$17.5</First_Bid><Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids><Bids/><Location>historic Old Town, Alexandria, VA 22314</Location><Country>USA</Country><Started>Dec-09-01 14:39:14</Started><Ends>Dec-14-01 14:39:14</Ends><Seller Rating="985" UserID="rad-dyn"/><Description>16mb 3.3-volt 72-pin SO-DIMM for DELL Latitude, Zenith, and CTX * Works in many notebooks and the Dells listed below * Standard 16mb (4mbX32-70ns) Fast Page Mode (FPM) SO-DIMM * FPM will work in place of EDO * Used modules assembled approximately 4 years ago * These are factory original from either Samsung or Hitachi * Engineered to last 50-years * 30-day warranty is included Upon your bid for both 16mb modules, I will end the auction early. The picture above is a front and back photo of a 16mb module! SOME COMPATABLE NOTEBOOK COMPUTERS: CTX DeskTop: 70LS CTX EasyBook: 700; 720CS; 722CS; 725CS; 750CDT; 750CDS; 750CS; 750M; 770; 772; 772MS; and 774 Dell Latitude LM: M133ST; M166ST; P100SD; P133ST; and P166 Dell Latitude XP: 450C; 475C; 4100C; and 4100CX Dell Latitude XPi: CD M133ST; CD M166ST; CD P150ST; P75D; P75T; P90; P90D; P90ST; P90T; P100SD; P120D; P120ST; and P133ST. Zenith Z-NoteFlex: 486SX33; 486DX2/50; 486DX4/75; 486DX4/100; and P Pentium 75 Shipping: For any quantity the package ships for only $2 via first-class or $4 via priority mail, uninsured. Shipping via UPS, insured, is $6 within the contiguous 48 United States. UPS shipment to AK or HI will require air freight charges. No international shipping service. Payment Terms: Cashier's check or money order puts your order at the front of the shipping queue. A personal or company check requires a hold of up to 21 days. Please note that our offices will be closed during the last week of December 2001. Pay on-line with it is fast, easy and it is without any service charge until December 17, 2001. Send a money order on-line with No need to wait for the payment to get here. Product ships to your credit-card billing address upon an e-mail confirmation from BidPay. AUCTION TERMS AND INFORMATION: Payment must be received within 14-days of close of the auction. Failure to get the payment to R&amp;D Dynamics, Inc. in the allotted time will result in a Non-Paying Bidder Alert form being issued. A high-bidder failing to pay is subject to negative feedback. Length of warranty is that stated in this auction. Any merchandise sold _as-is_ is sold with no warranty. All sales are final. R&amp;D Dynamics must be notified of defective merchandise within 10 days from the date of purchase. The customer is responsible for compatibility, suitability, usefulness and/or utility of the merchandise. No returns except for defective merchandise accompanied by the receipt provided with the product, defective merchandise will be repaired or replaced. No unauthorized returns. An RMA (return materials authorization) must be issued and that number must appear on the returned package. R&amp;D Dynamics shall make final determination as to the existence and cause of any alleged defect. Warranty excludes physically damaged merchandise. Non-defective or physically damaged merchandise will be returned to the buyer upon payment for examination, testing and shipping charges. Merchandise returned for refund is subject to a 20% restocking fee based upon the purchase price or current market price. There is a $25 returned check fee plus 1% monthly service charge for delinquent accounts. The delinquent customer assumes any and all collection costs incurred by R&amp;D Dynamics. Free Honesty Counters powered by Andale! Payment Details See item description and Payment Instructions, or contact seller for more information. Payment Instructions See item description or contact seller for more information.</Description></Item><Item ItemID="5458"><Name>32MB RAM for 600 770 1400 1720 ThinkPad</Name><Category>Computers</Category><Category>Laptops &amp; Accessories</Category><Category>Accessories</Category><Category>Memory Upgrades</Category><Currently>$4.95</Currently><First_Bid>$4.95</First_Bid><Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids><Bids/><Location Latitude="40.298988" Longitude="-76.847194">Harrisburg, PA</Location><Country>USA</Country><Started>Dec-09-01 17:48:46</Started><Ends>Dec-16-01 17:48:46</Ends><Seller Rating="2898" UserID="pcsurplusonline.com"/><Description>32 MB (4Mx64) SODIMM Non Parity 66Mhz 3.3V Cherish the Memory! PCSurplusOnline.com is back with another outrageous deal for laptop owners longing to get more from their machines... 32MB SO DIMM Non-Parity 66Mhz RAM! Yes, now you can breathe easy knowing your laptop won't buckle under your workload, and keep the focus on productivity, like you want to. Any time we run these specials on RAM, they always go fast, so act quickly and reap the benefits of improved performance. SDRAM for ThinkPad 600, 770, TP i Series 1400, 1720 Always Check with Your Manufacturer for Compatibility Click Image to Enlarge SBT IB-42H2819 Memory Type: 32 MB (4Mx64) SO DIMM Non Parity 66Mhz 3.3V Condition: These items are Working Pulls Payment / Shipping &amp; Handling &amp;#160 Cashiers Check, Money Order or PayPal &amp;#160 Continental U.S. : &amp;#160 $8 +5 each additional (PA Residents Please Add 6% Sales Tax) &amp;#160 Alaska + Hawaii : &amp;#160 $12 + 8 each additional Cashiers Check, Money Order and PayPal Only &amp;#160 Canada : &amp;#160 $18 + 15 each additional We will only accept International PayPal &amp;#160 International : Call 1-717-233-6650 or email: intl@pcpartsinc.com for rates. &amp;#160&amp;#149 All payments must be prepaid (refer to chart for payment options) - NO CODs. &amp;#160&amp;#149The above Shipping, Handling and Processing charges enable us to ensure that your purchase is delivered safely and in a timely manner. The costs incurred cover shipping, handling, tracking, and insurance. Shipping : PCSurplusOnline has partnered with FedEx as our preferred carrier for added reliability and convenience. Handling and Processing : These services include receiving, storing, transferring and preparing the product for shipment, and credit card processing. Most products are shipped directly from PCSurplusOnline_s state-of-the-art warehouse. Packages are carefully processed from the moment the product is removed from inventory to the point at which they are transferred to the carrier. Tracking: All products shipped by PCSurplusOnline are traceable Insurance : Deliveries are insured and guaranteed against loss, theft and damage &amp;#160&amp;#149 We WILL NOT ship to P.O. Boxes! &amp;#149 International customers, please email us for special instructions PRIOR to bidding. &amp;#160&amp;#149 We usually ship out the item(s) 2 to 3 business days after receipt of payment (Please allow extra 5 days for computers, printers, and monitors for proper testing and cleaning). Terms &amp; Conditions &amp;#160Warranty: &amp;#160&amp;#149 These items are working pulls. &amp;#160&amp;#149 On the rare occasion that a product arrives damaged (i.e., DOA), we reserve the right to repair, replace, or refund at our discretion. &amp;#160&amp;#149 All returns must be shipped back in original packaging and require an RMA number. This warranty is for exchange only - NO REFUNDS! Bid with confidence from an Ebay Powerseller! General: &amp;#160&amp;#149 All eBay bids and sales are final. &amp;#160&amp;#149 Payment must be received within 10 days of the close of the auction. &amp;#160&amp;#149 Call us at 1-800-666-9373 with any questions regarding the auction. &amp;#160&amp;#149 A bid on our auction states that you have read and agreed to all Terms and Conditions . Please, do not bid if you do not intend to complete your winning bid. We will leave negative feedback for all deadbeat bidders and report you to eBay. &amp;#160What To Do When The Auction Closes: Our sales department will contact you after auction close via email. We will typically email your payment instructions within 48 hours of the auction ending. If you do not receive the email, please feel free to call us at 1-800-666-9373 for payment instructions. Once you receive the e-mail, please follow the instructions enclosed. Payment: We accept Money Orders, Cashier Checks, Major Credit Cards, and PayPal (NO CODs) : PayPal customers: When paying by PayPal, please use our ID paypal@pcpartsinc.com. We're sorry, but we do not accept payments over $50 that are not verified and/or do not have a confirmed address . Should you choose to use a credit card, you will be given the location of our secure server to complete your order online. Credit card orders will be processed immediately. Therefore, if you are anxious to receive your merchandise, this is your best option. If you choose to send a money order, please fill out and send along a copy of the email. Please be patient and wait for your product to be shipped. Once your payment has been received, we will ship within 1-2 business days (please allow an extra 5 days for computers, printers, &amp; monitors for proper testing and cleaning) However, if a money order is submitted for payment, please allow an extra 5-7 working days for processing. Making you a satisfied customer is our #1 goal. Please feel free to e-mail us with any questions. Our friendly sales team will be more than happy to assist you. Thank you for your business and HAPPY BIDDING! Free Honesty Counters powered by Andale! Payment Details See item description and Payment Instructions, or contact seller for more information. Payment Instructions See item description or contact seller for more information.</Description></Item><Item ItemID="5478"><Name>Lot of 3 SCSI 50 Pin CD-ROMs</Name><Category>Computers</Category><Category>Apple, Macintosh</Category><Category>Drives-Internal</Category><Currently>$17.77</Currently><First_Bid>$17.77</First_Bid><Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids><Bids/><Location Latitude="40.298988" Longitude="-76.847194">Harrisburg PA</Location><Country>USA</Country><Started>Dec-10-01 10:02:07</Started><Ends>Dec-13-01 10:02:07</Ends><Seller Rating="623" UserID="mlujanac@paonline.com"/><Description>Lot of 3 SCSI 50 Pin CD-ROMs Nice clean units are tested and working, and as always, guaranteed not DOA. Lot of 3 SCSI standard 50 pin interface CD-ROM drives includes various makes such as NEC CDR-1410A, Apple 600i, Apple 300+, Plextor 6Plex or 8Plex, IBM/Matsushita, and/or various others. They are all tested, working, and carry 10 day replacement warranty. All work in Apple as well as PC. Please see manufacturer's websites for installation issues. Lots of 3 are randomly prepackaged for ease of handling, and are priced to go. NO RESERVE We accept Paypal, Ebay Payments, money orders, and US personal checks. MAILING ADDRESS IS MICHAEL LUJANAC 1777 SHEEPFORD RD MECHANICSBURG PA 17055 USA. Please include item number and ship to address on separate sheet. Thanks for looking at our auctions, and happy bidding! Buyer to pay $9.95 for shipping and handling. Click here to view my other auctions. This listing created by eBay Seller's Assistant Pro</Description></Item><Item ItemID="5481"><Name>HP LJ 4MV PRINTER W/250Tray Feed-44MB-46K.Pgs</Name><Category>Computers</Category><Category>Printers &amp; Supplies</Category><Category>Laser Printers</Category><Category>B&amp;W</Category><Category>HP</Category><Currently>$213.5</Currently><Buy_Price>$903.98</Buy_Price><First_Bid>$99.99</First_Bid><Number_of_Bids>3</Number_of_Bids><Bids><Bid><Bidder Rating="1626" UserID="bgoodno@prodigy.net"><Location>Venezia</Location><Country>Italy</Country></Bidder><Time>Dec-11-01 15:50:37</Time><Amount>$137.83</Amount></Bid><Bid><Bidder Rating="12" UserID="southwestcenter"><Location>Venezia</Location><Country>Italy</Country></Bidder><Time>Dec-12-01 19:50:37</Time><Amount>$175.66</Amount></Bid><Bid><Bidder Rating="3949" UserID="www.autographpros.com"><Location>Venezia</Location><Country>Italy</Country></Bidder><Time>Dec-13-01 23:50:37</Time><Amount>$213.5</Amount></Bid></Bids><Location Latitude="33.792687" Longitude="-117.79975">Orange County , CA</Location><Country>USA</Country><Started>Dec-10-01 11:50:37</Started><Ends>Dec-17-01 11:50:37</Ends><Seller Rating="30" UserID="alicia51001"/><Description>Hewlett Packard 4MV LASERJET PRINTER WIDE FORMAT UP TO 11X17 MAC COMPATIBLE WITH ADDITIONAL 250 SHEET OPTIONAL TRAYS , PAGE COUNT IS 46000 ,44 MB , WITH JET DIRECT CARD EXCELLENT GOOD WORKING CONDITION! This printer has a monthly duty cycle of 50,000 pages per month, Printer with 600 dpi, Prints up to 11x17and up to 16 pages per minute! Printer shipped with a power cord, cartridge . This printer weighs approx. 64lbs &amp; shipping costs $49.00. Product Specifications: Printing - 16 pages per minute Paper trays &amp; Media Sizes Letter, Legal, A4, Executive, 3.9x5.8in., 11x17in, B4, B5 Two Standard Trays One 100-sheet Multipurpose (Manual Feed) paper tray for up to 11x17 paper One 250-sheet paper tray Plain Paper, Envelopes, Transparencies, Labels Full Bleed Compatible Processor - 35 MHz Intel 80960CF RISC Duty Cycle (pages per month expected) -50,000 Languages - Enhanced HP PCL5 Postscript - Level 2 Interfaces -IEEE 1284-Complaint Parallel Port Compatibility - MacOS, MS-DOS, OS/2, Windows3.x, Windows 9x, Windows NT 3.51, Windows NT 4.0 Buyer to pay shipping and insurance. I accept Ebay billpoint , Paypal, Cashiers checks/Money orders. Buyer must pay for shipping Cost Plus $10.00 Packaging (FoamPack).</Description></Item><Item ItemID="5487"><Name>PERSONAL LASERWRITER 300 LASER PRINTER</Name><Category>Computers</Category><Category>Printers &amp; Supplies</Category><Category>Laser Printers</Category><Category>B&amp;W</Category><Category>Other</Category><Currently>$1.0</Currently><First_Bid>$1.0</First_Bid><Number_of_Bids>1</Number_of_Bids><Bids><Bid><Bidder Rating="160" UserID="bub63uk"><Location>Venezia</Location><Country>Italy</Country></Bidder><Time>Dec-12-01 09:42:05</Time><Amount>$1.0</Amount></Bid></Bids><Location Latitude="30.548421" Longitude="-91.6325">Louisiana</Location><Country>USA</Country><Started>Dec-10-01 15:42:05</Started><Ends>Dec-17-01 15:42:05</Ends><Seller Rating="330" UserID="auctions@compexbr.com"/><Description>PERSONAL LASERWRITER 300 LASER PRINTER This is a used Personal Laserwriter 300 laser printer. It does power on and the green light comes on, but we have not tested it while connected to a computer, therefore, a test print could not be obtained. The outer casing appears to be in very good condition. There is a toner cartridge and power cord included. We do provide a 5 Day DOA warranty, but this does not include the toner cartridge. Buyer pays $25.00 shipping and handling within the Continental United States. International buyers must call to get the total charges. Auction Information All items are used/refurbished unless stated otherwise above. All items do not include manuals, drivers, software, ink/toner, cables unless otherwise stated above. Always assume you will only get what is in the picture. If there is no software or accessories displayed in the picture of the item, they are not included. The text under the picture states warranty info and/or included items if applicable, this supersedes the description text if there is any discrepancy. After you receive the email from eBay, you will then receive one from us with payment instructions. Since we use the first email from eBay to send these payment instructions, there will be a delay between the time the auction closes and the email from us. Please be patient as eBay can take a long time to send that email and sometimes never sends it at all. If you do not receive this email after 24-48 hours, then please email us with the item number of the auction. Payment Options We accept Paypal, Mastercard, Visa, American Express, Discover, cashiers checks, money orders. Payment is due within ten (10) business days from the close of the auction. Non-paying bidders will receive negative feedback and a Non-Paying Alert will be filed. Shipping Shipping will be made via UPS regular ground within 24 hours of receipt of payment unless notified otherwise. Buyer is responsible for shipping and handling fees and any other fees related to international shipping. We will ship to any country unless specified otherwise in the item description. Freight damage claims must be reported to the delivering driver immediately, shortages and damages must be reported within 7 days of receipt of merchandise or we will not be responsible to any losses incurred. Item Description The items listed are described as accurately as possible. Picture below is of actual item, unless otherwise noted above. If you are uncertain about anything, do not make any assumptions- ask before you bid. Picture below is of actual item unless otherwise noted above. Warranty All products are guaranteed to be in working condition at the time of arrival unless the item is sold "as is" and is so specified in the item description. Buyer must notify seller within 5 business days of receipt of the item if the item is received in non-working condition. There shall be no warranty on software. Return Policy Any item returned for warranty must be returned in the same condition it was received. We reserve the right to repair or replace the item or refund the purchase price at our discretion. Return shipping shall be the responsibility of the buyer. Bid with Confidence! This auction tracked with the Shooting Star. Payment Details See item description and Payment Instructions, or contact seller for more information. Payment Instructions See item description or contact seller for more information.</Description></Item><Item ItemID="5490"><Name>NEW 60GB IBM 60GXP Hard Drive, 7200RPM</Name><Category>Computers</Category><Category>Drives, Media</Category><Category>Drives</Category><Category>Hard Drives-IDE</Category><Currently>$160.0</Currently><First_Bid>$160.0</First_Bid><Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids><Bids/><Location Latitude="34.087108" Longitude="-117.96966">Baldwin Park CA</Location><Country>USA</Country><Started>Dec-10-01 17:16:16</Started><Ends>Dec-17-01 17:16:16</Ends><Seller Rating="1074" UserID="usmtelecom"/><Description>_ Please view our eBay auctions: All auction items Our Hard Drive onchinahd 35HD HDIBMl060 Payment: We accept payment by approved Paypal, Visa, Mastercard, money order or cashiers check processed immediately and will be shipped out on the same day. California residents add 8.00% sales tax. ( We don't accept Debit cards ) Shipping: Shipping for all bidders residing in the 48 continental United States are to add $10.00 to the final price for shipping &amp; handling, and insurance via UPS Ground. Hawaii, Alaska, Puerto Rico with additional charge of $10 (total of $20). Additional item cost $5 to ship. Payments made before 2:00 pm will be shipped same day. Any orders that come in after 2:00 pm we can not gaurantee that it will be shipped on the same day. Anything being shipped USPS goes out every Tuesday morning and Friday morning. Currently we only ship to the United States and do not accept international orders. Warranty: 1 Year Warranty: W e issue refund, minus the freight charge, for any return within 30 days. Thereafter we issue replacement for any RMA for up to 1 year. If any defects in material and workmanship appear during the warranty period, please mail to sales@onchina.com Subj: RMA for a RMA number. Damaged product will be replaced or repaired at our option. This warranty does not cover normal wear and tear, improper handling or accidental damage caused by travel carriers. Note: We do not refund the freight portion. _ 60GB IBM Deskstar 60GXP 7200RPM HARD Drive (IBM IC35L060AVER07) auction by usmtelecom Highlights The award-winning IBM Deskstar* family provides industry-leading performance at 7200 RPM, 494 Mbits/sec internal transfer rates, and 8.5 ms average seek times- enabling sustained data rates of up to 40 MB/sec. Capacities range from 20 to 60 GB. An Ultra ATA/100 interface optimizes system performance. Unique design attributes enable shock protection to 400 G. Reduced acoustics enable extremely quiet operation at 3.1 Bels. Idle power consumes only 6.7 watts. Leading drive technology The IBM Deskstar 60GXP disk drive combines new and proven technologies to greatly enhance system performance and capacity--handling a wide range of advanced desktop and audio/video applications. Features such as low acoustics, reduced power, and tagged command queuing are ideal for low-cost routers, entry- level servers, and switches. Advanced desktop systems IBM continues to define state-of-the-art for storage. The high capacities and fast speeds of IBM Deskstar drives support higher quality digital audio/video storage, superior digital content creation capabilities, and significantly faster processing for multimedia and Internet applications. Technology for performance Increased track capacity and servo bandwidth combine with enhanced buffer throughput to significantly improve performance over the previous generation IBM drive. A 2 MB buffer uses advanced buffer management and hardware assisted caching to streamline data transfer. In addition, more servo pulses help ensure faster and more accurate head positioning to reduce head settling time. The IBM Deskstar 60GXP also supports Tagged Command Queuing and Rotational Position Optimization to further enhance throughput for data-intensive Windows NT** and UNIX** applications. Technology for reliability The industry's highest areal density increases capacity while reducing component count to improve reliability. Second-generation load/unload head ramps help protect data from drive mishandling, further enhancing reliability. In addition, glass media provides a smoother disk surface and greater rigidity to reduce the impact of shock. Ceramic spindle bearings and a tri-lamenate top cover reduce acoustics to just 3.1 Bels--a level that matches or improves upon many 5400 RPM models. Circuits and motors are also optimized to save power and reduce system temperature- extending system life and reliability. Deskstar drives utilize proven IBM technologies such as TrueTrack* servo and No- ID* sector formatting, as well as IBM Drive Fitness Test* (DFT), S.M.A.R.T. Self Test, and error logging. _ IBM Deskstar 60GXP at a glance Configuration Interface ATA Capacity (GB) 60GB Sector size (bytes) 512 Recording zones 18 User cylinders (physical) 27,724 Data heads (physical) 6/4/2 Data disks 3/2/1 Max. areal density (Gbits/sq. inch) 15.3 Max. recording density (BPI) 449k Track density (TPI) 34,000 Performance Data buffer 2MB Rotational speed (RPM) 7200 Latency (average ms) 4.17 Media transfer rate (max Mbits/sec) 494 Interface transfer rate (max MB/sec) 100 Sustained data rate (MB/sec) 20.9 to 40.8 Seek time (read typical) _ _Average (ms) 8.5 _ _Track-to-track (ms) 1.2 _ _Full-track (ms) 15.0 Reliability Error rate (nonrecoverable) 1 in 10E13 Start stop cycles (load/unload at 40_ C) 40,000 Power Requirement +5 VDC (+- 5%), +12 VDC (+10%/-8%) Dissipation (typical) _ _Startup current _ _(max A) 2.0(12v) _ _Idle (W) 6.7(3,2,1 disks) Physical size Height (mm) 25.4 Width (mm) 101.6 Depth (mm) 146 Weight (max g) 590 (3 disks), 575 (2 disks), 560 (1 disk) Environmental characteristics _ Operating Nonoperating Ambient temperature 5 to 55_ C -40 to 65_ C Relative humidity (noncondensing) 8% to 90% 5% to 95% Maximum wet bulb (noncondensing) 29.4_ C 35_ C Shock (half sine wave) 55_G/2_ms 400 G (2, 1 disks)_ 350 G (3 disks)_ _ Vibration (random [RMS]) 0.67 G_for_horizontal, 0.56_for_vertical 1.04 G Acoustics (idle) Bels 3.1 (3 disks), 3.0 (2 disks), 2.9 (1 disk) _ The above information exerted from IBM website. For more detail please see www.ibm.com Payment Details See item description and Payment Instructions, or contact seller for more information. Payment Instructions See item description or contact seller for more information.</Description></Item><Item ItemID="5503"><Name>XEROX Document WorkCentre 250 "NEW FOR PARTS"</Name><Category>Computers</Category><Category>Printers &amp; Supplies</Category><Category>Laser Printers</Category><Category>B&amp;W</Category><Category>Other</Category><Currently>$19.99</Currently><First_Bid>$19.99</First_Bid><Number_of_Bids>1</Number_of_Bids><Bids><Bid><Bidder Rating="68" UserID="ushemp"><Location>Venezia</Location><Country>Italy</Country></Bidder><Time>Dec-12-01 13:50:30</Time><Amount>$19.99</Amount></Bid></Bids><Location>Senators Country</Location><Country>Canada</Country><Started>Dec-10-01 19:50:30</Started><Ends>Dec-17-01 19:50:30</Ends><Seller Rating="116" UserID="dnrsports"/><Description>NO MANUALS, TRAYS,SIDE PHONE. THIS UNIT WAS NEVER USED, GREAT UNIT FOR PARTS. WE REMOVED THE DUST COVER FROM THE UNIT AND TO OUR SUPRIZE, WE FOUND THIS NEW UNIT. WILL PACK IT WELL..... PAYMENT BY CERTIFIED FUNDS OR INTERNATIONAL MONEY ORDER OR BILLPOINT. I WILL NOT ACCEPT PERSONAL CHECKS. CASH ACCEPTED, BUT I WILL NOT TAKE RESPONSIBILITY FOR LOSS IN THE MAIL. BUYER TO ADD $15.00 FOR SHIPPING VIA REGULAR MAIL - AT BUYERS RISK (INSURED REGISTERED SHIPPING IS $25.00)IT'S A PRETTY LARGE PACKAGE . PLEASE DO NOT BID UNLESS YOU INTEND ON PAYING. PAYMENT TO BE RECIEVED WITHIN 10 DAYS OF AUCTION END. NON-PAYER NOTICES WILL BE FILED SHOULD PAYMENT NOT BE RECIEVED IN A TIMELY MANNER. SELLER RESERVES THE RIGHT TO CANCEL BIDS WHERE BIDDER HAS NEGATIVE FEEDBACK. PLEASE CHECK OUT MY OTHER AUCTIONS 0F QUALITY INSERTS AND ROOKIE CARDS. GOOD LUCK WITH YOUR BIDDING. Payment Details U.S. Shipping and Handling $15.00 Shipping Insurance per item - Sales Tax (none) _ Learn more about checkout Payment Instructions See item description or contact seller for more information.</Description></Item><Item ItemID="5507"><Name>_SUPERB~ IBM PC-100 64MB DIMM_</Name><Category>Computers</Category><Category>Laptops &amp; Accessories</Category><Category>Accessories</Category><Category>Memory Upgrades</Category><Currently>$25.95</Currently><First_Bid>$25.95</First_Bid><Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids><Bids/><Location Latitude="40.298988" Longitude="-76.847194">Harrisburg, PA</Location><Country>USA</Country><Started>Dec-10-01 20:17:03</Started><Ends>Dec-15-01 20:17:03</Ends><Seller Rating="2898" UserID="pcsurplusonline.com"/><Description>SUPERB~ IBM PC-100 64MB DIMM Remember, You Wanted Some Memory We can always use more memory don't you think. Programs run faster. No need to worry about under buffering. Don't forget to pick up your memory today. &amp;nbsp ; FRU # 20L2202 Features: &amp;#160 &amp;#149 64MB RAM &amp;#149 DIMM &amp;#149 PC-100 Click To Enlarge Picture Condition: Memory is a working system pull. Only 10 auctions per order for bulk shipping rates Payment / Shipping &amp; Handling &amp;#160 Cashiers Check, Money Order or PayPal &amp;#160 Continental U.S. : &amp;#160 $5 + 2 each additional (PA Residents Please Add 6% Sales Tax) &amp;#160 Alaska + Hawaii : &amp;#160 $7 + 4 each additional Cashiers Check, Money Order and PayPal Only &amp;#160 Canada : &amp;#160 $12 + 8 each additional We will only accept International PayPal &amp;#160 International : Call 1-717-233-6650 or email: intl@pcpartsinc.com for rates. &amp;#160&amp;#149 All payments must be prepaid (refer to chart for payment options) - NO CODs. &amp;#160&amp;#149The above Shipping, Handling and Processing charges enable us to ensure that your purchase is delivered safely and in a timely manner. The costs incurred cover shipping, handling, tracking, and insurance. Shipping : PCSurplusOnline has partnered with FedEx as our preferred carrier for added reliability and convenience. Handling and Processing : These services include receiving, storing, transferring and preparing the product for shipment, and credit card processing. Most products are shipped directly from PCSurplusOnline_s state-of-the-art warehouse. Packages are carefully processed from the moment the product is removed from inventory to the point at which they are transferred to the carrier. Tracking: All products shipped by PCSurplusOnline are traceable Insurance : Deliveries are insured and guaranteed against loss, theft and damage &amp;#160&amp;#149 We WILL NOT ship to P.O. Boxes! &amp;#149 International customers, please email us for special instructions PRIOR to bidding. &amp;#160&amp;#149 We usually ship out the item(s) 2 to 3 business days after receipt of payment (Please allow extra 5 days for computers, printers, and monitors for proper testing and cleaning). Terms &amp; Conditions &amp;#160Warranty: &amp;#160 &amp;#149 Condition: Memory is a working system pull. &amp;#160&amp;#149 On the rare occasion that a product arrives damaged (i.e., DOA), we reserve the right to repair, replace, or refund at our discretion. &amp;#160&amp;#149 All returns must be shipped back in original packaging and require an RMA number. This warranty is for exchange only - NO REFUNDS! Bid with confidence from an Ebay Powerseller ! General: &amp;#160&amp;#149 All eBay bids and sales are final. &amp;#160&amp;#149 Payment must be received within 10 days of the close of the auction. &amp;#160&amp;#149 Call us at 1-800-666-9373 with any questions regarding the auction. &amp;#160&amp;#149 A bid on our auction states that you have read and agreed to all Terms and Conditions . Please, do not bid if you do not intend to complete your winning bid. We will leave negative feedback for all deadbeat bidders and report you to eBay. &amp;#160What To Do When The Auction Closes: Our sales department will contact you after auction close via email. We will typically email your payment instructions within 48 hours of the auction ending. If you do not receive the email, please feel free to call us at 1-800-666-9373 for payment instructions. Once you receive the e-mail, please follow the instructions enclosed. Payment: We accept Money Orders, Cashier Checks, Major Credit Cards, and PayPal (NO CODs) : PayPal customers: When paying by PayPal, please use our ID paypal@pcpartsinc.com. We're sorry, but we do not accept payments over $50 that are not verified and/or do not have a confirmed address . Should you choose to use a credit card, you will be given the location of our secure server to complete your order online. Credit card orders will be processed immediately. Therefore, if you are anxious to receive your merchandise, this is your best option. If you choose to send a money order, please fill out and send along a copy of the email. Please be patient and wait for your product to be shipped. Once your payment has been received, we will ship within 1-2 business days (please allow an extra 5 days for computers, printers, &amp; monitors for proper testing and cleaning) However, if a money order is submitted for payment, please allow an extra 5-7 working days for processing. Making you a satisfied customer is our #1 goal. Please feel free to e-mail us with any questions. Our friendly sales team will be more than happy to assist you. Thank you for your business and HAPPY BIDDING! Free Honesty Counters powered by Andale! Payment Details See item description and Payment Instructions, or contact seller for more information. Payment Instructions See item description or contact seller for more information.</Description></Item><Item ItemID="5511"><Name>HP LaserJet Series II AC Power Supply</Name><Category>Computers</Category><Category>Printers &amp; Supplies</Category><Category>Laser Printers</Category><Category>B&amp;W</Category><Category>HP</Category><Currently>$14.95</Currently><First_Bid>$14.95</First_Bid><Number_of_Bids>1</Number_of_Bids><Bids><Bid><Bidder Rating="377" UserID="dannyly"><Location>Venezia</Location><Country>Italy</Country></Bidder><Time>Dec-13-01 03:02:54</Time><Amount>$14.95</Amount></Bid></Bids><Location>NorthShore</Location><Country>USA</Country><Started>Dec-11-01 09:02:54</Started><Ends>Dec-18-01 09:02:54</Ends><Seller Rating="40" UserID="elliepelican"/><Description>This is a genuine Hewlett Packard LaserJet Series II AC power supply module, part #RG9-0205-000CN, 100/115V. This component is from spares stock of a certified HP field technician. This has been tested and is in excellent condition. Shipping to 48 states is $7.50 and PayPal is accepted. After purchasing, pay instantly with your credit card through PayPal! function dw(nu){document.write(s1+"ppslv"+nu+".gif"+s2+sA[nu]);}f1="document.links";s1="\ ","\"Winning bidder, click here to pay instantly by credit card!\"\","\"Winning bidder, click here to pay instantly by credit card!\"\");c1=c2=c3=c4=0;for(i=0;i =0){c1++;}else if((eval(f1+"["+i+"].search")).indexOf("BetterSeller")=0){c2++;}else if((eval(f1+"["+i+"].search")).indexOf("ListItemForSaleShow")=0){c3++;}else if((eval(f1+"["+i+"].hash")).indexOf("ListItemForSaleAutosShow")=0){c4++;}}if((c1=2)||(c20)||(c30)||(c40)){dw(3);}else{dw(2);}f11="xclick-auction";f13="iid=";f14="";for(i=0;i 0){s11=document.links[i].search;j=s11.indexOf(f13);if(j0){s11=s11.slice((j+(f13.length)));for(k=0;k =0){var p=new Array();p[0]=document.links[i].protocol;p[1]=document.links[i].hostname;p[2]=document.links[i].pathname;for(j=0;j Free Honesty Counters powered by Andale! Payment Details U.S. Shipping and Handling $7.50 Shipping Insurance per item - Sales Tax (0.000% if shipped to none) _ Learn more about checkout Payment Instructions I prefer PayPal for funds transfer, money orders ok, email for name and address.</Description></Item><Item ItemID="5522"><Name>Kingston 32 Meg and 4 Meg Memory Cards</Name><Category>Computers</Category><Category>Laptops &amp; Accessories</Category><Category>Accessories</Category><Category>Memory Upgrades</Category><Currently>$2.0</Currently><Buy_Price>$4.4</Buy_Price><First_Bid>$2.0</First_Bid><Number_of_Bids>1</Number_of_Bids><Bids><Bid><Bidder Rating="17" UserID="nonamestarr"><Location>Venezia</Location><Country>Italy</Country></Bidder><Time>Dec-13-01 08:10:59</Time><Amount>$2.0</Amount></Bid></Bids><Location Latitude="33.276539" Longitude="-112.18717">phoenix, AZ</Location><Country>USA</Country><Started>Dec-11-01 14:10:59</Started><Ends>Dec-18-01 14:10:59</Ends><Seller Rating="12" UserID="levelzero"/><Description>Kingston 32 Meg and 4 Meg Memory Cards I have two kengston memory cards up for auction. I have used both of them and they should work just fine. They work in older 486 and pentium I laptops. Money order or certified check are accepted and shipping is 4 dollars Free Honesty Counters powered by Andale! Payment Details U.S. Shipping and Handling $4.00 Shipping Insurance per item - Sales Tax (none) _ Learn more about checkout Payment Instructions See item description or contact seller for more information.</Description></Item><Item ItemID="5524"><Name>128MB IBM THINKPAD Laptop MEMORY BEST$10 OFF</Name><Category>Computers</Category><Category>Laptops &amp; Accessories</Category><Category>Accessories</Category><Category>Memory Upgrades</Category><Currently>$9.99</Currently><First_Bid>$9.99</First_Bid><Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids><Bids/><Location Latitude="27.405429" Longitude="-82.543519">Tallhassee, FL</Location><Country>USA</Country><Started>Dec-11-01 14:38:56</Started><Ends>Dec-14-01 14:38:56</Ends><Seller Rating="30" UserID="charliefsu"/><Description>128MB IBM THINKPAD Laptop MEMORY BEST$10 OFF v\:* {behavior:url(#default#VML);} o\:* {behavior:url(#default#VML);} w\:* {behavior:url(#default#VML);} .shape {behavior:url(#default#VML);} 128MB IBM THINKPAD Laptop Memory! MADE WITH BEST CHIPS ON MARKET!(TOSHIBA or SAMSUNG) Limited TIME ONLY $10 off(see below) 128MB IBM THINKPAD Laptop Memory Product Information PRODUCT SPECIFICATIONS These items are Brand New Lifetime Warranty Warranty Lifetime Condition NEW Total memory 128 MB PC-100 per module Chip type SDRAM / SODIMM Pins 144-pin Length 2 5/8 inch (standard length) Height 1.25 inch (low profile) Voltage 3.3v (standard voltage) Laptop Compatibility Guide ----------------------------------Models----------------------------------- IBM - ThinkPad 240 (2609-xxx) IBM - ThinkPad 390 Pentium Series 2626-2xx,5xx,7xx IBM - ThinkPad 390E Celeron Series IBM - ThinkPad 390E Pentium II Series IBM - ThinkPad 390X Celeron 2626-9xx,Bxx,Fxx IBM - ThinkPad 390X Pentium II 2626-A,C,D,E,F,H,Jxx IBM - ThinkPad 390X Pentium III 2626-Lxx, Mxx IBM - ThinkPad 390 Pentium Series 2626-2xx,5xx,7xx IBM - ThinkPad 390E Celeron Series IBM - ThinkPad 390E Pentium II Series IBM - ThinkPad 390X Celeron 2626-9xx,Bxx,Fxx IBM - ThinkPad 390X Pentium II 2626-A,C,D,E,F,H,Jxx IBM - ThinkPad 390X Pentium III 2626-Lxx, Mxx IBM - ThinkPad 570 (2644-1xx, 2xx, 3xx) IBM - ThinkPad 570E Pentium III 2644-5xx, 6xx IBM - ThinkPad 600 2645-21U/31U IBM - ThinkPad 600 2645-35U/41U/51U/A1U IBM - ThinkPad 600 2645-45U/85U IBM - ThinkPad 600E 2645-3AU/4AU/5AU/Cxx IBM - ThinkPad 600E 2645-4BU/5BU/8BU/Bxx IBM - ThinkPad 600E 2645-8AU/AAU IBM - ThinkPad 600E 2645-A5U/55U/Bxx IBM - ThinkPad 600X (2645-3xx,4xx,7xx) IBM - ThinkPad 600X (2645-5xx,8xx,9xx) IBM - ThinkPad 770 9548-3xx, 9548-4xx IBM - ThinkPad 770 9549-1xx IBM - ThinkPad 770E 9548-5xx IBM - ThinkPad 770ED 9549-5xx IBM - ThinkPad 770X 9549-7xU IBM - ThinkPad 770Z 9549-8xU IBM - ThinkPad A20 series IBM - ThinkPad A21 series IBM - ThinkPad A22 series IBM - ThinkPad 1200 i Series IBM - ThinkPad 1300 i Series IBM - ThinkPad 1400 Series IBM - ThinkPad i Series 1410 IBM - ThinkPad i Series 1411 IBM - ThinkPad i Series 1412 IBM - ThinkPad i Series 1420 IBM - ThinkPad i Series 1421 IBM - ThinkPad i Series 1422 IBM - ThinkPad i Series 1441 IBM - ThinkPad i Series 1442 IBM - ThinkPad i Series 1450 IBM - ThinkPad i Series 1451 IBM - ThinkPad i Series 1452 IBM - ThinkPad i Series 1460 IBM - ThinkPad i Series 1472 IBM - ThinkPad i Series 1480 IBM - ThinkPad i Series 1482 IBM - ThinkPad i Series 1483 IBM - ThinkPad i Series 1492 IBM - ThinkPad i Series 14E2 IBM - ThinkPad 1500 i Series IBM - ThinkPad i Series 1512 IBM - ThinkPad i Series 1540 IBM - ThinkPad i Series 1541 IBM - ThinkPad i Series 1542 IBM - ThinkPad i Series 1550 IBM - ThinkPad i Series 1552 IBM - ThinkPad i Series 1560 IBM - ThinkPad i Series 1562 IBM - ThinkPad i Series 1592 IBM - ThinkPad i Series 1720 IBM - ThinkPad i Series 1721 IBM - ThinkPad T20 Series IBM - ThinkPad T21 Series IBM - ThinkPad T22 Series IBM - ThinkPad T23 Series IBM - ThinkPad TransNote IBM - ThinkPad X20 IBM - ALL PENTIUM III Shipping and Handling Shipping and Handling is $10.00 per each auction. Memory will be shipped via United States Postal Service. I can ship to any of the 50 states and US possessions, I WILL ship to FPO/APO military bases. I WILL ship internationally. NO RESERVE Buyer to pay $9.99 for shipping and handling.(Act as Reserve) Insurance of $2.99 MUST also be Included Click here to view my other auctions. Created by eBay Seller's Assistant Pro</Description></Item><Item ItemID="5525"><Name>HP LaserJet 8150 printer Part No:C4265A</Name><Category>Computers</Category><Category>Printers &amp; Supplies</Category><Category>Laser Printers</Category><Category>B&amp;W</Category><Category>HP</Category><Currently>$1000.0</Currently><First_Bid>$1000.0</First_Bid><Number_of_Bids>1</Number_of_Bids><Bids><Bid><Bidder Rating="112" UserID="heritagevalleysales"><Location>Venezia</Location><Country>Italy</Country></Bidder><Time>Dec-13-01 09:33:22</Time><Amount>$1000.0</Amount></Bid></Bids><Location Latitude="40.679845" Longitude="-73.986415">New York</Location><Country>USA</Country><Started>Dec-11-01 15:33:22</Started><Ends>Dec-18-01 15:33:22</Ends><Seller Rating="1" UserID="therman30"/><Description>This is a HP LaserJet 8150 11" x 17", 32 ppm, HP FastRes 1200. Almost new, used for only 2 months. 3 Year manufacture extended warranty ($900 value). list price: $1998.98 We accept bank check or money order only. Buyer pays $85.00 shipping and handling by UPS, NO returns. thanks. Payment Details See item description and Payment Instructions, or contact seller for more information. Payment Instructions See item description or contact seller for more information.</Description></Item><Item ItemID="5549"><Name>HP LaserJet 5L printer, great condition</Name><Category>Computers</Category><Category>Printers &amp; Supplies</Category><Category>Laser Printers</Category><Category>B&amp;W</Category><Category>HP</Category><Currently>$22.5</Currently><First_Bid>$20.0</First_Bid><Number_of_Bids>2</Number_of_Bids><Bids><Bid><Bidder Rating="334" UserID="rockhound34"><Location>Venezia</Location><Country>Italy</Country></Bidder><Time>Dec-13-01 05:14:26</Time><Amount>$21.25</Amount></Bid><Bid><Bidder Rating="62" UserID="greekwoman99@yahoo.com"><Location>Venezia</Location><Country>Italy</Country></Bidder><Time>Dec-14-01 14:50:26</Time><Amount>$22.5</Amount></Bid></Bids><Location Latitude="37.189396" Longitude="-121.705327">San Jose, CA</Location><Country>USA</Country><Started>Dec-11-01 19:38:26</Started><Ends>Dec-18-01 19:38:26</Ends><Seller Rating="32" UserID="theresafrazee"/><Description>This is an HP 5L LaserJet printer in good working and cosmetic condition. The printer comes by itself with no manual or power cord included. Buyer adds $25 for shipping. I accept payment by paypal only. Good luck! Payment Details See item description and Payment Instructions, or contact seller for more information. Payment Instructions See item description or contact seller for more information.</Description></Item><Item ItemID="5550"><Name>Kodak EktaPlus 7016 Toner / NEW / Free S&amp;H</Name><Category>Computers</Category><Category>Printers &amp; Supplies</Category><Category>Laser Printers</Category><Category>B&amp;W</Category><Category>Other</Category><Currently>$11.95</Currently><First_Bid>$11.95</First_Bid><Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids><Bids/><Location Latitude="43.286024" Longitude="-77.684264">Rochester, NY</Location><Country>USA</Country><Started>Dec-11-01 19:54:09</Started><Ends>Dec-21-01 19:54:09</Ends><Seller Rating="2097" UserID="mav01"/><Description>eBay Template __________ _______ ____ _ __ __ _____________ __ __ _ _________ __________ __ Kodak EktaPlus 7016 Toner / NEW / Free S&amp;H This auction is for Kodak Ektaplus 7016 Toner, new in the box._ There is free shipping and handling for this item within the continental United States._ "Sold as is". Thank You for Considering Maven Technologies! mem Shipping &amp; Handling There is free shipping and handling for this item within the continental United States._ Please contact us for other shipping destinations or additional shipping information. Most items are typically shipped within 48 business hours of settlement._ International shipments may require an additional 24 business hours to process. Payment We accept Visa, MasterCard, Discover, Money Orders and PayPal Warranty 30 Day Warranty, excluding items which are "sold as is"._ Defective items will be repaired or replaced at no charge. If we deem an item as unrepairable and/or replacement is not available, a refund will be issued._ If we determine that the malfunction was caused by hardware or software not provided by us, including software conflicts, repairs will be subject to our service fee._ There is a 20% restocking fee for all non-defective equipment returns. Rules and Limitations (DISCLAIMER) Winning bidders who decide to cancel their orders shall be charged all applicable eBay fees._ Defective parts/systems will be exchanged with the same parts/systems. Shipping is non-refundable. If any item becomes unexpectedly out of stock, we reserve the right to substitute an item of equal or greater value. Technical Support is responsible for handling all technically related problems and questions._ Normal business hours are Monday - Friday, 8:00am - 5:00pm._Residents of New York will incur Sales Tax. Items can be picked up at our retail store location with prior notification, a $10 handling fee will be assessed in addition the purchase price and applicable taxes. _ If this auction is not settled within 10 business days of auction close, the sale will be considered void and the high bidder will receive negative feedback.__ __ By bidding, you hereby agree to these conditions Please E-Mail any questions to Auction@maventech.com ________ _ Mavens other Auctions ___ __ This listing created by eBay Seller's Assistant Pro</Description></Item><Item ItemID="5558"><Name>Kyocera FS-1500A Laser Printer (40776)</Name><Category>Computers</Category><Category>Printers &amp; Supplies</Category><Category>Laser Printers</Category><Category>B&amp;W</Category><Category>Other</Category><Currently>$29.95</Currently><First_Bid>$29.95</First_Bid><Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids><Bids/><Location Latitude="40.017096" Longitude="-82.34322">Ohio</Location><Country>USA</Country><Started>Dec-12-01 05:49:05</Started><Ends>Dec-19-01 05:49:05</Ends><Seller Rating="5728" UserID="cpu77"/><Description>{ link=document.img.src link=link.substring(link.length,link.length-10) link='http://www.firebuy.com/pic1/'+link window.location.href=link } { if (num==1) { document.img.src=document.img1.src; } if (num==2) { document.img.src=document.img2.src; } if (num==3) { document.img.src=document.img3.src; } if (num==4) { document.img.src=document.img4.src; } } Kyocera FS-1500A Laser Printer Picture Navigator Item is Used/Unused Used Item is Sold As Is/Warranty Sold As Is Item was Tested/Untested Powers up More Detailed Information Available This is all the information we have Manufacturer Kyocera Model Number FS-1500A Kyocera FS-1500A Ecosys a-Si Laser Printer m/n: FS-1500A s/n: ABP3372581 features: Resolution: 300 X 300 dots-per-inch, 300 X 1200 with Kyocera Image Refinement Speed: 10 ppm it has no instruction manuals, power cords, or drivers powered-up but no further testing was done missing external paper trays the toner is not tested the inside of the unit needs to be cleaned Because the Item was not tested, it might be damaged and in need of repair! Payment Details See item description and Payment Instructions, or contact seller for more information. Payment Instructions See item description or contact seller for more information.</Description></Item><Item ItemID="5560"><Name>L@@K!CANON 460 Lazer Printer!!N/R</Name><Category>Computers</Category><Category>Printers &amp; Supplies</Category><Category>Laser Printers</Category><Category>B&amp;W</Category><Category>Other</Category><Currently>$41.0</Currently><First_Bid>$19.99</First_Bid><Number_of_Bids>6</Number_of_Bids><Bids><Bid><Bidder Rating="145" UserID="Antonios"><Location>Venezia</Location><Country>Italy</Country></Bidder><Time>Dec-12-01 20:10:03</Time><Amount>$23.49</Amount></Bid><Bid><Bidder Rating="1226" UserID="davem5"><Location>Venezia</Location><Country>Italy</Country></Bidder><Time>Dec-13-01 09:30:03</Time><Amount>$26.99</Amount></Bid><Bid><Bidder Rating="634" UserID="pillowtalklingerie"><Location>Venezia</Location><Country>Italy</Country></Bidder><Time>Dec-13-01 22:50:03</Time><Amount>$30.49</Amount></Bid><Bid><Bidder Rating="2635" UserID="gpbabe@aol.com"><Location>Venezia</Location><Country>Italy</Country></Bidder><Time>Dec-14-01 00:10:03</Time><Amount>$34.0</Amount></Bid><Bid><Bidder Rating="1286" UserID="$9.99warehouse"><Location>Venezia</Location><Country>Italy</Country></Bidder><Time>Dec-15-01 01:30:03</Time><Amount>$37.5</Amount></Bid><Bid><Bidder Rating="6" UserID="jw_sport"><Location>Venezia</Location><Country>Italy</Country></Bidder><Time>Dec-15-01 14:50:03</Time><Amount>$41.0</Amount></Bid></Bids><Location Latitude="39.853981" Longitude="-88.981511">Decatur</Location><Country>USA</Country><Started>Dec-12-01 06:50:03</Started><Ends>Dec-17-01 06:50:03</Ends><Seller Rating="8" UserID="showbiz7"/><Description>.titledata { font-family: verdana, sans-serif; font-size:18px; color:#FD3336; } .description { font-family: verdana, sans-serif; color:#000000; } .link { font-family: verdana, sans-serif; font-size:12px; underline; } HR { color: #000000; } L@@K!CANON 460 Lazer Printer!!N/R Click image to view larger version You are bidding on a Canon 460 Lazer Printer in excellent condition, it works and looks like new. The toner cartridge is near new. Printer comes with manual, driver installation disks, and parallel cable. Winning bidder is to pay $19 flat rate shipping to anywhere in the U.S. and can pay via PAYPAL, MO, or e-mail me direct with Visa, MC, AE, or Discover account information. Good Luck and Merry Christmas! Payment I accept the following forms of payment: Visa/Master Card, American Express, Discover, Money Order, COD. Additional Information Low cost image hosting and full service auction management solutions: AuctionWatch Payment Details See item description and Payment Instructions, or contact seller for more information. Payment Instructions See item description or contact seller for more information.</Description></Item><Item ItemID="5563"><Name>HP Laserjet 5L/6L Service Manual on CD!</Name><Category>Computers</Category><Category>Printers &amp; Supplies</Category><Category>Laser Printers</Category><Category>B&amp;W</Category><Category>HP</Category><Currently>$12.99</Currently><First_Bid>$12.99</First_Bid><Number_of_Bids>1</Number_of_Bids><Bids><Bid><Bidder Rating="227" UserID="starlitecollectibles"><Location>Venezia</Location><Country>Italy</Country></Bidder><Time>Dec-13-01 14:10:51</Time><Amount>$12.99</Amount></Bid></Bids><Location Latitude="33.786594" Longitude="-118.298662">Pasadena</Location><Country>USA</Country><Started>Dec-12-01 08:10:51</Started><Ends>Dec-17-01 08:10:51</Ends><Seller Rating="78" UserID="slimshady310"/><Description>This cd contains the complete HP Laserjet 5L/6L Service Manual. Includes photos and diagrams of complete disassembly of the printer. Full troubleshooting procedures. Complete list of all part #'s. Schematics of entire electrical subsystems. This manual is a must for all 5L/6L Laserjet owners/technicians. Shipping is $3.00 anywhere in the lower 48 states. Personal checks will delay shipping for up to 10 days.</Description></Item><Item ItemID="5571"><Name>256MB 256 MB sodimm Pc100 cl2 *NEW*</Name><Category>Computers</Category><Category>Laptops &amp; Accessories</Category><Category>Accessories</Category><Category>Memory Upgrades</Category><Currently>$20.0</Currently><First_Bid>$10.0</First_Bid><Number_of_Bids>3</Number_of_Bids><Bids><Bid><Bidder Rating="39" UserID="hlynn15"><Location>Venezia</Location><Country>Italy</Country></Bidder><Time>Dec-13-01 08:49:33</Time><Amount>$13.33</Amount></Bid><Bid><Bidder Rating="674" UserID="squig43"><Location>Venezia</Location><Country>Italy</Country></Bidder><Time>Dec-14-01 04:49:33</Time><Amount>$16.67</Amount></Bid><Bid><Bidder Rating="138" UserID="hylie"><Location>Venezia</Location><Country>Italy</Country></Bidder><Time>Dec-15-01 00:49:33</Time><Amount>$20.0</Amount></Bid></Bids><Location Latitude="40.679845" Longitude="-73.986415">New York, NY</Location><Country>USA</Country><Started>Dec-12-01 00:49:33</Started><Ends>Dec-17-01 00:49:33</Ends><Seller Rating="33" UserID="sega714"/><Description>I'm currently selling a new 256MB PC100 CL2 Sodimm from crucial.com. The chip number is CT32M64S4W8E.8T . I have purchased this ram, but is incompatible with my laptop (IBM Thinkpad T22), therefore have never been used. if you say how many hours out of the box, it's approximately 1 hour. Once again, if you own a IBM Thinkpad T22, I recommend you not to bid on this. Happy Bidding!!! Payment option Money Order or by Paypal Shipping and Handling: $6.00 in addition to winning bid.</Description></Item><Item ItemID="5587"><Name>NEW 256 MB IBM THINKPAD Laptop MEMORY $10OFF*</Name><Category>Computers</Category><Category>Laptops &amp; Accessories</Category><Category>Accessories</Category><Category>Memory Upgrades</Category><Currently>$24.99</Currently><First_Bid>$24.99</First_Bid><Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids><Bids/><Location Latitude="27.405429" Longitude="-82.543519">Tallhassee, FL</Location><Country>USA</Country><Started>Dec-12-01 18:30:01</Started><Ends>Dec-15-01 18:30:01</Ends><Seller Rating="30" UserID="charliefsu"/><Description>NEW 256MB IBM THINKPAD Laptop MEMORY $10 OFF! New 256MB IBM THINKPAD Laptop Memory(Made with BEST QUALITY-Samsung and Toshiba chips, FAST!)! Get $10 off see below Product Information PRODUCT SPECIFICATIONS These items are Brand New Lifetime Warranty Warranty Lifetime Condition NEW Total memory 256 MB PC-133/100 per module Chip type SDRAM / SODIMM Pins 144-pin Length 2 5/8 inch (standard length) Height 1.25 inch (low profile) Voltage 3.3v (standard voltage) Laptop Compatibility Guide ----------------------------------Models----------------------------------- MODULE Made with Toshiba or samsung chips with 6 Layer boards(BEST QUAILTY) Welcome you are bidding on a New PC100/133 256mb SO Dimm Laptop memory MADE BY TOSHIBA OR SAMSUNG!BEST in HIGH Quality. Newest On the market!Degined for newer LAPTOPS, THAT MEANS It is lightning fast and great for multi-tasking and internet surfing, the speed of your laptop will greatly increase if you upgrade using this Chip. 32x64 8 chips Module(32x8) pc133mhz or pc100mhz Please check with IBM IBM - ThinkPad 390E Celeron Series IBM - ThinkPad 390X Celeron 2626-9xx,Bxx,Fxx IBM - ThinkPad 390X Pentium III 2626-Lxx, Mxx IBM - ThinkPad 390X Celeron 2626-9xx,Bxx,Fxx IBM - ThinkPad 390X Pentium III 2626-Lxx, Mxx IBM - ThinkPad 570E Pentium III 2644-5xx, 6xx IBM - ThinkPad 600X (2645-3xx,4xx,7xx) IBM - ThinkPad 600X (2645-5xx,8xx,9xx) IBM - ThinkPad 770X 9549-7xU IBM - ThinkPad 770Z 9549-8xU IBM - ThinkPad A20 series IBM - ThinkPad A21 series IBM - ThinkPad A22 series IBM - ThinkPad 1200 i Series IBM - ThinkPad 1300 i Series IBM - ThinkPad 1400 Series IBM - ThinkPad i Series 1410 IBM - ThinkPad i Series 1411 IBM - ThinkPad i Series 1412 IBM - ThinkPad i Series 1420 IBM - ThinkPad i Series 1421 IBM - ThinkPad i Series 1422 IBM - ThinkPad i Series 1441 IBM - ThinkPad i Series 1442 IBM - ThinkPad i Series 1450 IBM - ThinkPad i Series 1451 IBM - ThinkPad i Series 1452 IBM - ThinkPad i Series 1460 IBM - ThinkPad i Series 1472 IBM - ThinkPad i Series 1480 IBM - ThinkPad i Series 1482 IBM - ThinkPad i Series 1483 IBM - ThinkPad i Series 1492 IBM - ThinkPad i Series 14E2 IBM - ThinkPad 1500 i Series IBM - ThinkPad i Series 1512 IBM - ThinkPad i Series 1540 IBM - ThinkPad i Series 1541 IBM - ThinkPad i Series 1542 IBM - ThinkPad i Series 1550 IBM - ThinkPad i Series 1552 IBM - ThinkPad i Series 1560 IBM - ThinkPad i Series 1562 IBM - ThinkPad i Series 1592 IBM - ThinkPad i Series 1720 IBM - ThinkPad i Series 1721 IBM - ThinkPad T20 Series IBM - ThinkPad T21 Series IBM - ThinkPad T22 Series IBM - ThinkPad T23 Series IBM - ThinkPad TransNote IBM - ThinkPad X20 IBM - ALL PENTIUM III Shipping and Handling Shipping and Handling is $10.00 per each auction. Memory will be shipped via United States Postal Service. I can ship to any of the 50 states and US possessions, AND I will ship to FPO/APO military bases. I will ship internationally.(e-mail request please) NO RESERVE Buyer to pay $9.99 for shipping and handling.(Act as Reserve) Insurance of $2.99 MUST also be Included Click here to view my other auctions. Created by eBay Seller's Assistant Pro</Description></Item><Item ItemID="5589"><Name>HP laserjet 4000 maintnance kit in the box</Name><Category>Computers</Category><Category>Printers &amp; Supplies</Category><Category>Laser Printers</Category><Category>B&amp;W</Category><Category>HP</Category><Currently>$51.0</Currently><Buy_Price>$315.82</Buy_Price><First_Bid>$0.1</First_Bid><Number_of_Bids>11</Number_of_Bids><Bids><Bid><Bidder Rating="627" UserID="doandcl@sympatico.ca"><Location>Venezia</Location><Country>Italy</Country></Bidder><Time>Dec-13-01 06:53:12</Time><Amount>$4.73</Amount></Bid><Bid><Bidder Rating="2522" UserID="www.commonscents.to"><Location>Venezia</Location><Country>Italy</Country></Bidder><Time>Dec-13-01 18:53:12</Time><Amount>$9.35</Amount></Bid><Bid><Bidder Rating="676" UserID="lanny7"><Location>Venezia</Location><Country>Italy</Country></Bidder><Time>Dec-14-01 06:53:12</Time><Amount>$13.98</Amount></Bid><Bid><Bidder Rating="1771" UserID="klskls"><Location>Venezia</Location><Country>Italy</Country></Bidder><Time>Dec-14-01 18:53:12</Time><Amount>$18.61</Amount></Bid><Bid><Bidder Rating="1085" UserID="cookscloset"><Location>Venezia</Location><Country>Italy</Country></Bidder><Time>Dec-15-01 06:53:12</Time><Amount>$23.24</Amount></Bid><Bid><Bidder Rating="86" UserID="cinegeek"><Location>Venezia</Location><Country>Italy</Country></Bidder><Time>Dec-15-01 18:53:12</Time><Amount>$27.86</Amount></Bid><Bid><Bidder Rating="544" UserID="styxscottii"><Location>Venezia</Location><Country>Italy</Country></Bidder><Time>Dec-16-01 06:53:12</Time><Amount>$32.49</Amount></Bid><Bid><Bidder Rating="1764" UserID="tamisuzn"><Location>Venezia</Location><Country>Italy</Country></Bidder><Time>Dec-16-01 18:53:12</Time><Amount>$37.12</Amount></Bid><Bid><Bidder Rating="240" UserID="tabbyannie"><Location>Venezia</Location><Country>Italy</Country></Bidder><Time>Dec-17-01 06:53:12</Time><Amount>$41.75</Amount></Bid><Bid><Bidder Rating="4787" UserID="carcon63"><Location>Venezia</Location><Country>Italy</Country></Bidder><Time>Dec-17-01 18:53:12</Time><Amount>$46.37</Amount></Bid><Bid><Bidder Rating="0" UserID="drtexas02"><Location>Venezia</Location><Country>Italy</Country></Bidder><Time>Dec-18-01 06:53:12</Time><Amount>$51.0</Amount></Bid></Bids><Location Latitude="42.338947" Longitude="-70.919635">Boston Area</Location><Country>USA</Country><Started>Dec-12-01 18:53:12</Started><Ends>Dec-19-01 18:53:12</Ends><Seller Rating="44" UserID="vikno2000"/><Description>This is a HP laserjet 4000 maintnance kit, includes fuser rollers Est..in the box. Regular price is $ 297. We are trying to minimize our Stock and we have more hardware for sale. We accept PAYPAL, Money orders and checks. Check out our rating, bid with comfidence. Please email with any questions. Hapy Bidding and good luck. Payment Details See item description and Payment Instructions, or contact seller for more information. Payment Instructions See item description or contact seller for more information.</Description></Item><Item ItemID="5599"><Name>HP LaserJet 4, Refurbed 30-Day Warranty</Name><Category>Computers</Category><Category>Printers &amp; Supplies</Category><Category>Laser Printers</Category><Category>B&amp;W</Category><Category>HP</Category><Currently>$150.0</Currently><First_Bid>$150.0</First_Bid><Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids><Bids/><Location Latitude="39.779492" Longitude="-86.132837">Indianapolis, IN</Location><Country>USA</Country><Started>Dec-13-01 09:20:23</Started><Ends>Dec-18-01 09:20:23</Ends><Seller Rating="381" UserID="computerpile.com"/><Description>.titledata { font-family: verdana, sans-serif; font-size:17px; color:#ffffff; font-weight : bold; } .description { font-family: verdana, sans-serif; color:#ffffff; } a.textLink { color: #FFCB00;} } HR { color: #ffffff; } HP LaserJet 4, Refurbed 30-Day Warranty Click image to view larger version Item is Used Intellifont and TrueType Resident Scalable Fonts, One Font Cartridge Slot, Fonts Per Page Limited Only by Memory. 2 MB RAM Standard, Upgradeable to 16 MB (four Universal SIMM slots). Enhanced PCL 5 Language plus HP-GL/2 for Plotter Output, Automatic Language Switching, Hot I/Os. LaserJet 4 8 Pages Per Minute (EX engine) Buyer pays fixed shipping - $40.00 PLEASE READ DESCRIPTION CAREFULLY If you do not agree to the terms of the auction, please do not bid. The Items we post are sold AS-IS. Most products are New or near Brand New Condition. If we know of any problems or damage it will be in the description text or viewable via pics. Items posted most likely work, but we cannot guarantee their functionality or operating condition since we cannot test items ourselves before they are sent to the winning bidder. SO PLEASE BID ACCORDINGLY. Pictures are of actual product. If we are selling multiples of the same item, we usually use the same pictures, but we take new pics if the item has been damaged or is different in any way from the others. We try to post as much info about the product that we can, but if you need technical info beyond what is in the listing, please try doing a search using the model and part information before emailing us with questions. Normally whatever we know about the item is already been put in the posting. FEEDBACK - - - We leave feedback according to how the entire transaction went...and we leave our feedback according to the feedback we receive from you, the customer. If you leave us Good feedback, we leave you Good feedback. If you leave us Neutral feedback, we leave you Neutral feedback. If you leave us Negative Feedback, expect to receive the same. Any questions that you can't find the info to, we will do our best to help. Good Luck to the Highest Bidder... And Have a great day... :) PCode:0920JD ICN#CP1967-01 Auction Terms and Conditions Bidder : All Items are USED, and sold AS-IS, unless otherwise stated. We ship only to the Contiguous United States. &amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbspComputerPile.Com takes all auctions very seriously.All failed transactions will result in negative feedback! Winner : Buyer agrees to pay all costs for Shipping and Handling (US Dollars). &amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbspWe charge a fixed shipping rate based upon the weight of the package. &amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbspWe ship everything via FedEx, they will NOT deliver to a PO Box. &amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbspAll auction winners will be billed automatically at the close of auction. Payment : PayPal, Check or Money Order only, sorry no COD'S. (Checks will require __time to clear before shipment is made.) Payment accepted via Paypal with Mastercard or Visa Warranty : All items are provided as-is. No warranty is expressed or implied unless otherwise stated. All items sold are as listed. Contact Information : If you have any questions about the Item up for auction, there are many research resources online ( http://www.google.com ). Item information questions to: Product Manager Shipping questions to: Shipping Manager Our Mailing Address is: &amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbspComputerPile.Com &amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp11058 Virgil St. &amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp&amp;nbspActon, IN 46259 Low cost image hosting and full service auction management solutions: AuctionWatch Payment Details See item description and Payment Instructions, or contact seller for more information. Payment Instructions See item description or contact seller for more information.</Description></Item><Item ItemID="5601"><Name>128MB DELL Laptop/Notebook Memory + GIFT</Name><Category>Computers</Category><Category>Laptops &amp; Accessories</Category><Category>Accessories</Category><Category>Memory Upgrades</Category><Currently>$16.5</Currently><First_Bid>$16.5</First_Bid><Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids><Bids/><Location>eUSweb.net</Location><Country>USA</Country><Started>Dec-13-01 11:05:52</Started><Ends>Dec-20-01 11:05:52</Ends><Seller Rating="45" UserID="anguyen724"/><Description>128MB DELL Laptop/Notebook Memory (NEW). BUY IT NOW GET Free PS/2 Mouse. (Value of $9.75) FREE GIFT DO NOT APPLY FOR AUCTION ITEM 128MB MEMORY COMPAQ,IBM, COMPAQ,APPLE,HITACH, FUSITSU,IBM,TOSHIBA,SONY,APPLE,HITACHI,HP,DELL ARE Available in MY STORE @$19.75 _ Genica 3 Button PS2 Mouse - Retail Boxed - 3 Button Mouse - Standard PS/2 Interface - Nicely retail boxed as 'Genica' - High resolution and excellent tracking - Fully compatible with all operating systems Retail Value: $9.75 Compatibility Guide ----------------------------------Models------------------------------- ---- Dell - Inspiron 3500 Dell - Inspiron 3500 D Dell - Inspiron 3500 K Dell - Inspiron 3700 Dell - Inspiron 3700 C Dell - Inspiron 3800 Dell - Inspiron 4000 Dell - Inspiron 5000 Dell - Inspiron 5000 E Dell - Inspiron 5000 C Dell - Inspiron 7000 Dell - Inspiron 7000 A Dell - Inspiron 7000 D Dell - Inspiron 7500 Dell - Inspiron 7500 C Dell - Inspiron 8000 Dell - Inspiron A433LT Dell - Inspiron C400GT Dell - Inspiron C433GT Dell - Inspiron R450GT Dell - Inspiron R500GT Dell - Inspiron R500VT Dell - Inspiron R500YT Dell - Latitude C500 Series Dell - Latitude C600 Series Dell - Latitude C800 Series Dell - Latitude CPi A300ST Dell - Latitude CPi A366ST Dell - Latitude CPi A366XT Dell - Latitude CPi A400XT Dell - Latitude CPi R400GT Dell - Latitude CPt C Series Dell - Latitude CPt S Series Dell - Latitude CPt V Series Dell - Latitude CPx H Series Dell - Latitude CPx J Series Dell - Latitude CS Series Dell - Latitude CSx Series Dell - Latitude LS 128MB MEMORY FOR LAPTOP/NOTEBOOK UPGRADE for Dell Laptop/Notebook High Quality Gold Contacts S0-Dimm 144 Pin Low Profile 3.3 Standard Volt _ Payment Visa &amp; MasterCard through PayPal Visa, MasterCard, Discover, &amp; Electronic Checks through BillPoint Money Order, Cashiers Check &amp; Personal/Business Check (held till cleared*) Item must be shipped to a confirmed address. *Checks/Money Orders: We will hold the check for up to 10 business days to allow for check to clear _ Shipping and Handling Usually we ship USPS mail (3-7 days) with delivery confirmation. For United States: Buyer agrees to pays $10.00 For International:_ Buyer agrees to pays $16.00 _ Returns Return the product to us within 14 days of the invoice date for a full refund._ You are responsible for shipping costs back to us._ After 14 days product covered under warranty only. _ Note This is bulk product , not retail pack. No pickup. Please do not bid If you don't except the above terms and conditions for shipping and handling. (do not email us after you have won the auction and ask us to reduce the price of the item.) Please provide these information when you make payment: Quantity and Auction Item Number. First and Last Name. Complete Shipping Address Email Address _ _ _ 2001 eUSweb.net. All rights reserved.</Description></Item><Item ItemID="5605"><Name>CHEAP IBM 16" COLOR MONITORS NO RESERVE</Name><Category>Computers</Category><Category>Monitors</Category><Category>16-inch or smaller</Category><Currently>$5.0</Currently><First_Bid>$5.0</First_Bid><Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids><Bids/><Location Latitude="41.951797" Longitude="-75.77536">Hallstead, PA</Location><Country>USA</Country><Started>Dec-13-01 11:44:40</Started><Ends>Dec-20-01 11:44:40</Ends><Seller Rating="258" UserID="new2ucomputers"/><Description>This is a great deal for anyone looking to get the bigger screen without the cost of the bigger price. MODEL 8514... DOA Warranty Bid with confidence. Buyer pays shipping/handling/insurance charge of $35.00 within the continental U.S. PA &amp; NY Residents pay applicable sales tax. Hours of operation for questions M-F 9:00-5:00 ET. Good Luck Bidding!!! We have large quantities of 8 Series Model#'s available if interested email me at pbonavita@matcogroup.com for any questions. Payment Details U.S. Shipping and Handling $35.00 Each additional item $35.00 Shipping Insurance per item - Sales Tax (6.000% if shipped to PA) _ Learn more about checkout Payment Instructions If you live in NY you must also pay applicable county tax. If paying by credit card you can either email me your information or give me a call at 800-711-6010 x231. If paying by Money Order/Cashier Check please send to: Envirocycle P.O. Box 899 Hallstead, PA 18822. Either way please email me your shipping address. Thanks</Description></Item><Item ItemID="5607"><Name>64MB PC100 SoDIMM Laptop Memory NR</Name><Category>Computers</Category><Category>Laptops &amp; Accessories</Category><Category>Accessories</Category><Category>Memory Upgrades</Category><Currently>$5.99</Currently><First_Bid>$5.99</First_Bid><Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids><Bids/><Location Latitude="36.186605" Longitude="-86.785248">Nashville, TN</Location><Country>USA</Country><Started>Dec-13-01 00:44:04</Started><Ends>Dec-16-01 00:44:04</Ends><Seller Rating="51" UserID="brian.hiss@vanderbilt.edu"/><Description>This is a used in MINT Condition 64 MB SODIMM PC100 SDRAM.. The specs are below, and shipping will be $3.95 flat USPS 2-3 Day Priority Mail. Accept Billpoint, and Paypal only for faster shipment. Email brian.hiss@vanderbilt.edu with any questions. 64 MB 100 MHz Non-Parity (NP) SDRAM Small Outline DIMM (SoDIMM) upgrade and increase system productivity and speed. SDRAM memory perform faster than either traditional fast page mode (FPM) or Extended Data Out (EDO) memory modes of operation. SDRAM SoDIMM features access times that are synchronous to the system bus clock. Pin 144 Type SDRAM Contacts Gold Volts 3.3 Standard V Size 64 MB Bus PC100 _ _ _ _ _ _ _ _ Payment Details U.S. Shipping and Handling $3.95 Each additional item $0.00 Shipping Insurance per item - Sales Tax (none) _ Learn more about checkout Payment Instructions Please Pay ASAP via Paypal or Billpoint</Description></Item><Item ItemID="5608"><Name>128MB PC100 4 MOST NOTEBOOKS/LAPTOPS @ $14.99</Name><Category>Computers</Category><Category>Laptops &amp; Accessories</Category><Category>Accessories</Category><Category>Memory Upgrades</Category><Currently>$14.99</Currently><First_Bid>$14.99</First_Bid><Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids><Bids/><Location>Fast shipping!</Location><Country>USA</Country><Started>Dec-13-01 13:30:04</Started><Ends>Dec-16-01 13:30:04</Ends><Seller Rating="3039" UserID="egiant1"/><Description>128MB 128MB pc100 sodimm memory for notebook/laptop Picture may not reflected from the actual item Product Specs/Compatibility Your are bidding on a brand new 128MB PC-100 144pin SODIMM Notebook memory. We only use high quality RAM made by U.S major memory module manufacture like, IBM, NEC, Samsung, and etc. 128MB 144pin SODIMM 16M x 64 SDRAM DIMM PC100 Mhz 8ns CAS2 3.3 Volt Compatible with almost all laptop computers, including Acer, Apple, Compaq, Dell, Fujitsu, Gateway, HP, IBM, Sony, Panasonic, and Toshiba ; There is too many model this RAM will work in for us to write it all down. Please consult your owner's manual for storage capacity of your laptop. 100% compatible with all notebook that support 128MB RAM Package Includes One 128MB PC100 SODIMM Memory Warranty All item come with 30 day replacement warranty We guarantee each item to be free of defects but we are not responsible for any incompatibility problems All RMA returns shipping must be prepaid by the buyer, insured and bearing a Return Material Authorization (RMA) number on the shipping label A 20% stocking fees will applied on all return item that is not defected. Shipping and Handling fees are non-refundable All sales are final. Shipping &amp; Handling United States of America: $10 For first item, $5 for each additional item. Canada: $18 For first item, $5 for each additional item. All Other International Countries: $25 For first item, $5 for each additional item. All item is shipped by USPS (United States Postal Services). Shipping and Handling price is not negotiable. We use the handling charge to cover our shipping department cost, packaging materials, fuel charges, boxes, and labels. Please do not bid if you don't agree with our shipping and handling prices. Do not email us after the auction to reduce the shipping price. No local pick up. No third party shipping carrier will be used. We only ship via USPS. Payment Information Paypal Bidpay Money Order, and Cashier's Check Credit card can be used through our website Winners Please wait for our payment instruction through email. Payment instruction is usually send within 24 hours of end of auction. Do not email us for payment instruction unless you have not receive one from us for past 24 hours. Include your Auction Item #, eBay User ID, and Shipping Address along with your payment. Payment must be received within 10 days of the close of the auction. All CA resident must add 8% sales tax before shipping General Info Your bid is a contract - Place a bid only if you're serious about buying the item. If you are the winning bidder, you will enter into a legally binding contract to purchase the item from us. All NPB (Non Paying Bidder) will be report to eBay and we will leave you a negative feedback. All order is usually shipped with in 24 - 48 hours upon receipt of payment. Please include your Auction Item #, and your eBay User ID with all of your email inquires. If you receive a defected item, email us for RMA instruction. We will leave you a feedback within 1 week of close of auction. Low cost image hosting and full service auction management solutions: AuctionWatch Visit eGiant today! Payment Details See item description and Payment Instructions, or contact seller for more information. Payment Instructions See item description or contact seller for more information.</Description></Item><Item ItemID="5609"><Name>HP 4MV LASEJET PRINTER WITH LOWER PAPER TRAY</Name><Category>Computers</Category><Category>Printers &amp; Supplies</Category><Category>Laser Printers</Category><Category>B&amp;W</Category><Category>HP</Category><Currently>$185.0</Currently><First_Bid>$185.0</First_Bid><Number_of_Bids>1</Number_of_Bids><Bids><Bid><Bidder Rating="905" UserID="pegjoyner@aol.com"><Location>Venezia</Location><Country>Italy</Country></Bidder><Time>Dec-15-01 04:17:20</Time><Amount>$185.0</Amount></Bid></Bids><Location Latitude="36.47266" Longitude="-79.90522">NC</Location><Country>USA</Country><Started>Dec-13-01 13:43:07</Started><Ends>Dec-20-01 13:43:07</Ends><Seller Rating="121" UserID="rtickle69"/><Description>if (navigator.appName == 'Microsoft Internet Explorer') { if (navigator.appVersion.substring(0,1) "); } else { document.write(" "); document.write(" "); document.write(" BODY { background: url(http://home.mebtel.net/~rtickle69/Clouds.gif) }"); document.write(" "); document.write(" "); } } else { //Default to Netscape settings. document.write(" "); } HP 4MV LASEJET PRINTER WITH LOWER PAPER TRAY HP 4MV Laserjet printer. Printer has been cleaned and tested. 28 Mb memory expandable to 52 Mb. Has enhanced PCL 5 standard. Adobe PostScript Level 2 is included. Printer shipped with standard letter size tray and optional 500 sheet lower paper tray. It adjusts to: letter, legal, 11" x 17", A4, A3, or B4 Sizes. NO JETDIRECT CARD ! Prints 16 pages per minute, 600X600 DPI. Comes with power cord, test pages and a used toner. Condition of toner cartridge unknown so "Cartridge is as is." I accept PayPal, money orders and checks. Buyer to pay shipping/packaging and insurance if desired. Please allow time for personal check to clear or send m.o. for quick shipping. Ship USA only. All items won in the auction must be paid for within 7 days of auction end. Failure to pay for your item will result in negative feedback. This listing created by eBay Seller's Assistant Basic. Free Honesty Counters powered by Andale! Payment Details See item description and Payment Instructions, or contact seller for more information. Payment Instructions See item description or contact seller for more information.</Description></Item><Item ItemID="5610"><Name>HP LaserJet II Laser Printer NR</Name><Category>Computers</Category><Category>Printers &amp; Supplies</Category><Category>Laser Printers</Category><Category>B&amp;W</Category><Category>HP</Category><Currently>$20.0</Currently><First_Bid>$20.0</First_Bid><Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids><Bids/><Location Latitude="34.733898" Longitude="-86.645592">Huntsville, AL</Location><Country>USA</Country><Started>Dec-13-01 13:45:47</Started><Ends>Dec-20-01 13:45:47</Ends><Seller Rating="26" UserID="ferreed"/><Description>READ THIS INFORMATION BEFORE BIDDING HP LaserJet II Printer This auction is for a Hewlett Packard LaserJet II Laser Printer. This printer powers up, runs through its diagnostics, and says that it is ready to print, but I haven't been able to test printing with it because I don't have the drivers for it. The printer is in good condition cosmetically and includes a removable paper tray. There is some sticky residue left from when labels were removed from the casing, and there are a few labels still left on it, but the casing has no cracks or signs of damage. I have another one of these printers in identical condition, so if the winning bidder wants to buy two of them, I'll list the second one in a Buy It Now auction for the same amount as the winning bid. Good luck, and thanks for looking! READ THIS INFORMATION BEFORE BIDDING Terms and Conditions: I will email the winning bidder shortly after close-of-auction (typically less than 24 hours.) The winning bidder should reply with their full address and phone number (you don't have to give me this, but if you don't I'll put my number on your shipping label.) I ship FedEx Ground for most items and can provide you with a shipping quote if you email me your zip code. Please request your quote before the day your auction ends. I charge exact shipping charges and exact packaging charges-- I will also quote these to you. If we receive payment by Saturday at noon, your package will go out to FedEx on the weekend and ship out on Monday morning. If we receive your payment by Tuesday at noon, your package will go out Wednesday night and ship Thursday morning. We stick to this schedule because we both work regular jobs and have to maintain some kind of normalcy in our schedules. Please inspect your package as soon as it arrives and keep ALL packaging. If the shipper causes damage in transit, you will have to present your packaging as proof when you make your claim. I do not give refunds or exchanges on things damaged in shipping-- you'll have to file a claim with the shipper. I will provide whatever supporting information I can in order to help. I guarantee that things are as-advertised, so if there is an issue, please email me and I'll do my best to fix the problem. Please contact me first if you feel that my service is so poor that I deserve negative or neutral feedback. Sometimes email fails and I'll miss a message, but I always strive to make my customers happy. Let me know if there are problems and I'll try to fix them. One last thing-- do NOT ask me to ship things that aren't media by the USPS media rate. I won't lie and break a federal law to save you ten bucks. I'm here to run a clean business and enjoy the eBay community. Let's keep it friendly and professional. Hourly Statistics by Ruby Lane Payment Details See item description and Payment Instructions, or contact seller for more information. Payment Instructions See item description or contact seller for more information.</Description></Item><Item ItemID="5613"><Name>Hewlett-Packard 5Si MX Laser Printer</Name><Category>Computers</Category><Category>Printers &amp; Supplies</Category><Category>Laser Printers</Category><Category>B&amp;W</Category><Category>Other</Category><Currently>$19.99</Currently><First_Bid>$19.99</First_Bid><Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids><Bids/><Location Latitude="38.6531" Longitude="-90.243462">St. Louis, Missouri</Location><Country>USA</Country><Started>Dec-13-01 15:55:02</Started><Ends>Dec-18-01 15:55:02</Ends><Seller Rating="269" UserID="pcdiscounter"/><Description>if( navigator.appName == 'Microsoft Internet Explorer') { if( navigator.appVersion.substring(0,1) "); } else { document.write(" "); document.write(" "); document.write(" BODY { background: url(http://www.pcpusher.com/Users/Jploof/whitemar.jpg) }"); document.write(" "); document.write(" "); } } else { // use netscape style background statement document.write(" "); } HP LaserJet 5Si MX Ref 66850107 Hewlett-Packard 5Si MX Laser Printer _ Reference 66850107 This unit is just back from corporate lease. Unit powers up OK and appears to be in Good Condition. This unit reports a paper jam even when there is no paper in the printer. -- This printer has 12MB RAM. Page Count = 5,271. Duplexing unit IS INCLUDED. Postscript chip IS INCLUDED. This printer has Parallel Interface ONLY. JetDirect card IS NOT INCLUDED. Condition of consumables is UNKNOWN and NOT WARRENTED. Manuals, cables, drivers and software IS NOT INCLUDED. Quantities are available. Bidders should bid on this item as a unit for parts or for repair only. No warranty , expressed or implied, is available for this printer. -- Winning bidder to pay fixed shipping &amp; handling charges of $120.00 for shipping via common carrier freight company to continental US locations. _ E-Poster Template Check out our company here. Doing business since 1984. Use only my company's verified account. bc@epctech.com Check my other auctions for more computer equipment. __ _ Auction Information Will only ship to continental US, Alaska, Hawaii and Canada. Winning bidder pays fixed shipping and handling costs as indicated in the ad above. Shipping is based on UPS Ground. Canada, Alaska &amp; Hawaii shipments will incur additional shipping charges. Preferred payment methods are most major credit cards or PayPal. Other payment options are money order, cashier's check, corporate or personal check. Items are held for 14 days or until personal or company check clears bank, as applicable. Missouri residents and local pickups are required to pay an additional 6.575% sales tax. Payment must be made within 7 days after the end of auction. Absolutely No CODs. Absolutely No PO Boxes. All sales final. 30 Day Warranty against Dead On Arrival (D.O.A.) only. Please email any questions before bidding to jploof@epctech.com _ Good Luck and Let the bidding begin! - Preferred method of payment &amp; Items will be shipped within 72 hrs! By placing your bid you agree: _ To confirm receipt of my e-mail within three days . After auction closes, provide shipping address (No P.O. Box or APO)._ To make payment no later than seven days after close date of auction._ If payment is not received in ten days, transaction will be considered NULL AND VOID and the item will be RELISTED and NEGATIVE FEEDBACK will be left. If an unexpected problem should come up,_ please notify me within ten days. Thank you for your cooperation. _ _ View and search all the items in my picture gallery My Service Box Money Orders :_ _ Bidder Tools :_ _ By Auctiva Auctiva PowerTools . Create, Schedule, Manage your auctions Free Trial! Payment Details See item description and Payment Instructions, or contact seller for more information. Payment Instructions See item description or contact seller for more information.</Description></Item><Item ItemID="5621"><Name>Toshiba Laptop 128 MB RAM Memory Upgrade</Name><Category>Computers</Category><Category>Laptops &amp; Accessories</Category><Category>Accessories</Category><Category>Memory Upgrades</Category><Currently>$19.99</Currently><Buy_Price>$89.97</Buy_Price><First_Bid>$19.99</First_Bid><Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids><Bids/><Location Latitude="38.8951" Longitude="77.0367">DC Metro</Location><Country>USA</Country><Started>Dec-13-01 18:13:35</Started><Ends>Dec-16-01 18:13:35</Ends><Seller Rating="81" UserID="laptopbroker"/><Description>Toshiba Laptop 128MB RAM Manufactured Specifically for your Toshiba Laptop Product Specifications: - - Brand New - - 128 MB RAM - - PC 100 - - Gold Contacts - - 144 Pin (Standard) - - Low Profile - - 3.3 volt - - SO DIMM - - Lifetime Warranty - - Customer Service and Installation assistance included. - - Anti-Static Packaging Additional Product Information: - - Made for use in the folllowing models: - Toshiba - Portege 7000CT/CT-NT - Toshiba - Portege 7010CT/CT-NT - Toshiba - Portege 7020CT/CT-NT - Toshiba - Portege 7200CT/CTe/7220CTe - Toshiba - Portege 7140CT/CT-NT - Toshiba - Satellite 1555CDS/2100CDS/CDT/2105CDS - Toshiba - Satellite 2210XCDS/CDT - Toshiba - Satellite 1605CDS/1625CDT/2140XCDS/2180CDT - Toshiba - Satellite 1675CDT/1695CDT/2250XCDS - Toshiba - Satellite 2060CDS/2065DVD - Toshiba - Satellite 2550CDT/2590CDS/CDT/XDVD - Toshiba - Satellite 2595/2655/2615 - Toshiba - Satellite 2650/2675/2714 - Toshiba - Satellite 2650/2670/2710/2715 - Toshiba - Satellite 2775/2755 - Toshiba - Satellite 4000/4010/4020 - Toshiba - Satellite Pro 4260/4270/4280/4320/4300 - Toshiba - Tecra 8000 PII300/333/366/400 - Toshiba - Tecra 8000 PIII500/6000/650/700 Terms&amp;Conditions We want your eBay experience to be as enjoyable as possible. PLEASE do not bid if you are not 100% sure that you want this item and you are sure you are willing to pay your maximum bid price. We will contact the winning bidder via e-mail within 2 Business days after the auction has ended. Winning bidders must confirm their order within 3 business days after notification. Additional instructions for completion of sale will be included in the e-mail notification. Payment must be received within 7 business days after order is confirmed, or the winning bid will automatically be voided. Exceptions to this rule will be made on an individual basis. Please contact us within 3 days if you need special arrangements. We make every attempt to represent our products honestly, on occasion; we have found that packages have different specifications than the actual product. When bidding please keep in mind that there can be minor differences from specifications advertised and what is actually present (this is rare, but does happen). Most orders shipped within 2 Business days of receipt of verifiable payment. Since all sales are in auction format, all auction sales are final. No refunds are available, we can only issue an exchange for the following reasons: o Incorrect Quantity or Incorrect Item Shipped o Freight Damage (Recipient must make claim with shipment carrier first.) o Defective items must be returned to the manufacturer for service We cannot issue an exchange product for any other reason than stated above. We will not be held liable for any incident or any accident or consequential damages related to the use or misuse of this item under any circumstances. No suitability of use is expressed or implied in this sale. Shipping fees and return fees are non-refundable! Shipping and Freight: - - Freight, Insurance and handling within the US is $9.99 per module. - - International bids accepted please email us for freight rate Payment Options: Pay me securely with your Visa or MasterCard through PayPal! function dw(nu){document.write(s1+"ppsl"+nu+".gif"+s2+sA[nu]);}f1="document.links";s1="\ ","\"Pay me securely with your Visa or MasterCard through PayPal!\"\","\"Winning bidder, click here to pay instantly by credit card!\"\");c1=c2=c3=c4=0;for(i=0;i =0){c1++;}else if((eval(f1+"["+i+"].search")).indexOf("BetterSeller")=0){c2++;}else if((eval(f1+"["+i+"].search")).indexOf("ListItemForSaleShow")=0){c3++;}else if((eval(f1+"["+i+"].hash")).indexOf("ListItemForSaleAutosShow")=0){c4++;}}if((c1=2)||(c20)||(c30)||(c40)){dw(3);}else{dw(2);}f11="xclick-auction";f13="item=";f14="";for(i=0;i 0){s11=document.links[i].search;j=s11.indexOf(f13);if(j0){s11=s11.slice((j+(f13.length)));for(k=0;k =0){document.links[i].href=((document.links[i].href)+"&amp;jitem_id="+f14+"&amp;jmagic=1");}} BidPay.com - the online money order auction payment service. www.BidPay.com Wire Transfers, Money Orders and Cashiers Checks Accepted. Additional Questions: Please do not hesitate to contact us with your questions Sales@laptopbroker.com http://www.laptopbroker.com " style="text-decoration:none" id=blinklink Please Check Our Other Auctions Payment Details See item description and Payment Instructions, or contact seller for more information. Payment Instructions See item description or contact seller for more information.</Description></Item><Item ItemID="5628"><Name>Toner Ctg IBM / Lexmark 4039 4039+ 3912 3916</Name><Category>Computers</Category><Category>Printers &amp; Supplies</Category><Category>Laser Printers</Category><Category>B&amp;W</Category><Category>Lexmark</Category><Currently>$59.99</Currently><Buy_Price>$339.73</Buy_Price><First_Bid>$59.99</First_Bid><Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids><Bids/><Location Latitude="37.495812" Longitude="-88.16099">cchicago, il</Location><Country>USA</Country><Started>Dec-13-01 19:04:34</Started><Ends>Dec-18-01 19:04:34</Ends><Seller Rating="52" UserID="dmdbase"/><Description>This is a IBM type toner cartridge (in sealed box, not the one in the picture) for IBM/Lexmark 4039, 4039+, 3912, 3916, generic type (reconditioned) Part number 1380950. Satisfaction guaranteed! Please feel free to email me for any questions. S/H 10.75$. Item will be shipped immediately after receiving payment. Accept Paypal, Billpoint or personal check. Happy Bidding and thanks for looking! 417104039LF Free Honesty Counters powered by Andale! Payment Details U.S. Shipping and Handling $10.75 Shipping Insurance per item - Sales Tax (8.250% if shipped to IL) _ Learn more about checkout Payment Instructions See item description or contact seller for more information.</Description></Item><Item ItemID="5632"><Name>XEROX DOCUPRINT N3225 TABLOID NETWORK LASER</Name><Category>Computers</Category><Category>Printers &amp; Supplies</Category><Category>Laser Printers</Category><Category>B&amp;W</Category><Category>Other</Category><Currently>$1099.0</Currently><First_Bid>$1099.0</First_Bid><Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids><Bids/><Location Latitude="45.308105" Longitude="-122.77266">Wilsonville, OR</Location><Country>USA</Country><Started>Dec-13-01 19:58:50</Started><Ends>Dec-16-01 19:58:50</Ends><Seller Rating="204" UserID="xerox-tektronix"/><Description>WILL SHIP TO THE US ONLY ACCEPT ONLY VISA, MASTER CARD, AMERICAN EXPRESS DIRECT FROM THE MANUFACTURER ESTIMATED RETAIL PRICE - $3,299.00 This Manufacturer renewed Xerox N3225 Monochrome Laser Printer will keep the pace at an amazing speed of 32 pages-per-minute. It has been thoroughly tested by the Manufacturer to ensure it meets performance standards. In addition, it comes with a 30-day warranty that covers repair or replacement of the product at the Manufacturer's discretion. Ground freight is only $9.95 (for purchases under $2,000.00) and $19.95 (for bids between $2,000.00 and $4,999.99). It is being sold as a Standard configuration and comes with built in 10/100BaseT Ethernet network connection, USB connection, and parallel port. This printer comes complete with all necessary accessories (excluding printer cable) including user manual, software, power cord, etc. It also ships with a NEW 23,000 page print cartridge! This printer ships in original factory packaging to ensure delivery in great condition! Winning bid does not include any applicable State and Local sales taxes. Visit our web site to see our FAQ page and all the printers we have available Free Honesty Counters powered by Andale!</Description></Item><Item ItemID="5646"><Name>HP Laserjet II III upper Fan</Name><Category>Computers</Category><Category>Printers &amp; Supplies</Category><Category>Laser Printers</Category><Category>B&amp;W</Category><Category>HP</Category><Currently>$5.0</Currently><First_Bid>$5.0</First_Bid><Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids><Bids/><Location>Silicon Vallley</Location><Country>USA</Country><Started>Dec-14-01 00:23:07</Started><Ends>Dec-21-01 00:23:07</Ends><Seller Rating="238" UserID="macpowerg3"/><Description>HP Laserjet II III upper Fan This is a pulled upper fan for LaserJet II/IID/III/IIID or Apple Laserwriter Series II. It is in good working condition. Payment &amp; Shipping Information Buyer prepays and pays for shipping and insurance. Insurance is optional however, we will not be responsible for uninsured items which are lost or damaged. When possible, multiple items will be packaged together to reduce shipping charges. We will NOT ship to PO Boxes. California residents will need to add 8.0% sales tax.Payment must be received within 14 days of the auction's ending date. Payment by Visa, MasterCard or PayPal is preferred but US postal money orders are also accepted. We usually contact winning bidders within 24 hours of the auction's end- however our offices are closed on weekends so allow extra time if your auction closes Friday-Sunday. Please confirm receipt of the winning bidder notification within 72 hours. If you have any questions, please contact us BEFORE bidding. I accept payment through X.com's PayPal! I'm VERIFIED so Buyer Protection is guaranteed. Listing created with eLister 1.1b4 for Macintosh from Black Magik Software. Free Honesty Counters powered by Andale! Payment Details See item description and Payment Instructions, or contact seller for more information. Payment Instructions See item description or contact seller for more information.</Description></Item><Item ItemID="5647"><Name>FIX HP LaserJet 5L/6L/3100/3150 Laser Printer</Name><Category>Computers</Category><Category>Printers &amp; Supplies</Category><Category>Laser Printers</Category><Category>B&amp;W</Category><Category>HP</Category><Currently>$5.75</Currently><First_Bid>$5.75</First_Bid><Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids><Bids/><Location Latitude="40.679845" Longitude="-73.986415">New York City</Location><Country>USA</Country><Started>Dec-14-01 00:42:52</Started><Ends>Dec-19-01 00:42:52</Ends><Seller Rating="1163" UserID="janjiang"/><Description>If your HP 5L/6L/3100/3150 laser printer is picking up multiple pages or misfeed. You need to install the HP "Customer Replaceable Seperation Pad" kit and your printer will be as good as new. This kit is brand NEW from HP in a factory sealed box. It requires NO disassembly and takes less than 3 minutes to install for everyone. Easy to follow instructions are included. Buyer pays for the S/H. All major credit card accepted. I prefer PayPal or Billpoint. Check &amp; Money order is acceptable. Check my feedback and bid with confident. []</Description></Item><Item ItemID="5650"><Name>HP Laserjet 4 Plus Printer 21ram network</Name><Category>Computers</Category><Category>Printers &amp; Supplies</Category><Category>Laser Printers</Category><Category>B&amp;W</Category><Category>HP</Category><Currently>$50.0</Currently><First_Bid>$50.0</First_Bid><Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids><Bids/><Location Latitude="39.991729" Longitude="-83.082262">COLUMBUS,OH</Location><Country>USA</Country><Started>Dec-14-01 13:36:25</Started><Ends>Dec-19-01 13:36:25</Ends><Seller Rating="728" UserID="aebady@columbus.rr.com"/><Description>This auction is for a very clean HP 4 plus laserjet printer with a 10base-t interface card J2550, 21 MB RAM and 129,000 pages printed, equivalente to 6 months of use. 250 sheet letter tray, power cord and a good used CARTRIDGE. One week warranty to fully test the unit. Features HP LaserJet 4 Plus: Model:C2037A; Printer Speed:12 pages ppm; Resolution:300/600 dpi; Expandable I/O Buffer; Resource Savings; Languages:Enhanced PCL 5; Printer Maximum Memory Capacity:66 Mb; Output Capacity:250 sheets; Maximum Monthly Duty Cycle:20,000 pages; We accept payment via Paypal or money orders. Buyer will pay for UPS shipping plus $6 for packing. RESERVE $190.00 Free Honesty Counters powered by Andale! Payment Details See item description and Payment Instructions, or contact seller for more information. Payment Instructions See item description or contact seller for more information.</Description></Item><Item ItemID="5653"><Name>New Microsoft SideWinder Pro GamePad USB</Name><Category>Computers</Category><Category>Input Peripherals</Category><Category>Gaming Controls</Category><Currently>$22.99</Currently><First_Bid>$22.99</First_Bid><Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids><Bids/><Location Latitude="34.087108" Longitude="-117.96966">Baldwin Park, California</Location><Country>USA</Country><Started>Dec-14-01 14:18:31</Started><Ends>Dec-21-01 14:18:31</Ends><Seller Rating="2975" UserID="onlyusb"/><Description>***Brand New*** MICROSOFT Sidewinder GamePad Pro USB _ Benefits Digital and proportional control Features both digital control for instantaneous response and proportional control for smooth, joystick style movements. 16 Programmable functions Features the highest level of progammability ever offered in a SideWinder game pad. Plug-and-play Uses USB technology for plug-and-play functionality. Game schemes Includes SideWinder Game Controller Software with 45 pre-defined schemes for popular games. Standard Features Greater control The most feature-rich game pad that delivers the greatest level of control and customization. The SideWinder Game Pad Pro has 6 action buttons, two triggers, a shift button, and an 8-way d-pad. Dual precision D-pad Creates greater control in game play by allowing the D-pad to deliver proportional and digital control from the same D-pad. Lastest in Microsoft ergonomic design SideWinder Game Pad Pro brings a new ergonomic design for premium comfort for longer game play and a fresh new color. Added sophistication of the SideWinder Game Controller software Create profiles for your favorite games by assigning game actions or keystroke commands to the SideWinder Gamepad buttons. Program buttons and triggers to enhance gameplay. USB compatible only Takes advantage of the latest operating system functionality for easy installation and set up. Requirements Computer/Processor Pentium 166 or higher microprocessor Memory 16 MB of RAM Hard Disk 10 MB of hard disk space Drive Quad-speed CD-ROM drive Display Super VGA, 256-color monitor Operating System Windows 98 or later operating system Peripherals SoundBlaster-compatible audio card; Enclosed Driver; USB compatible only; Microsoft Mouse or compatible pointing device. Miscellaneous Microsoft Internet Explorer 3.0a or later, Netscape Navigator 3.0 or later, or other frames-compatible browser for use of on-line tutorial This auction is brought to you by OnlyUSB Please visit our other eBay auctions. If you have any questions or concerns, please e-mail us at info@onlyusb.com or call 626-336-1178 for more information. Terms and Conditions PAYMENT We accept PayPal ( our ID is: info@onlyusb.com ), BillPoint , Visa , MasterCard , Money Orders and Checks . For checks and money orders, please include your auction number and make them payable to: OnlyUSB . Send checks and money orders to the address in the Contact Us section below. For personal checks, please allow 5-10 business for funds to clear. ***CALIFORNIA RESIDENTS, PLEASE ADD 8% FOR CA SALES TAX TO THE FINAL AUCTION PRICE*** WARRANTY 1 YEAR WARRANTY: We warranty this products to be free from defects in material and workmanship for one year from the date of the original purchase. If any defects in material and workmanship appear during the warranty period, please send us an email at info@onlyUSB.com or call 626-336-1178 for an repair authorization number. Damaged products will be replaced or repaired at our option. This waranty DOES NOT COVER NORMAL WEAR AND TEAR, IMPROPER HANDLING OR ACCIDENTAL DAMAGES. There are no refunds unless the product is defective. SHIPPING &amp; HANDLING All bidders who reside in the 48 continental United States are to add $8.00 to the final bid price for shipping, handling, and insurance via UPS Ground. To combine shipping for multiple items, please add $4.00 for each additional item after the first. For Hawaii, Alaska and Canada, please add an additional $8.00 to the shipping and handling fee. We ship to the United States only, NO EXCEPTIONS. No customer pick ups are allowed. All orders must be arranged by freight carrier. CONTACT US OnlyUSB 450 Cloverleaf Dr. Baldwin Park, CA 91706 TEL: 626-336-1178 E-Mail: info@onlyUSB.com Business Hrs: M-F 9am~6pm PST There is always someone here during our normal business hours if you have any questions or concerns. Please mention the auction number for all questions that you have! Please read all the above information before you place a bid! Thank you and happy biddings!!! Visit www.OnlyUSB.com today! Payment Details See item description and Payment Instructions, or contact seller for more information. Payment Instructions See item description or contact seller for more information.</Description></Item><Item ItemID="5657"><Name>Hewlett Packard Laserjet 5L Laser Printer</Name><Category>Computers</Category><Category>Printers &amp; Supplies</Category><Category>Laser Printers</Category><Category>B&amp;W</Category><Category>HP</Category><Currently>$49.99</Currently><First_Bid>$49.99</First_Bid><Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids><Bids/><Location Latitude="29.694629" Longitude="-91.259347">Morgan City, LA</Location><Country>USA</Country><Started>Dec-14-01 15:16:04</Started><Ends>Dec-21-01 15:16:04</Ends><Seller Rating="155" UserID="ebay@creativesystem.com"/><Description>Please visit my Website before bidding. By Bidding on this auction you have read and understand the rules in order to bid. Unit is a Hewlett Packard Laserjet 5L Laser Printer with toner. Unit works, prints well. Unit sales as is and sales are final. Paypal or Money Order preferred payment options. Buyer pays Actual Shipping Costs plus a $5.00 Handling Fee. Free Honesty Counters powered by Andale! Payment Details See item description and Payment Instructions, or contact seller for more information. Payment Instructions See item description or contact seller for more information.</Description></Item><Item ItemID="5659"><Name>Avatar Shark*PCMCIA Cable Upgrade*NEW*</Name><Category>Computers</Category><Category>Laptops &amp; Accessories</Category><Category>Accessories</Category><Category>PCMCIA Cards</Category><Currently>$2.49</Currently><First_Bid>$2.49</First_Bid><Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids><Bids/><Location Latitude="33.640302" Longitude="-117.769442">Anaheim, CA</Location><Country>USA</Country><Started>Dec-14-01 16:37:18</Started><Ends>Dec-19-01 16:37:18</Ends><Seller Rating="7748" UserID="connectcomp.com"/><Description>ConnectComp AVATAR Shark 250 Mobile Hard Drive *PC Card Cable Upgrade Faster Transfer * "Better Than Zip" Brand New OEM Packaging Laptop PCMCIA (PC Card) Interface Direct Replacement For Original Equipment Parallel Interface Cable Increases Transfer Rate From 1MB Per Second To 2MB Per Second Hot Pluggable, Connect &amp; Disconnect Without Restarting Your Laptop Includes Instructions Software Not Included, Original Drivers Only Supported Windows 95, Download Latest Drivers From Link Provided CLICK HERE For Latest Drivers 30 Day Warranty. This auction only includes what is pictured unless stated otherwise. Add $7.50 for packaging, shipping and handling. Shipping cost is fixed. Please bid accordingly. No discounts will be given. Multiple auctions will not be shipped together. Shipping via UPS ground. Sorry NO pickups. Shipping to Alaska, Hawaii, Guam, Puerto Rico, U.S. Virgin Islands and Canada may be considerably more. Most items shipped 1 to 3 business days after receiving payment. Payment by Cashier's check, Money Order, or PayPals. 7.5% Sales tax applies to California residents. 20% restocking fee on all returned items (no exceptions). Shipping cost is not refundable. Thanks for bidding! Check All Our ConnectComp Auctions Visit Connectcomp.com today! Payment Details See item description and Payment Instructions, or contact seller for more information. Payment Instructions See item description or contact seller for more information.</Description></Item><Item ItemID="5661"><Name>Powerbook 1400 ZIP Drive Module (VST)</Name><Category>Computers</Category><Category>Apple, Macintosh</Category><Category>Drives-Internal</Category><Currently>$52.0</Currently><First_Bid>$52.0</First_Bid><Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids><Bids/><Location Latitude="40.679845" Longitude="-73.986415">New York, NY</Location><Country>USA</Country><Started>Dec-14-01 17:36:56</Started><Ends>Dec-19-01 17:36:56</Ends><Seller Rating="0" UserID="gman5555"/><Description>VST Zip Drive 100 for Powerbook 1400 (right bay) low reserve! This is a tough to find item. The drive is in good working condition and is guaranteed not DOA. The drive uses standard Iomega drivers (included with MacOS) thus software/drivers are NOT provided with purchase. The drive has been fully tested with various Zip media, and is sold as is. 1 Zip Disk will be included. Features: - 100MB Zip storage - Self Powered - Faster than the external Zip drive. - Fast enough for Multimedia - Locking head technology - Hot swappable (when no disk in drive) The VST Zip100 for the PowerBook 1400 brings affordable, reliable, and mass storage to the Apple Powerbook 1400. PLEASE Serious bidders ONLY!!. FREE priority shipping is included in cont/USA I WILL ACCEPT PAYPAL AND EBAY PAYMENT ONLY!!</Description></Item><Item ItemID="5662"><Name>Brand New HP Microfine Toner Cartridge 92298X</Name><Category>Computers</Category><Category>Printers &amp; Supplies</Category><Category>Laser Printers</Category><Category>B&amp;W</Category><Category>HP</Category><Currently>$69.95</Currently><First_Bid>$69.95</First_Bid><Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids><Bids/><Location>Park Ridge</Location><Country>USA</Country><Started>Dec-14-01 17:36:27</Started><Ends>Dec-17-01 17:36:27</Ends><Seller Rating="1744" UserID="asenashop"/><Description>Brand New HP Microfine Toner Cartridge 92298X HP Microfine Toner Cartridge - 92298X Product Information Compatible with HP LaserJet 4, 4M, 4 Plus, 4M Plus, 5, 5M, and 5N printers OVERVIEW For clear, sharp printouts, nothing outperforms genuine HP LaserJet toner cartridges. No matter what your printing needs, HP LaserJet toner cartridges are engineered to deliver high-impact results every time. All toner cartridges for newer HP LaserJet printers produce even finer lines, sharper edges, and darker black coverage with HP s microfine toner formula. Microfine toner assures you of the blackest blacks and the cleanest possible lines. Every HP toner cartridge is warranted to be free from defects in materials and workmanship during its useful lifetime. For the crisp, sharp results you ve come to expect from your HP LaserJet printer, choose genuine HP toner cartridges. SPECIFICATIONS Capacity Toner capacity: 8800 Coverage: 5 Compatibility Printer compatibility: HP LaserJet 4, 4M, 4 Plus, 4M Plus, 5, 5M, and 5N printers Engine Consumables Type of Consumable: Toner Back to Menu Back to Menu There is no return on any opened box item. No Cancellations accepted if won; Ask all your questions before you bid. Back to Menu In US (except AK,HI,PR,APO,FPO) $ 10.00 AK,HI,PR,APO,FPO $ 15.00 Canada $ 20.00 Europe $ 50.00 Other $ 60.00 All international bidders please confirm your address before you bid. ( auctions@asenaworld.com ) All packages are insured. Shipping method is UPS Ground unless otherwise stated. We are not responsible for custom charges of international shippings. There is no combo shipping. Back to Menu We accept money orders and cashier checks We prefer PayPal, the #1 payment service in online auctions! Back to Menu Brand New Unopened Retail Box. We assume no responsibility for sealed items. All registration papers comes with the item. Warranty goes to manufacturer. Back to Menu Asena Corporation 808 West Higgins Road Park Ridge, IL, 60068 United States Email: auctions@asenaworld.com Phone: +1 847 692 2292 Fax: +1 847 692 2955 Back to Menu NO RESERVE Buyer to pay $10.00 for shipping and handling. Please click here to see my other auctions. Created by eBay Seller's Assistant Pro Payment Details See item description and Payment Instructions, or contact seller for more information. Payment Instructions See item description or contact seller for more information.</Description></Item><Item ItemID="5663"><Name>128MB Toshiba Laptop Notebook Memory NEW</Name><Category>Computers</Category><Category>Laptops &amp; Accessories</Category><Category>Accessories</Category><Category>Memory Upgrades</Category><Currently>$0.01</Currently><First_Bid>$0.01</First_Bid><Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids><Bids/><Location>memorymodules</Location><Country>USA</Country><Started>Dec-14-01 17:45:31</Started><Ends>Dec-17-01 17:45:31</Ends><Seller Rating="1362" UserID="memorymodules"/><Description>128MB Toshiba Laptop Notebook Memory NEW 128MB TOSHIBA Laptop Memory Satellite - Tecra - Portege Product Information PRODUCT SPECIFICATIONS These items are Brand New Lifetime Warranty Warranty Lifetime Condition NEW Total memory 128 MB PC-100 per module Chip type SDRAM / SODIMM Pins 144-pin Length 2 5/8 inch (standard length) Height 1.25 inch (low profile) Voltage 3.3v (standard voltage) Laptop Compatibility Guide ----------------------------------Models----------------------------------- Toshiba - Portege 7000CT Toshiba - Portege 7000CT-NT Toshiba - Portege 7010CT Toshiba - Portege 7010CT-NT Toshiba - Portege 7020CT Toshiba - Portege 7020CT-NT Toshiba - Portege 7140 CT Toshiba - Portege 7140 CT-NT Toshiba - Portege 7200CT Toshiba - Satellite 1555CDS Toshiba - Satellite 1605CDS Toshiba - Satellite 1620CDS Toshiba - Satellite 1625CDT Toshiba - Satellite 1670CDS Toshiba - Satellite 1675CDS Toshiba - Satellite 1690CDT Toshiba - Satellite 1695CDT Toshiba - Satellite 1700-200 Series Toshiba - Satellite 1700-300 Series Toshiba - Satellite 1710CDS Toshiba - Satellite 1715XCDS Toshiba - Satellite 1730CDT Toshiba - Satellite 1735 Toshiba - Satellite 1755 Toshiba - Satellite 2060CDS Toshiba - Satellite 2065CDS Toshiba - Satellite 2100CDS Toshiba - Satellite 2100CDT Toshiba - Satellite 2105CDS Toshiba - Satellite 2140XCDS Toshiba - Satellite 2180CDT Toshiba - Satellite 2210XCDS/CDT Toshiba - Satellite 2550CDT Toshiba - Satellite 2590CDS Toshiba - Satellite 2590CDT/XDVD Toshiba - Satellite 2595CDS Toshiba - Satellite 2595CDT Toshiba - Satellite 2595XDVD Toshiba - Satellite 2615 DVD Toshiba - Satellite 2650XDVD Toshiba - Satellite 2655XDVD Toshiba - Satellite 2670DVD Toshiba - Satellite 2675DVD Toshiba - Satellite 2710XDVD Toshiba - Satellite 2715XDVD Toshiba - Satellite 2755DVD Toshiba - Satellite 2775XDVD Toshiba - Satellite 2800 Series Toshiba - Satellite 2805 Series Toshiba - Satellite 4000CDS Toshiba - Satellite 4000CDT Toshiba - Satellite 4005CDS Toshiba - Satellite 4005CDT Toshiba - Satellite 4010CDS/CDT Toshiba - Satellite 4015CDS/CDT Toshiba - Satellite 4020CDT Toshiba - Satellite 4025CDT Toshiba - Satellite 4030CDS Toshiba - Satellite 4030CDT Toshiba - Satellite 4030CDT-NT Toshiba - Satellite 4060CDT Toshiba - Satellite 4060CDT-NT Toshiba - Satellite 4060XCDT Toshiba - Satellite 4070CDS Toshiba - Satellite 4070CDT Toshiba - Satellite 4080XCDT Toshiba - Satellite 4080XCDT-NT Toshiba - Satellite 4090CDS Toshiba - Satellite 4090XDVD-NT Toshiba - Satellite 4090XDVD/XCDT Toshiba - Satellite 4100XCDT Toshiba - Satellite 4100XCDT NT Toshiba - Satellite 4100XDVD Toshiba - Satellite 4100XDVD-NT Toshiba - Satellite Pro 4260DVD Toshiba - Satellite Pro 4270XDVD Toshiba - Satellite Pro 4280XDVD Toshiba - Satellite Pro 4280ZDVD Toshiba - Satellite Pro 4300 Series Toshiba - Satellite Pro 4320CD/DVD Toshiba - Tecra 8000 (All Models) Toshiba - Tecra 8100 (All models) Toshiba - Tecra 8200 (All models) Shipping and Handling Shipping and Handling is $10.00 per each auction. Memory will be shipped via United States Postal Service. I can ship to any of the 50 states and US possessions, but I will NOT ship to FPO/APO military bases. I will not ship internationally. Shipping and Handling Shipping and Handling is $10.00 per each auction. Memory will be shipped via United States Postal Service. I can ship to any of the 50 states and US possessions, but I will NOT ship to FPO/APO military bases. I will not ship internationally. Payment Terms I accept VISA and MasterCard via PayPal (your shipping address must be confirmed). I will send you a PayPal money request after the auction ends. I also accept Money Orders. I will not accept Personal Checks. Payment is expected within 10 days after the auction. Payment Details See item description and Payment Instructions, or contact seller for more information. Payment Instructions See item description or contact seller for more information.</Description></Item><Item ItemID="5670"><Name>CANON N650U FLATBED SCANNER</Name><Category>Computers</Category><Category>Scanners</Category><Category>USB</Category><Currently>$49.95</Currently><First_Bid>$49.95</First_Bid><Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids><Bids/><Location Latitude="42.406357" Longitude="-96.37617">Sioux CIty, ia</Location><Country>USA</Country><Started>Dec-14-01 20:05:35</Started><Ends>Dec-17-01 20:05:35</Ends><Seller Rating="831" UserID="jimhug"/><Description>CANON N650U USB FLATBED SCANNER 600 x 1200 dpi, 42-Bit w/Z-Lid Great Scanning at a Great Price: The groundbreaking CanoScan N650U USB Flatbed Scanner launches a new era in scanning performance, innovation and value-giving you the power to do so much more, for so much less. Small Wonder: At just over one inch high, the N650U scanner is one of the thinnest flatbed scanners in the world. It's also one of the easiest to set up and use. Connect with just a single USB cable to any compatible Mac_ or PC-no power cord or bulky transformers are necessary. Just plug it in to your computer and scan photos, graphics, copy and more at a remarkable 600 x 1200 dpi for crisp, clear images. Plus, 42-bit resolution gives you over four trillion possible colors for richer, more robust scans. It even has an external programmable button for fast, one-touch scanning. Scanning bulky items is easier then ever: Canon's exclusive Z-Lid Expansion Top will change the way you scan bulky items, such as books and magazines. Many other scanner covers lift only at an angle and become uneven and awkward when scanning anything that isn't completely flat. The N650U scanner includes a special expansion hinge that lifts up to one inch vertically allowing the lid to lie flat, creating the space needed for bulky items. Features: Exclusive Z-Lid_ Expansion Top 600 x 1200 dpi resolution One cable for USB and power 42-bit for over 4 trillion possible colors Ultra-slim-just over 1 inch high Software: ScanGear CS-U TWAIN driver, ScanGear Toolbox CS, Canon Plug-in Module CS-U, CanoScan Toolbox CS, ArcSoft_ PhotoStudio_ 2000, ArcSoft PhotoBase_ and ScanSoft_ OmniPage_ OCR Manufacturer Part Number F91-4631-US1 Warranty: This is a factory refurbished item and comes with a 90 day warranty through Canon Shipping: There is a $10.00 shipping and handling charge for all shipments within the continental US. If you need this item shipped to Canada, Alaska, Hawaii, APO, FPO or other US territories, email me for any additional charge. Payment: I accept cashier's checks, money orders or credit cards at Billpoint or Paypal. Note: Returns for DOA only. Buyer is responsible for return shipping. Any refunds do not include shipping. Click below to... send me email: jimhug@cableone.net .This ad created using *FREE* ad creation software from www.etusa.com</Description></Item><Item ItemID="5671"><Name>Enhance The IBM 32MB 70ns 5.0V IC DRAM Kit</Name><Category>Computers</Category><Category>Laptops &amp; Accessories</Category><Category>Accessories</Category><Category>Memory Upgrades</Category><Currently>$7.95</Currently><First_Bid>$7.95</First_Bid><Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids><Bids/><Location Latitude="40.298988" Longitude="-76.847194">Harrisburg, PA</Location><Country>USA</Country><Started>Dec-14-01 20:06:58</Started><Ends>Dec-21-01 20:06:58</Ends><Seller Rating="2898" UserID="pcsurplusonline.com"/><Description>Enhance The IBM 32MB 70ns 5.0V IC DRAM Kit Enhance your system with the IBM 32MB, 8Mx36, 5.0V IC DRAM card! This robust Memory card will boost up your system IMMEDIATELY! Don't waste your time and this once in a life-time opportunity, UPGRADE now. Click To Enlarge Each Picture Dealer Closeout - No Returns Part #: 92G7235 Condition: All RAM are working System Pulls . Payment / Shipping &amp; Handling &amp;#160 Cashiers Check, Money Order or PayPal &amp;#160 Continental U.S. : &amp;#160 $6 (PA Residents Please Add 6% Sales Tax) &amp;#160 Alaska + Hawaii : &amp;#160 $10 Cashiers Check, Money Order and PayPal Only &amp;#160 Canada : &amp;#160 $20 We will only accept International PayPal &amp;#160 International : Call 1-717-233-6650 or email: intl@pcpartsinc.com for rates. _ All payments must be prepaid (refer to chart for payment options) - NO CODs. _The above Shipping, Handling and Processing charges enable us to ensure that your purchase is delivered safely and in a timely manner. The costs incurred cover shipping, handling, tracking, and insurance. Shipping : PCSurplusOnline has partnered with FedEx as our preferred carrier for added reliability and convenience. Handling and Processing : These services include receiving, storing, transferring and preparing the product for shipment, and credit card processing. Most products are shipped directly from PCSurplusOnline_s state-of-the-art warehouse. Packages are carefully processed from the moment the product is removed from inventory to the point at which they are transferred to the carrier. Tracking: All products shipped by PCSurplusOnline are traceable Insurance : Deliveries are insured and guaranteed against loss, theft and damage _ We WILL NOT ship to P.O. Boxes! _ International customers, please email us for special instructions PRIOR to bidding. _ We usually ship out the item(s) 2 to 3 business days after receipt of payment (Please allow extra 5 days for computers, printers, and monitors for proper testing and cleaning). Terms &amp; Conditions Warranty: _ All RAM are working System Pulls &amp;#160&amp;#149 Sold As Is &amp;#160&amp;#149 NO REFUNDS! Bid with confidence from an Ebay Powerseller! General: _ All eBay bids and sales are final. _ Payment must be received within 10 days of the close of the auction. _ Call us at 1-800-666-9373 with any questions regarding the auction. _ A bid on our auction states that you have read and agreed to all Terms and Conditions . Please, do not bid if you do not intend to complete your winning bid. We will leave negative feedback for all deadbeat bidders and report you to eBay. What To Do When The Auction Closes: Our sales department will contact you after auction close via email. We will typically email your payment instructions within 48 hours of the auction ending. If you do not receive the email, please feel free to call us at 1-800-666-9373 for payment instructions. Once you receive the e-mail, please follow the instructions enclosed. Payment: We accept Money Orders, Cashier Checks, Major Credit Cards, and PayPal (NO CODs) : PayPal customers: When paying by PayPal, please use our ID paypal@pcpartsinc.com. We're sorry, but we do not accept payments over $50 that are not verified and/or do not have a confirmed address . Should you choose to use a credit card, you will be given the location of our secure server to complete your order online. Credit card orders will be processed immediately. Therefore, if you are anxious to receive your merchandise, this is your best option. If you choose to send a money order, please fill out and send along a copy of the email. Please be patient and wait for your product to be shipped. Once your payment has been received, we will ship within 1-2 business days (please allow an extra 5 days for computers, printers, &amp; monitors for proper testing and cleaning) However, if a money order is submitted for payment, please allow an extra 5-7 working days for processing. Making you a satisfied customer is our #1 goal. Please feel free to e-mail us with any questions. Our friendly sales team will be more than happy to assist you. Thank you for your business and HAPPY BIDDING! Free Honesty Counters powered by Andale! Payment Details See item description and Payment Instructions, or contact seller for more information. Payment Instructions See item description or contact seller for more information.</Description></Item><Item ItemID="5675"><Name>NEW SONY/TOSHIBA 128MB PC100 FREE SHIPPING!!</Name><Category>Computers</Category><Category>Laptops &amp; Accessories</Category><Category>Accessories</Category><Category>Memory Upgrades</Category><Currently>$1.0</Currently><First_Bid>$1.0</First_Bid><Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids><Bids/><Location Latitude="33.276539" Longitude="-112.18717">Phoenix, AZ</Location><Country>USA</Country><Started>Dec-14-01 20:40:31</Started><Ends>Dec-17-01 20:40:31</Ends><Seller Rating="495" UserID="blackdiamondcomputer"/><Description>NEW SONY/TOSHIBA 128MB PC100 FREE SHIPPING!! BLACK DIAMOND COMPUTER PRODUCTS BRAND NEW 128MB PC100/66 SODIMM FREE SHIPPING WITHIN THE CONTINENTAL U.S.!! GUARANTEED NO DOAS!! COMPATIBLE WITH 99.99% OF EXISTING LAPTOP COMPUTERS. STARTING BID FOR THIS ITEM IS JUST $1.00 !! MEMORY SPECS ARE AS FOLLOWS: 128MB PC100 and PC66 COMPATIBLE 144 PIN SODIMM 16X64 CONFIGURATION 8 CHIP DESIGN 3.3 VOLT CAS 2 7ns EACH MODULE TESTED PRIOR TO SHIPMENT - GOLD LEADS MIGHT SHOW SLIGHT WEAR FROM THE TEST PROCEDURES LIFETIME REPLACEMENT WARRANTY SELLER PAYS SHIPPING CHARGES AFTER MODULE FAILURE WITHIN FIRST YEAR OF PURCHASE BUYER PAYS SHIPPING FOR MODULE FAILURE AFTER FIRST YEAR OF PURCHASE PRODUCT SHIPPED WITHIN 48 HOURS AFTER RECEIVING PAYMENT OR IT'S YOURS FOR FREE!! (EXCEPT SHIPMENT FALLING ON SUNDAYS AND HOLIDAYS. THESE WILL BE SHIPPED THE FOLLOWING BUSINESS DAY.) BUY YOUR MEMORY TODAY WHILE THE PRICES ARE STILL LOW!! GOOD LUCK FROM BLACK DIAMOND COMPUTER PRODUCTS SHIPPING AND HANDLING Within Continental U.S. Outside the Continental U.s. FREE!! $7.50 First Module FREE!! - Each Additional Module $5.50 Each Additional Module Add $1.10 Per $50 for Insurance (Optional) Add $2.50 Per $50 for Insurance (Optional) Memory Modules are shipped in anti-static bags and Bubble Mailers for protection. All shipments mailed using USPS First Class. Modules Tested on Various Sony and Toshiba Notebooks. Arizona Residents Please add 8% Sales Tax. RETURNS AND REFUNDS Modules Found To Be Incompatible will be Replaced or 100% of the Auction Price will be Refunded. Defective Modules Will Be Replaced With Like Kind, Not Necessarily The Exact Brand. We Will Test All Returned Modules Suspected Of Being Defective, Any Module Found Defective Due To Mishandling Or Incorrect Installation Will Void The Warranty. SHIPPING INFORMATION All Orders Are Shipped Within 48 Hours Of Receiving Payment Or The Module Is Yours For Free (This Excludes Shipments Falling On Sundays And Holidays, These Will Be Shipped On The Following Business Day.) WE ARE A PAYPAL VERIFIED SELLER!! TO VIEW MY OTHER AUCTIONS CLICK HERE! SEND INQUIRIES TO BLACK DIAMOND COMPUTER PRODUCTS NO RESERVE Insurance of $1.10 should also be included if desired. Click here to view my other auctions. Created by eBay Seller's Assistant Pro</Description></Item><Item ItemID="5683"><Name>18.3GB Internal Hard Drive+ HardDrive Toolkit</Name><Category>Computers</Category><Category>Apple, Macintosh</Category><Category>Drives-Internal</Category><Currently>$127.5</Currently><First_Bid>$100.0</First_Bid><Number_of_Bids>4</Number_of_Bids><Bids><Bid><Bidder Rating="1294" UserID="promonut62@aol.com"><Location>Venezia</Location><Country>Italy</Country></Bidder><Time>Dec-16-01 04:11:41</Time><Amount>$106.88</Amount></Bid><Bid><Bidder Rating="135" UserID="nanni46"><Location>Venezia</Location><Country>Italy</Country></Bidder><Time>Dec-16-01 19:29:44</Time><Amount>$113.75</Amount></Bid><Bid><Bidder Rating="326" UserID="jmullenger"><Location>Venezia</Location><Country>Italy</Country></Bidder><Time>Dec-17-01 10:47:47</Time><Amount>$120.62</Amount></Bid><Bid><Bidder Rating="631" UserID="sweetmagic2000"><Location>Venezia</Location><Country>Italy</Country></Bidder><Time>Dec-18-01 02:05:51</Time><Amount>$127.5</Amount></Bid></Bids><Location Latitude="33.276539" Longitude="-112.18717">Phoenix, AZ</Location><Country>USA</Country><Started>Dec-15-01 00:53:38</Started><Ends>Dec-20-01 00:53:38</Ends><Seller Rating="4" UserID="txjade"/><Description>Western Digital 18.3GB 10K RPM Ultra SE SCSI Interal Hard Drive. WD Vantage. (Western Digital Model #WD183FN-00ASA0) Currently formatted with Macintosh System 9. Used in PM8500 for about 1 year. No apparent bad blocks. Purchase price INCLUDES Hard Disk Toolkit for Mac (which has a current new list price of $129 by itself!). This software allows you to format, partition, etc. 3rd-party Western Digital drive for your Mac. I believe the disk also works for PC. Satisfaction guarantee. Return for full refund if not compatible. Buyer pays shipping costs - you choose shipping method and insurance coverage. Payments made by EBay payments will allow me to ship ASAP. Other modes of payments may delay shipping until after the new year. Free Honesty Counters powered by Andale! Payment Details See item description and Payment Instructions, or contact seller for more information. Payment Instructions Buyer pays shipping costs - you choose shipping method and insurance coverage. Payments made by EBay payments will allow me to ship ASAP. Other modes of payments may delay shipping until after the new year.</Description></Item><Item ItemID="5684"><Name>128MB PC100 4-MOST NOTEBOOKS/LAPTOPS NEW HOT!</Name><Category>Computers</Category><Category>Laptops &amp; Accessories</Category><Category>Accessories</Category><Category>Memory Upgrades</Category><Currently>$17.99</Currently><First_Bid>$17.99</First_Bid><Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids><Bids/><Location>PC Micro Store</Location><Country>USA</Country><Started>Dec-15-01 14:15:11</Started><Ends>Dec-18-01 14:15:11</Ends><Seller Rating="2815" UserID="www.pcmicrostore.com"/><Description>128MB 128MB PC100 SODIMM NOTEBOOKS MEMORY Picture may not reflected from the actual item Product Description This is the 128MB 100MHz SODIMM Industry Standard DIMM module from PC Micro Store. This specific model is a 128MB, 144-Pin, 100MHz Synchronous, 16x64, 3.3Volt Non-Buffered SDRAM DIMM module with Gold Contact Leads. Product Specs/Compatibility Module Size: 128MB Package: 144-pin DIMM Feature: SODIMM, PC100 Configuration: 16Meg x 64 DIMM Type: Unbuffered Error Checking: Non-Parity Speed: 8ns Voltage: 3.3V Contact: Gold Industry Standard Memory modules work with most new Notebooks/Laptops including: -----------------------------Models------------------------------ Acer - AOpen AX6B Acer - AOpen A63 Acer - Aspire 2190 Acer - Aspire 6331 Acer - Aspire 7110 Acer - Aspire Power SE Acer - Power 2100 Acer - Power 3200 Acer - Power 4100 Acer - Power 6100 Acer - Power 8000 Acer - PorStation 2500 Acer - PorStation 7000 -----------------------------Models------------------------------ IBM - Aptiva 2153 Model E2U IBM - Aptiva 2139 Model E5D IBM - Aptiva 2163 IBM - Aptiva 2174 IBM - Aptiva 240 IBM - Aptiva 270 IBM - Aptiva 520 IBM - Aptiva 570 IBM - Aptiva 631 IBM - Network station 2800 IBM - Network station 2200 IBM - P300 GL IBM - P300 PL -----------------------------Models------------------------------ Gateway - G6-450 Gateway - G6-400 Gateway - Performace 450 Gateway - Destination XTV Gateway - E-1400 Gateway - E-3200 Gateway - E-4200 Gateway - E-5200 Gateway - Essential 400 Gateway - Essential 500 Gateway - Performace 850xl Gateway - Selet 600/700/800 -----------------------------Models------------------------------ Dimension L series Dimension V333 Dimension V450 Dimension XPS T Series OptiPlex GX100 OptiPlex GX110 OptiPlex NX1 Precision 610 -----------------------------Models------------------------------ Compaq - Presario 5304 Compaq - Presario 5070 Compaq - Presario 5360 Compaq - Deskpro 6450 Compaq - Deskpro 6500 Compaq - Deskpro 6600 Compaq - Deskpro EP 6400 Compaq - Deskpro EP Celeron Compaq - Deskpro EP P550 Compaq - Prosignia Desktop 320 Compaq - Prosignia Desktop 330 Compaq - Prosignia Desktop 340 -----------------------------Models------------------------------ Hewlett-Packard - Brio 8511 Hewlett-Packard - Brio BA Hewlett-Packard - Brio BAx Hewlett-Packard - Net PC20 Hewlett-Packard - Pavilio 4530 Hewlett-Packard - Pavilio 4535 Hewlett-Packard - Pavilio 8550C Hewlett-Packard - Vectra VE Series i7/i8 Hewlett-Packard - Vectra VL Series 8 Hewlett-Packard - Visualize P-Class Hewlett-Packard - Visualize X-Class Hewlett-Packard - Kayak XU PC Workstation -----------------------------Models------------------------------ Toshiba - Equium 100 Toshiba - Equium 7100 Desktop Toshiba - Equium 7100 Minitower Toshiba - Equium 7100 Slimline Toshiba - Equium 7300 Toshiba - Equium 7350 Toshiba - M500 Toshiba - M500D Toshiba - Value-Priced 3100 Toshiba - Value-Priced 3200 -----------------------------Models------------------------------ Apple - Power Mac G3 PC100 Apple - Power Mac G4 PCI Apple - Power Mac G4 AGP Apple - iMac 350 Apple - iMac 400 DV Apple - iMac 400 Special Edition Apple - Apple - Apple - Apple - -----------------------------Models------------------------------ Sony - VAIO PCG 748 Sony - VAIO PCG 808 Sony - VAIO PCG 812 Sony - VAIO PCG 818 Sony - VAIO PCG 838 Sony - VAIO PCG F150 Sony - VAIO PCG F160 Sony - VAIO PCG F180 Sony - VAIO PCG F190 Sony - VAIO PCG F250 Sony - VAIO PCG F270 Sony - VAIO PCG F280 Sony - VAIO PCG F290 Sony - VAIO PCG F304 Sony - VAIO PCG F305 Sony - VAIO PCG F309 Sony - VAIO PCG F340 Sony - VAIO PCG F350 Sony - VAIO PCG F360 Sony - VAIO PCG F370 Sony - VAIO PCG F390 Sony - VAIO PCG F400 Sony - VAIO PCG F403 Sony - VAIO PCG F409 Sony - VAIO PCG F420 Sony - VAIO PCG F430 Sony - VAIO PCG F450 Sony - VAIO PCG F480 Sony - VAIO PCG F480K Sony - VAIO PCG F490 Sony - VAIO PCG F490K Sony - VAIO PCG-F520 Sony - VAIO PCG-F540 Sony - VAIO PCG-F540K Sony - VAIO PCG-F560 Sony - VAIO PCG-F560K Sony - VAIO PCG-F580 Sony - VAIO PCG-F580K Sony - VAIO PCG-F590 Sony - VAIO PCG-F590K Sony - VAIO PCG-F610 Sony - VAIO PCG-F630 Sony - VAIO PCG-F650 Sony - VAIO PCG-F650K Sony - VAIO PCG-F680 Sony - VAIO PCG-F680K Sony - VAIO PCG-F690 Sony - VAIO PCG-F690K Sony - VAIO PCG-F701 Sony - VAIO PCG-F707 Sony - VAIO PCG-F709 Sony - VAIO PCG-F709K Sony - VAIO PCG-F801 Sony - VAIO PCG-F807k Sony - VAIO PCG-F808k Sony - VAIO PCG-F809k Sony - VAIO PCG-FX101 Sony - VAIO PCG-FX120 Sony - VAIO PCG-FX120K Sony - VAIO PCG-FX140 Sony - VAIO PCG-FX140K Sony - VAIO PCG-FX150 Sony - VAIO PCG-FX150K Sony - VAIO PCG-FX170 Sony - VAIO PCG-FX170K Sony - VAIO PCG-FX190 Sony - VAIO PCG-FX190K Sony - VAIO PCG-FX210 Sony - VAIO PCG-FX270 Sony - VAIO PCG R505TE Sony - VAIO PCG R505TEK Sony - VAIO PCG R505TS Sony - VAIO PCG R505TSK Sony - VAIO PCG Z505(all models) Sony - VAIO PCG Z505HE Sony - VAIO PCG Z505HS Sony - VAIO PCG Z505HSK Sony - VAIO PCG Z505J Sony - VAIO PCG Z505JE Sony - VAIO PCG Z505JEK Sony - VAIO PCG Z505JS Sony - VAIO PCG Z505JSK Sony - VAIO PCG Z505JX Sony - VAIO PCG Z505LE Sony - VAIO PCG Z505LEK Sony - VAIO PCG Z505LS Sony - VAIO PCG Z505LSK Sony - VAIO PCG Z505R Sony - VAIO PCG Z505RE Sony - VAIO PCG Z505RX Sony - VAIO PCG Z505S Sony - VAIO PCG Z505SX Sony - VAIO PCG Z600HEK Sony - VAIO PCG Z600LEK Sony - VAIO PCG Z600NE Sony - VAIO PCG Z600NEK Sony - VAIO PCG Z600RE Sony - VAIO PCG Z600REK Sony - VAIO PCG Z600TEK Sony - VAIO PCG X29 Sony - VAIO PCG XG18 Sony - VAIO PCG XG19 Sony - VAIO PCG XG28 Sony - VAIO PCG XG28K Sony - VAIO PCG XG29 Sony - VAIO PCG XG29K Sony - VAIO PCG XG38 Sony - VAIO PCG XG38K Sony - VAIO PCG XG39 Sony - VAIO PCG XG39K Sony - VAIO PCG XG9 Sony - VAIO PCG XG500 Sony - VAIO PCG XG500K Sony - VAIO PCG XG700 Sony - VAIO PCG XG700K However, they may or may not work in some proprietary models from Compaq, IBM, or Dell. Consult your system manual of manufacturer's web site to ensure compatibility before purchasing. It may also work on other motherboards also. Please check your manual to ensure compatibility. Please check your Notebook/Laptop specification for memory type before you purchase it. It is not our responsibility for any incompatibilities of the systems and memory. Package Includes 128MB PC100 SODIMM Memory Warranty All item come with 30 day replacement warranty We guarantee each item to be free of defects but we are not responsible for any incompatibility problems All RMA returns shipping must be prepaid by the buyer, insured and bearing a Return Material Authorization (RMA) number on the shipping label A 20% stocking fees will applied on all return item that is not defected. Shipping and Handling fees are non-refundable All sales are final. Shipping &amp; Handling United States of America: $10 For first item, $5 for each additional item. Canada: $18 For first item, $5 for each additional item. All Other International Countries: $25 For first item, $5 for each additional item. All item is shipped by USPS (United States Postal Services). Shipping and Handling price is not negotiable. We use the handling charge to cover our shipping department cost, packaging materials, fuel charges, boxes, and labels. Please do not bid if you don't agree with our shipping and handling prices. Do not email us after the auction to reduce the shipping price. No local pick up. No third party shipping carrier will be used. We only ship via USPS. Payment Information Paypal Bidpay Money Order, and Cashier's Check Credit card can be used through our website Click here to pay with credit card Winners Please wait for our payment instruction through email. Payment instruction is usually send within 24 hours of end of auction. Do not email us for payment instruction unless you have not receive one from us for past 24 hours. Include your Auction Item #, eBay User ID, and Shipping Address along with your payment. Payment must be received within 10 days of the close of the auction. All CA resident must add 8% sales tax before shipping General Info Your bid is a contract - Place a bid only if you're serious about buying the item. If you are the winning bidder, you will enter into a legally binding contract to purchase the item from us. All NPB (Non Paying Bidder) will be report to eBay and we will leave you a negative feedback. All order is usually shipped with in 24 - 48 hours upon receipt of payment. Please include your Auction Item #, and your eBay User ID with all of your email inquires. If you receive a defected item, email us for RMA instruction. We will leave you a feedback within 1 week of close of auction. Email Us | Our eBay Store | Pay Auction | Support Payment I accept the following forms of payment: PayPal, Visa/Master Card, American Express, Money Order. Low cost image hosting and full service auction management solutions: AuctionWatch Visit www.PCMicroStore.com today! Payment Details See item description and Payment Instructions, or contact seller for more information. Payment Instructions See item description or contact seller for more information.</Description></Item><Item ItemID="5689"><Name>~POWERBOOK 2GB HARD DRIVE 190/5300/3400/1400+</Name><Category>Computers</Category><Category>Laptops &amp; Accessories</Category><Category>Accessories</Category><Category>Memory Upgrades</Category><Currently>$30.0</Currently><First_Bid>$30.0</First_Bid><Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids><Bids/><Location Latitude="33.016928" Longitude="-116.846046">Escondido, CA</Location><Country>USA</Country><Started>Dec-15-01 16:06:14</Started><Ends>Dec-18-01 16:06:14</Ends><Seller Rating="18024" UserID="adeal.com"/><Description>~POWERBOOK 2GB HARD DRIVE 190/5300/3400/1400+ This is an IBM 2160MB hard drive. 12.5mm height - slim. Will work in the Powerbook 190, 2300, 5300, 1400, 3400, and more. This AT drive will not work in SCSI systems like the Powerbook 1xx series (100, 140, 160, etc.) or the 520/540 series. Formatted blank - No OS Pulled from a unit with a bad display. GUARANTEED NO DOA! Note: The mounting holes dont line up on this drive. The drive will need to be secured with double sided tape or another method. Buyer prepays with check / money order or paypal.com plus $6.50 for S/H and Tracking Number in Continental US. We welcome customers from Australia, Canada, Japan, Hong Kong, New Zealand, Singapore, South Korea, Taiwan, and all West-European Countries. Please write us for additional shipping costs. Please note that Battery Orders must be shipped via UPS only!!!! California Residents please add 7.50 % Sales Tax to the purchased price -NO RESERVE- Visit our eBay Store for more NON-AUCTION HOT DEALS.... Click here to review Our Payment Terms and Warranty Policy . We welcome credit card payments via Paypal and BillPoint: Visit our eBay Store for more NON-AUCTION HOT DEALS.... This listing created by eBay Seller's Assistant Pro Free Honesty Counters powered by Andale! Visit Adeal.com today! Payment Details U.S. Shipping and Handling $6.50 Shipping Insurance per item - Sales Tax (7.500% if shipped to CA) _ Learn more about checkout Payment Instructions All sales through Auction are final. We do not offer refunds, as this is an Auction. Any exceptions to this policy will be done by special request only; and are subject to a 20?restocking fee. Shipping costs are non-refundable.</Description></Item><Item ItemID="5690"><Name>NEW 256 MB IBM THINKPAD Laptop MEMORY FAST!++</Name><Category>Computers</Category><Category>Laptops &amp; Accessories</Category><Category>Accessories</Category><Category>Memory Upgrades</Category><Currently>$24.99</Currently><First_Bid>$24.99</First_Bid><Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids><Bids/><Location Latitude="27.405429" Longitude="-82.543519">Tallhassee, FL</Location><Country>USA</Country><Started>Dec-15-01 16:40:02</Started><Ends>Dec-18-01 16:40:02</Ends><Seller Rating="30" UserID="charliefsu"/><Description>NEW 256 MB IBM THINKPAD Laptop MEMORY FAST!++ v\:* {behavior:url(#default#VML);} o\:* {behavior:url(#default#VML);} w\:* {behavior:url(#default#VML);} .shape {behavior:url(#default#VML);} 256MB SONY Laptop Memory 0 NEW 256MB Sony VAIO Laptop BEST QUALITY USING SONY CHIPS FAST!Memory Product Information PRODUCT SPECIFICATIONS These items are Brand New Lifetime Warranty Warranty Lifetime Condition NEW Total memory 256 MB PC-100 per module Chip type SDRAM / SODIMM Pins 144-pin Length 2 5/8 inch (standard length) Height 1.25 inch (low profile) Voltage 3.3v (standard voltage) Laptop Compatibility Guide ----------------------------------Models----------------------------------- FX Series(1 slot)*upgrade to a better chip FREE E-mail GR Series(1slot)*upgrade to a better chip FREE E-mail SR Series All-in-One PCG-FX1xxk Notebooks PCG-FX120K* unsure PCG-FX140K PCG-FX150K PCG-FX170K PCG-FX190K All-in-One PCG-FX2xx Notebooks PCG-FX250 FX250K PCG-FX290, FX290K All-in-One PCG-FX3xx Notebooks PCG-FX340, FX340K,FX340P PCG-FX370, FX370K,FX370P PCG-FX390, FX390K,FX390P VAIO PCG--FXA series PCG-FXA32, FXA36 VAIO All-in-One Notebook PCG-F520, F540, F560, F580, F590 PCG-F540K, F560K, F580K, F590K PCG-F610, F630, F650, F650K PCG-F680, F680K, F690, F690K SuperSlim Pro R505 Notebooks PCG-R505TS, PCG-R505TSK. PCG-R505TE, PCG-R505TEK Shipping and Handling Shipping and Handling is $10.00 per each auction. Memory will be shipped via United States Postal Service. I can ship to any of the 50 states and US possessions, but I will ship to FPO/APO military bases. I will ship internationally. NO RESERVE Buyer to pay $9.99 for shipping and handling.(Act as Reserve/ shipping/handling) Insurance of $2.99 MUST also be Included Click here to view my other auctions. Created by eBay Seller's Assistant Pro</Description></Item><Item ItemID="5692"><Name>Ship Boat Carriers Mousepad</Name><Category>Computers</Category><Category>Input Peripherals</Category><Category>Mousepads</Category><Currently>$7.95</Currently><First_Bid>$7.95</First_Bid><Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids><Bids/><Location Latitude="41.685744" Longitude="-81.672797">Cleveland,Ohio</Location><Country>USA</Country><Started>Dec-15-01 17:28:04</Started><Ends>Dec-18-01 17:28:04</Ends><Seller Rating="1354" UserID="fatmat0126"/><Description>Here is an Adorable mousepad.Measurements are 7.5"x8" and is 1/4".This is a Brand New mousepad.PayPal is accepted.Winning Bidder needs to add $2.50 for S/H and $3.50 if outside of the USA and Canada.If you win more than 1 auction you get free shipping on all the rest of them after the 1st.Please no dead beat bidders.Appropriate feedback is always left.Thanks for looking and Good Luck!.</Description></Item><Item ItemID="5693"><Name>BROTHER HL 1260 #331</Name><Category>Computers</Category><Category>Printers &amp; Supplies</Category><Category>Laser Printers</Category><Category>B&amp;W</Category><Category>Other</Category><Currently>$99.0</Currently><First_Bid>$99.0</First_Bid><Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids><Bids/><Location Latitude="39.012134" Longitude="-76.68561">CROFTON MD.</Location><Country>USA</Country><Started>Dec-15-01 17:46:21</Started><Ends>Dec-22-01 17:46:21</Ends><Seller Rating="836" UserID="computerstore2"/><Description>BROTHER HL 1260 #331 THIS IS A BROTHER HL-1260 1200dpi LASER PRINTER , THAT PRINTS AT 12ppm. IT HAS A 650 SHEET PAPER TRAY, AND WILL COME WITH A GOOD USER TONER CART. IT HAS A PAPER COUNT OF 18K. AND 6-MEGS OF RAM . We offer a 30 DAY WARRANTY on hardware only, software is not included in the warranty. We offer a 30 DAY WARRANTY on hardware only, software is not included in the warranty. All items won in the auction must be paid for within 10 days of auction end. Failure to pay for your item will result in negative feedback. The next highest bidder will then have the opportunity to buy the item. Our preferred shipper is UPS ground. Buyers pay actual shipping and handling fees. The handling fee is a separate charge to double pack the merchandise so it arrives safely to your door in working order, it will be $15.00 for this unit. Insurance for purchases is available upon request and buyer pays insurance fees CHECK OUT OUR OTHER GREAT DEALS Created by eBay Seller's Assistant Pro</Description></Item><Item ItemID="5695"><Name>HP LaserJet 6P Printer only 20k pg ct NICE!</Name><Category>Computers</Category><Category>Printers &amp; Supplies</Category><Category>Laser Printers</Category><Category>B&amp;W</Category><Category>HP</Category><Currently>$100.0</Currently><First_Bid>$100.0</First_Bid><Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids><Bids/><Location>Mid-Northwest</Location><Country>USA</Country><Started>Dec-15-01 18:06:42</Started><Ends>Dec-18-01 18:06:42</Ends><Seller Rating="311" UserID="lovin75"/><Description>This auction is for one Hewlett Packard Laserjet 6P Printer. Total memory is 2 Mbytes. Page Count is 20,021. For more information, please visit the HP site. Low Reserve. Buyer pays fixed s/h charges of $25.00, will be shipped by UPS. This printer does have a used toner cartridge. The printer includes both Power Cord and Printer Cable. This printer is Clean, and Prints Well. All printers offered are corporate off-lease items and will be Guaranteed No Dead On Arrival. Payment by Money order or Cashiers check. Sorry No Shipping to P.O. Boxes. Thank You and Happy Bidding! Please view my other auctions for other Quality: Monitors, Printers, and Servers.</Description></Item><Item ItemID="5702"><Name>NEW 128 MB Laptop memory SONY VIAO! A++ LOOK!</Name><Category>Computers</Category><Category>Laptops &amp; Accessories</Category><Category>Accessories</Category><Category>Memory Upgrades</Category><Currently>$9.99</Currently><First_Bid>$9.99</First_Bid><Number_of_Bids>1</Number_of_Bids><Bids><Bid><Bidder Rating="42" UserID="folkartshoppe@aol.com"><Location>Venezia</Location><Country>Italy</Country></Bidder><Time>Dec-16-01 13:45:03</Time><Amount>$9.99</Amount></Bid></Bids><Location Latitude="27.405429" Longitude="-82.543519">Tallhassee, FL</Location><Country>USA</Country><Started>Dec-15-01 19:45:03</Started><Ends>Dec-18-01 19:45:03</Ends><Seller Rating="30" UserID="charliefsu"/><Description>NEW 128 MB Laptop memory SONY VIAO! A++ LOOK! v\:* {behavior:url(#default#VML);} o\:* {behavior:url(#default#VML);} w\:* {behavior:url(#default#VML);} .shape {behavior:url(#default#VML);} 128MB IBM THINKPAD Laptop Memory 0 NEW 128MB Sony VAIO Laptop Memory(BEST QUALITY!) Product Information PRODUCT SPECIFICATIONS These items are Brand New Lifetime Warranty Warranty Lifetime Condition NEW Total memory 128 MB PC-100 per module Chip type SDRAM / SODIMM Pins 144-pin Length 2 5/8 inch (standard length) Height 1.25 inch (low profile) Voltage 3.3v (standard voltage) Laptop Compatibility Guide ----------------------------------Models----------------------------------- All-in-One PCG-FX1xx Notebooks PCG-FX120, FX120K PCG-FX140, FX140K PCG-FX1500, FX150K PCG-FX170, FX170K PCG-FX190, FX190K All-in-One PCG-FX2xx Notebooks PCG-FX210 PCG-FX220, FX220K PCG-FX240, FX240K PCG-FX250, FX250K PCG-FX270, FX270K PCG-FX290, FX290K VAIO PCG-XG series PCG-XG28, 28K VAIO All-in-One Notebook PCG-F520, F540, F560, F580, F590 PCG-F540K, F560K, F580K, F590K PCG-F610, F630, F650, F650K PCG-F680, F680K, F690, F690K VAIO SuperSlim Notebooks PCG-Z505HS, Z505HSK PCG-Z505JE, Z505JEK PCG-Z505JS, Z505JSK PCG-Z505LE, Z505LEK PCG-Z505LS, Z505LSK PCG-Z505RE SuperSlim Pro R505 Notebooks PCG-R505TS, PCG-R505TSK. PCG-R505TE, PCG-R505TEK Shipping and Handling Shipping and Handling is $10.00 per each auction. Memory will be shipped via United States Postal Service. I can ship to any of the 50 states and US possessions, but I will ship to FPO/APO military bases. I will ship internationally. NO RESERVE Buyer to pay $9.99 for shipping and handling. Insurance of $2.99MUST also be INCLUDED. Please click here to see my other auctions. Created by eBay Seller's Assistant Pro</Description></Item><Item ItemID="5704"><Name>NEC SuperScript 1260 Laser Printer</Name><Category>Computers</Category><Category>Printers &amp; Supplies</Category><Category>Laser Printers</Category><Category>B&amp;W</Category><Category>Other</Category><Currently>$1.0</Currently><Buy_Price>$5.9</Buy_Price><First_Bid>$1.0</First_Bid><Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids><Bids/><Location Latitude="40.134792" Longitude="-79.74272">PA</Location><Country>USA</Country><Started>Dec-15-01 19:55:41</Started><Ends>Dec-20-01 19:55:41</Ends><Seller Rating="47" UserID="phillydiscounters"/><Description>NEC SUPERSCRIPT 1260 LASER PRINTER Specifications Print Speed: 12 pages per minute Print Resolution: 600 x 600 dots per inch NEC Sharp Edge Technology (SET): 124 levels of gray _Processor: 60MHz PrintGear imaging processor, 18MHz 68EC000 coprocessor Minimum System Requirements: Windows 95, Windows 3.1x, Windows NT 4.0, or DOS 3.3 386 or better IBM-compatible 4MB of RAM (6MB recommended) for use with Windows 3.1x 8MB of RAM for use with Windows 95 16MB of RAM for use with Windows NT 4.0 Interface: Bidirectional parallel _Print Languages: Adobe PrintGear, HP PCL 4 RAM: 2MB RAM standard, 16MB RAM maximum, Parity or non-parity (uses industry-standard , 72pin SIMM, 70 nanoseconds or faster) Adobe Memory Booster effectively triples_ installed memory to ensure printing of even complex jobs Printer Drivers: Windows 95, Windows 3.1x, Windows NT 4.0 and DOS Mac OS through EtherTalk (with Network Interface Upgrade Kit option) Paper Weights: 20 to 28 lbs (cassette feed), 20 to 50 lbs (multipurpose feed) Paper Types: Paper: Letter, executive, A4, B5, legal, heavy stock paper, transparency film, adhesive label Envelopes: Commercial 10, Monarch, International DL, International C5 Paper Output: Face-down tray (maximum capacity 250 sheets at 20 lbs) Fact about this printer: -Printer is refurbished, worn or broken part are replaced with working or new parts -2MB Ram -Toner -Power Cord Page count: -Page printed:___ 2,446 Before making your bid please read the following. You are responsible to know and understand this information prior to bidding. Auction info: All items are used/refurbished unless stated otherwise above. All items do not include manuals, drivers, software, ink/toner, cables or anything else unless stated otherwise above. Always assume you will only get what is in the picture. If there is no software or accessories displayed in the picture of the item, then they are not included. If Toner is included, there is no guarantee of amount._ The text next to the picture states warranty info and/or included items if applicable, this supersedes the description text if there is any discrepancy. Shipping: Shipping and Handling:_ 65.00 dollars. Sales/Warranty Policy: All auction sales are final. The high bidder(s) is/are expected to pay for this product whether or not they want it. All non-payments will be turned over to a 3rd party collection agency. No refunds. Exchanges or replacement only when available. All returns must be verified via e-mail prior to return. No unauthorized returns will be accepted. Please include_ Invoice #, purchase date, and description of problem. All returns must be packaged in the same packaging that they where received in. Product will be repaired or replaced with_ similar unit, and shipped to customer at no charge during warranty period. All products that are sold As-Is or without warranty are purchased at the risk of the customer. We test_ all units and they are working or as described in auction information._ Under no circumstances will refunds or replacements be given for non-working products that are sold without warranty. If it does not state in the above auction description that this item includes a warranty, then it does not. We are not responsible for typographical errors and reserve the right to refuse any order for any reason._ We love using ebay and usually have great relationships with our customers! There are a few people who email us with less than friendly emails. In most cases, they have NOT read the entire auction carefully. We spend a lot of time researching each item as carefully as we can before posting. We represent each item as best we can, to help make your decision process as easy as possible. In some cases the information we receive from literature in the product or from a website is inaccurate. We will do all we can to remedy such mistakes as soon as possible. Ultimately it is the responsibility of the bidder/potential bidder to know what they are bidding on, period. If you are uncertain, do the research. If you still are uncertain then ask before you bid, not after. We do not refund any monies due to misunderstood auctions. In the event that a shipping carrier is late in a delivery of your item, please contact us and we will do all we can to assist in locating the shipment. Please realize that once a package is shipped it is no longer in our control. _ _ _ _ _ Free Honesty Counters powered by Andale! Payment Details See item description and Payment Instructions, or contact seller for more information. Payment Instructions See item description or contact seller for more information.</Description></Item><Item ItemID="5705"><Name>SONY VAIO Laptop 128MB RAM Memory Upgrade</Name><Category>Computers</Category><Category>Laptops &amp; Accessories</Category><Category>Accessories</Category><Category>Memory Upgrades</Category><Currently>$19.99</Currently><First_Bid>$19.99</First_Bid><Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids><Bids/><Location Latitude="38.8951" Longitude="77.0367">DC Metro</Location><Country>USA</Country><Started>Dec-15-01 19:58:50</Started><Ends>Dec-18-01 19:58:50</Ends><Seller Rating="81" UserID="laptopbroker"/><Description>SONY VAIO Laptop 128MB RAM Manufactured Specifically for your Sony Vaio Product Specifications: - - Brand New - - 128 MB RAM - - PC 100 - - Gold Contacts - - 144 Pin (Standard) - - Low Profile - - 3.3 volt - - SO DIMM - - Lifetime Warranty - - Customer Service and Installation assistance included. - - Anti-Static Packaging Additional Product Information: - - Made for use in the folllowing models: - Sony - VAIO PCG 705C 707C 717C Sony - VAIO PCG 719C 729C - Sony - VAIO PCG 748 808 812 818 838 - Sony - VAIO PCG F150 F160 F180 F190 - Sony - VAIO PCG Z505S Z505SX Z505R Z505RX - Sony - VAIO PCG F304 F305 F309 F340 - Sony - VAIO PCG F370 F390 F420 F430 - Sony - VAIO PCG F450 F480 F490 F480K F490K - Sony - VAIO PCG F590 F580 F560 F540 - Sony - VAIO PCG F590K F580K F560K F540K - Sony - VAIO PCG XG9 XG18 XG19 - Sony - VAIO PCG XG28K XG29 XG28 - Sony - VAIO PCG Z505HE PIII 450 - Sony - VAIO PCG Z505HS PIII 500 - Sony - VAIO PCG Z505HSK PIII 500 - Sony - VAIO PCG Z505JSK PIII 650 - Sony - VAIO PCG Z505JEK PIII 500 - Sony - VAIO PCG Z505JS PIII 650 - Sony - VAIO PCG Z505JE PIII 500 Terms&amp;Conditions We want your eBay experience to be as enjoyable as possible. PLEASE do not bid if you are not 100% sure that you want this item and you are sure you are willing to pay your maximum bid price. We will contact the winning bidder via e-mail within 2 Business days after the auction has ended. Winning bidders must confirm their order within 3 business days after notification. Additional instructions for completion of sale will be included in the e-mail notification. Payment must be received within 7 business days after order is confirmed, or the winning bid will automatically be voided. Exceptions to this rule will be made on an individual basis. Please contact us within 3 days if you need special arrangements. We make every attempt to represent our products honestly, on occasion; we have found that packages have different specifications than the actual product. When bidding please keep in mind that there can be minor differences from specifications advertised and what is actually present (this is rare, but does happen). Most orders shipped within 2 Business days of receipt of verifiable payment. Since all sales are in auction format, all auction sales are final. No refunds are available, we can only issue an exchange for the following reasons: o Incorrect Quantity or Incorrect Item Shipped o Freight Damage (Recipient must make claim with shipment carrier first.) o Defective items must be returned to the manufacturer for service We cannot issue an exchange product for any other reason than stated above. We will not be held liable for any incident or any accident or consequential damages related to the use or misuse of this item under any circumstances. No suitability of use is expressed or implied in this sale. Shipping fees and return fees are non-refundable! Shipping and Freight: - - Freight, Insurance and handling within the US is $9.99 per module. - - International bids accepted please email us for freight rate Payment Options: Pay me securely with your Visa or MasterCard through PayPal! function dw(nu){document.write(s1+"ppsl"+nu+".gif"+s2+sA[nu]);}f1="document.links";s1="\ ","\"Pay me securely with your Visa or MasterCard through PayPal!\"\","\"Winning bidder, click here to pay instantly by credit card!\"\");c1=c2=c3=c4=0;for(i=0;i =0){c1++;}else if((eval(f1+"["+i+"].search")).indexOf("BetterSeller")=0){c2++;}else if((eval(f1+"["+i+"].search")).indexOf("ListItemForSaleShow")=0){c3++;}else if((eval(f1+"["+i+"].hash")).indexOf("ListItemForSaleAutosShow")=0){c4++;}}if((c1=2)||(c20)||(c30)||(c40)){dw(3);}else{dw(2);}f11="xclick-auction";f13="item=";f14="";for(i=0;i 0){s11=document.links[i].search;j=s11.indexOf(f13);if(j0){s11=s11.slice((j+(f13.length)));for(k=0;k =0){document.links[i].href=((document.links[i].href)+"&amp;jitem_id="+f14+"&amp;jmagic=1");}} BidPay.com - the online money order auction payment service. www.BidPay.com Wire Transfers, Money Orders and Cashiers Checks Accepted. Additional Questions: Please do not hesitate to contact us with your questions Sales@laptopbroker.com http://www.laptopbroker.com " style="text-decoration:none" id=blinklink Please Check Our Other Auctions Payment Details See item description and Payment Instructions, or contact seller for more information. Payment Instructions See item description or contact seller for more information.</Description></Item><Item ItemID="5706"><Name>NEW 128 MB Laptop memory DELL Inspiron BEST!</Name><Category>Computers</Category><Category>Laptops &amp; Accessories</Category><Category>Accessories</Category><Category>Memory Upgrades</Category><Currently>$9.99</Currently><First_Bid>$9.99</First_Bid><Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids><Bids/><Location Latitude="27.405429" Longitude="-82.543519">Tallhassee, FL</Location><Country>USA</Country><Started>Dec-15-01 20:00:06</Started><Ends>Dec-18-01 20:00:06</Ends><Seller Rating="30" UserID="charliefsu"/><Description>NEW 128 MB Laptop memory DELL Inspiron BEST! Brand New 128 MB RAM Laptop memory DELL Inspiron and Latitude, FAST! Brand New 128 MB RAM Laptop memory DELL Inspiron and Latitude, FAST! BEST QUALITY! ($10 OFF see below) Welcome you are bidding on a New PC100/133 128mb SO Dimm Laptop memory. MADE with Samsung or TOSHIBA chips and NEC 6 layer board(BEST IN QUALITY!),It is lightning fast and great for multi-tasking and internet surfing, the speed of your laptop will greatly increase if you upgrade using this Chip. DELL Inspiron, Latitude / Speed: PC100 (100 MHz @ CL2) / Density: 128 MB / Organization: 16M x 64 / Module Type: 144 pin SODIMM SDRAM / * Inspiron 2000 * Inspiron 2100 * Inspiron 2500 * Inspiron 3500 * Inspiron 3700 * Inspiron 3800 * Inspiron 4000 * Inspiron 5000 * Inspiron 5000e * Inspiron 7500 * Inspiron 8000 * Inspiron 8100 *Latitude C600 * Latitude C800 * Latitude CPx * Latitude LS Also Compatib w/ most ACER, COMPAQ, IBM,APPLE, GATEWAY,NEC, SONY,Hewlett Packard, Toshiba &amp; others. PLUS FREE Lifetime wty Features *JEDEC standard 3.3V power supply *LVTTL compatible with multiplexed address *Four banks operation *MRS cycle with address key programs CAS latency (2 &amp; 3) Burst length (1, 2, 4, 8 &amp; Full page) Burst type (Sequential &amp; Interleave) *All inputs are sampled at the positive going edge of the system clock. *Burst read single-bit write operation *DQM for masking *Auto &amp; self refresh *64ms refresh period (8KB Cycle) Good luck! Lightning FAST!! Info Link: Dell (price check) Please E-mail For questions and price! Name: Charlie Email: xyc1013@garnet.acns.fsu.edu Buyer to pay $9.99 for shipping and handling. MUST BE INCLUDED Insurance of $2.99 MUST BE INCLUDED Click here to view my other auctions. Created by eBay Seller's Assistant Pro</Description></Item><Item ItemID="5707"><Name>HP laserjet 4Plus printer</Name><Category>Computers</Category><Category>Printers &amp; Supplies</Category><Category>Laser Printers</Category><Category>B&amp;W</Category><Category>HP</Category><Currently>$5.5</Currently><First_Bid>$1.0</First_Bid><Number_of_Bids>2</Number_of_Bids><Bids><Bid><Bidder Rating="105" UserID="klubkar@aol.com"><Location>Venezia</Location><Country>Italy</Country></Bidder><Time>Dec-16-01 16:07:26</Time><Amount>$3.25</Amount></Bid><Bid><Bidder Rating="89" UserID="wildkelkat"><Location>Venezia</Location><Country>Italy</Country></Bidder><Time>Dec-17-01 00:05:35</Time><Amount>$5.5</Amount></Bid></Bids><Location Latitude="39.963622" Longitude="-79.785349">PA</Location><Country>USA</Country><Started>Dec-15-01 20:09:18</Started><Ends>Dec-20-01 20:09:18</Ends><Seller Rating="47" UserID="phillydiscounters"/><Description>HP LaserJet 4Plus Printer -Self-test came out perfectly _ _It's appearance is very nice but shows that it has been used. The printer was thoroughly tested and cleaned and meets factory specifications._ Please read notes below._ _ Printer Include: -Toner -Power Cord _ Printer Name: Hp Laserjet 4 Plus Pages Printed: 44,060 Ports: Parallel Print Quality Mode: Standard Network HP jetdirect -J2555B RAM Memory: 2MB Fonts Available: N/A Before making your bid please read the following. You are responsible to know and understand this information prior to bidding. Auction info: All items are used/refurbished unless stated otherwise above. All items do not include manuals, drivers, software, ink/toner, cables or anything else unless stated otherwise above. Always assume you will only get what is in the picture. If there is no software or accessories displayed in the picture of the item, then they are not included. If Toner is included, there is no guarantee of amount. The text next to the picture states warranty info and/or included items if applicable, this supersedes the description text if there is any discrepancy. Shipping: Shipping and Handling:_ 49.00 dollars Sales/Warranty Policy: All auction sales are final. The high bidder(s) is/are expected to pay for this product whether or not they want it. All non-payments will be turned over to a 3rd party collection agency. No refunds. Exchanges or replacement only when available. All returns must be verified via e-mail prior to return. No unauthorized returns will be accepted. Please include Invoice #, purchase date, and description of problem. All returns must be packaged in the same packaging that they where received in. Product will be repaired or replaced with similar unit, and shipped to customer at no charge during warranty period. All products that are sold As-Is or without warranty are purchased at the risk of the customer. We test all units and they are working or as described in auction information. Under no circumstances will refunds or replacements be given for non-working products that are sold without warranty. If it does not state in the above auction description that this item includes a warranty, then it does not. We are not responsible for typographical errors and reserve the right to refuse any order for any reason We love using ebay and usually have great relationships with our customers! There are a few people who email us with less than friendly emails. In most cases, they have NOT read the entire auction carefully. We spend a lot of time researching each item as carefully as we can before posting. We represent each item as best we can, to help make your decision process as easy as possible. In some cases the information we receive from literature in the product or from a website is inaccurate. We will do all we can to remedy such mistakes as soon as possible. Ultimately it is the responsibility of the bidder/potential bidder to know what they are bidding on, period. If you are uncertain, do the research. If you still are uncertain then ask before you bid, not after. We do not refund any monies due to misunderstood auctions . In the event that a shipping carrier is late in a delivery of your item, please contact us and we will do all we can to assist in locating the shipment. Please realize that once a package is shipped it is no longer in our control. PayPal Account is phillydiscounters@altavista.com Outside of USA ask for shipping quote Free Honesty Counters powered by Andale! Payment Details See item description and Payment Instructions, or contact seller for more information. Payment Instructions See item description or contact seller for more information.</Description></Item><Item ItemID="5725"><Name>HP Laserjet 4L with toner cartridge and cable</Name><Category>Computers</Category><Category>Printers &amp; Supplies</Category><Category>Laser Printers</Category><Category>B&amp;W</Category><Category>HP</Category><Currently>$60.0</Currently><First_Bid>$60.0</First_Bid><Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids><Bids/><Location Latitude="30.31536" Longitude="-97.663293">austin, tx</Location><Country>USA</Country><Started>Dec-16-01 00:33:00</Started><Ends>Dec-23-01 00:33:00</Ends><Seller Rating="86" UserID="dejai@swbell.net"/><Description>Used working HP Laserjet 4L printer....shipping $15.00..payment via paypal, MO ane Cashier ck...thanks. Payment Details See item description and Payment Instructions, or contact seller for more information. Payment Instructions See item description or contact seller for more information.</Description></Item><Item ItemID="5727"><Name>HP LaserJet 1100 Copier/Scanner Option *New*</Name><Category>Computers</Category><Category>Printers &amp; Supplies</Category><Category>Laser Printers</Category><Category>B&amp;W</Category><Category>HP</Category><Currently>$69.95</Currently><First_Bid>$69.95</First_Bid><Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids><Bids/><Location>Winnipeg, MB</Location><Country>Canada</Country><Started>Dec-16-01 13:42:07</Started><Ends>Dec-23-01 13:42:07</Ends><Seller Rating="32" UserID="kortextsg"/><Description>KORTEX TSG HP LaserJet 1100 Copier/Scanner Option *New* Product Information You are bidding on one (1) new, factory sealed Copier/Scanner option for the HP LaserJet 1100 series of printers. Condition: HP Factory sealed, new with standard HP manufacturer's warranty.. Mfg Part Number: C4421A Asset ID: W4-81228 Shipping, Handling &amp; Insurance Information US &amp; Canadian customers - All products will be sent via UPS Ground. Insurance extra. Winnipeg customers - No pick-ups available. All products will be delivered by city courier from our warehouses at a flat rate of $10Cdn. Save on shipping by winning multiple auctions. All products are located in Winnipeg, Manitoba, Canada and will ship 2-3 days after payment. Local Courier UPS Ground Winnipeg $10.00 Cdn -- Canada -- $ 19.95 USD United States -- $ 19.95 USD Payment Information Visa and MasterCard are the ONLY forms of payment. Sorry, PayPal, Billpoint and money orders will not be accepted. Payment must be received within 3 days of auction close. Winning bidders will receive notification immediately after the auction closes on the steps required to complete the purchase. All prices indicated are listed in US Dollars unless otherwise specified. Final credit card payment (product, shipping and taxes) will be processed in CANADIAN funds. US credit card payments will be converted back into US funds by the issuing credit card company. Auction Terms &amp; Conditions It is our goal to describe the items in our auctions to the best of our ability. All auction sales are final. No returns, exchanges, credits or offsets. Products are sold as is, where is with no warranty expressed or implied. Some products may have balance of original manufacturer's warranty. No response or non-paying bidders will result in negative feedback. We reserve the right to end an auction early as well as refuse a bid from anyone with negative feedback. Taxes Canadian customers are subject to any applicable taxes (PST, GST and HST). US customers are responsible for all applicable taxes - local, state, import duties and brokerage fees. Contact Information E-mail us at ebay@KortexTSG.com with any questions and INCLUDE the eBay item number. Winning bidders will receive a Winning Bidder Notification e-mail indicating all post-sale auction information and purchasing instructions (via AuctionWatch.com). Please submit all inquiries by e-mail and please be advised that e-mails will only be answered between 8am to 4pm CST. Thank you. Good luck, happy bidding &amp; bid with confidence! Low cost image hosting and full service auction management solutions: AuctionWatch Payment Details See item description and Payment Instructions, or contact seller for more information. Payment Instructions See item description or contact seller for more information.</Description></Item><Item ItemID="5729"><Name>Diamond HomeFree Phoneline PCI Network Kit</Name><Category>Computers</Category><Category>Networking &amp; I.T.</Category><Category>Network Interface Cards</Category><Category>Other</Category><Currently>$9.95</Currently><First_Bid>$9.95</First_Bid><Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids><Bids/><Location Latitude="37.680181" Longitude="-121.921498">Hayward, CA</Location><Country>USA</Country><Started>Dec-16-01 14:21:06</Started><Ends>Dec-19-01 14:21:06</Ends><Seller Rating="7827" UserID="justdeals.com"/><Description>Overview HomeFree connects your PCs using the phone lines already in your home, making it both affordable and easy to use. Now your family can share Internet access and printers. Plus, Homefree's innovative design is based on the Home PNA network standard, assuring compatibility with a wide range of phoneline networking products. Phone lines transfer voice and data over different frequencies, allowing you to use your phone and network simultaneously. What's more, HomeFree's speed (up to 1 Mbps) makes it easy to share files of any size. It also delivers the performance that today's intense multi-player games require. It's simple to install too. Just plug in the card, and plug the card into an open phone jack and your network is up and running. Best of all, HomeFree saves you money because you no longer need additional modems, printers, and other peripherals to make each networked PC fully functional. One HomeFree Phoneline Card per computer is all you need. Homefree Phoneline PCI Network Kit W/10 Base (2-Cards) Larger Image Features Simultaneous telephone &amp; network connections Internet sharing Printer &amp; peripheral sharing 1 Mbps transfer speed Uses existing phone lines Product Name S3/Diamond HomeFree Phoneline PCI adapter (Homefree PCI) OS Supported Windows 95, Windows 98, or Windows 2000 Transmission Method Phoneline Standard HomePNA 1.0 (1Mbps) Card Format PCI Data rate 1Mbps (Manufacturer's specification) 0.45 - 0.50Mbps measured Winning bidders will receive a payment link in their user's email within three(3) business days of auction close. All International (outside the United States) orders will be automatically cancelled. All transactions not completed within ten(10) business days of auction closing date will be cancelled. All items are sold "as-is" and guaranteed to be in good working order upon arrival unless otherwise specified. *Not responsible for typographical errors. *Third-party brands and names are the property of their respective owners. Condition This is a Brand New OEM Packaged item with Justdeals.com's 30 day warranty. Payment Options Visa or MasterCard or Amex or Discover Shipping Shipping is $9.95 PER ITEM via UPS Ground Service No International Shipping (outside the US) Sales Tax California Residents Please Add 8% Sales Tax JDpart: NW10649B If you are the winning bidder, please read the following instructions: Once this auction ends, I will send you an email with instructions for completing your purchase. To use my fast, easy, and secure checkout, just click on the link in the email or on the Checkout logo in this ad. At my checkout --powered by Andale-- please enter your shipping address and other information so I can calculate a final price and ship your purchase quickly. andale andalecheckout JustDeals.com, Inc. Visit JustDeals.com today! Payment Details See item description and Payment Instructions, or contact seller for more information. Payment Instructions Please see the item description for payment and checkout instructions.</Description></Item><Item ItemID="5732"><Name>Okidata Image Drum Kit OL400 / 800</Name><Category>Computers</Category><Category>Printers &amp; Supplies</Category><Category>Laser Printers</Category><Category>B&amp;W</Category><Category>Other</Category><Currently>$50.0</Currently><First_Bid>$50.0</First_Bid><Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids><Bids/><Location>Edmonton, Alberta</Location><Country>Canada</Country><Started>Dec-16-01 15:00:58</Started><Ends>Dec-23-01 15:00:58</Ends><Seller Rating="471" UserID="centre1"/><Description>if (navigator.appName == 'Microsoft Internet Explorer') { if (navigator.appVersion.substring(0,1) "); } else { document.write(" "); document.write(" "); document.write(" "); document.write(" BODY { background: url(/marble2.jpg) }"); document.write(" "); document.write(" "); } } else { //Default to Netscape settings. document.write(" "); } Okidata Image Drum Kit OL400 / 800 Genuine Replacement Image Drum Kit for use with all Okidata OL 400/800 Series Led Page Printers, DOC IT 3000/4000 Desktop Document Processors, (not for use with OL 400e/OL410e/OL410e/PS printers) NOS dated JL-03-99. P/N 56106601 NO RESERVE ALL SALES FINAL, AND SOLD AS IS, NO REFUNDS OR EXCHANGES. Ebay Payments, Paypal, Bidpay, Payment due within 7 days. In the USA, click on Ebay Payments or Paypal. No checks, money orders via Bidpay.com only. Buyer to pay $12.00 for shipping and handling. Air mail 4-7 business days. $1.00 optional insurance fee. Canadian Residents send your postal code so shipping charges may be adjusted, and an updated Ebay or Paypal invoice can be sent. No Overseas bidders without Prior approval. Not responsible for uninsured items. Click here to view my other auctions. Please register for electronic payments before bidding, Please send email questions before end of auction. Created by eBay Seller's Assistant Pro Free Honesty Counters powered by Andale! Payment Details U.S. Shipping and Handling $12.00 Shipping Insurance per item (optional) $1.00 Sales Tax (none) _ Learn more about checkout Payment Instructions All sales final.</Description></Item><Item ItemID="5745"><Name>4MB Memory for Compaq Contura, LTE Elite</Name><Category>Computers</Category><Category>Laptops &amp; Accessories</Category><Category>Accessories</Category><Category>Memory Upgrades</Category><Currently>$4.99</Currently><First_Bid>$4.99</First_Bid><Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids><Bids/><Location Latitude="33.711552" Longitude="-117.809881">Irvine, OC</Location><Country>USA</Country><Started>Dec-16-01 20:03:38</Started><Ends>Dec-23-01 20:03:38</Ends><Seller Rating="225" UserID="www.ezupgrades.com"/><Description>W E L C O M E 4MB Memory for Compaq Contura, LTE Elite 4MB Memory for Compaq Contura, LTE Elite FEATURES Compatible with following models: Compaq Lte Elite DX4/75, DX4/100 Compaq Contura Concerto *Manufacturer Warranty : 1Year *Item P/N :EXPCCON-4(SKU#) *Condition : NEW *Shipping Charge: $6(UPS GND Continental USA, lower 48 states) Bidding, shipping, and return policy We accept VISA/Master/AE credit card, cashier's check, money order and personal check. Personal checks delay shipping for 5-10 working days, cashier's check, money order, or credit card get immediate shipping. 15-day money back guarranty applies to defective part or part not as described, 15% restocking fee will be applied to the non-defective returns, shipping/handling charge is not refundable. California residents add 7.5% sales tax. All winners will receive the payment instructions email within one hour of the auction's end, or you can click here to submit the payment. If you win more than one item and would like to combine shipping please click here to find out the correct shipping charge. To track your auction order status please click here . click here for more detail Payment Details See item description and Payment Instructions, or contact seller for more information. Payment Instructions See item description or contact seller for more information.</Description></Item><Item ItemID="5749"><Name>Lot of 4 Standard Laptop Memory Modules</Name><Category>Computers</Category><Category>Laptops &amp; Accessories</Category><Category>Accessories</Category><Category>Memory Upgrades</Category><Currently>$1.0</Currently><First_Bid>$1.0</First_Bid><Number_of_Bids>1</Number_of_Bids><Bids><Bid><Bidder Rating="1" UserID="linhai99"><Location>Venezia</Location><Country>Italy</Country></Bidder><Time>Dec-17-01 15:56:40</Time><Amount>$1.0</Amount></Bid></Bids><Location Latitude="39.991729" Longitude="-83.082262">Columbus, OH</Location><Country>USA</Country><Started>Dec-16-01 21:15:34</Started><Ends>Dec-23-01 21:15:34</Ends><Seller Rating="34" UserID="einsteinsurplus.com-avogadro"/><Description>Shipping (UPS Ground): $7.45 (Approximately) _ (DOMESTIC US Bidders ONLY ) Payment: ONLY WE DO NOT TAKE PAYPAL All payments will be processed via our secure payment system, hosted by ReturnTrac._ For more info click here . For more information on our warranty terms and conditions click here . Conditions: 1. No Foreign Bids._ Domestic US bidders only. 2. No bidders with a negative feedback rating. 3. Failure to respond to email after 4 days of auction close will result in loss of the right to buy. 4. Failure to complete a transaction will result in negative feedback posted to buyer's account. 5. I reserve the right to cancel a bid for any reason on an item. Lot of 4 Standard Laptop Memory Modules _ ( Click image to view actual image size ) Item Details: Lot of 4 16MB SODIMMs Manufactured by Simple Technology New, Sealed In Individual Static Bags Standard Laptop Memory Time To Upgrade! This Auction Is For A Lot of 4, Picture Shows 10 Item Condition: New Untested Complete Free Honesty Counters powered by Andale! Payment Details U.S. Shipping and Handling $7.45 Shipping Insurance per item - Sales Tax (5.750% if shipped to OH) _ Learn more about checkout Payment Instructions A link to our secure online payment service, ReturnTrac, will be emailed shortly after the auction closes.</Description></Item><Item ItemID="5752"><Name>TIMESHEET PROFESSIONAL</Name><Category>Computers</Category><Category>Software</Category><Category>PC</Category><Category>Business</Category><Category>Project Management</Category><Currently>$6.95</Currently><First_Bid>$6.95</First_Bid><Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids><Bids/><Location Latitude="36.038181" Longitude="-115.086999">Henderson, NV</Location><Country>USA</Country><Started>Dec-17-01 01:29:16</Started><Ends>Dec-24-01 01:29:16</Ends><Seller Rating="175" UserID="whitd"/><Description>Fluke Manual TIMESHEET PROFESSIONAL You are bidding on TimeSheet Professional Version 2.0 by Timeslips Corporation._ Included is the software manual and 2 program disks.__ Timesheet is a versatile tool for both home and office._ The Timesheet Professional program helps you track your time and expenses for projects, clients, and activities using its unique "time sheet" format.__ _THEY ARE IN EXCELLENT CONDITION.__ REQUIREMENTS: AN IBM PC, XT, AT OR COMPATIBLE A 3.5" DISK DRIVE A VGA MONITOR AT LEAST 512K OF RAM A HARD DISK DOS 3.1 OR HIGHER PAYMENT AND SHIPPING Money Order, Cashier Check, or Visa/MC accepted through PayPal or Billpoint. Personal checks also accepted, but could take 10 days to clear. Payment is expected within 10 days after auction ends._ Product will be listed up again after the 10th day and appropriate feedback will be posted. Buyer to pay $5.00 for shipping and handling._ USPS Item will be shipped when payment has cleared. Insurance is optional and will be extra if buyer wants the package insured. Please only bid if you are willing to accept these terms. Read my feedbacks and Bid with confidence! Email me if you have any questions. Good Luck &amp; Happy Bidding! Take a look at my other auctions!</Description></Item><Item ItemID="5753"><Name>128MB IBM ThinkPad Laptop/Notebook Memory</Name><Category>Computers</Category><Category>Laptops &amp; Accessories</Category><Category>Accessories</Category><Category>Memory Upgrades</Category><Currently>$17.5</Currently><First_Bid>$17.5</First_Bid><Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids><Bids/><Location>AwesomeAuction</Location><Country>USA</Country><Started>Dec-17-01 03:52:18</Started><Ends>Dec-20-01 03:52:18</Ends><Seller Rating="76" UserID="ironhorse949"/><Description>128MB IBM ThinkPad Laptop/Notebook Memory IBM ThinkPad _ 128MB MEMORY FOR LAPTOP/NOTEBOOK UPGRADE for IBM Laptop/Notebook . New brand, one year warranty. Brand new! 144 Pin Low Profile 3.3 Standard V 128mb Sdram Gold Contacts High Quality So-Dimm _ _ IBM Laptop Compatibility Guide ----------------------------------Models----------------------------------- IBM - ThinkPad 240 (2609-xxx) IBM - ThinkPad 390 Pentium Series 2626-2xx,5xx,7xx IBM - ThinkPad 390E Celeron Series IBM - ThinkPad 390E Pentium II Series IBM - ThinkPad 390X Celeron 2626-9xx,Bxx,Fxx IBM - ThinkPad 390X Pentium II 2626-A,C,D,E,F,H,Jxx IBM - ThinkPad 390X Pentium III 2626-Lxx, Mxx IBM - ThinkPad 390 Pentium Series 2626-2xx,5xx,7xx IBM - ThinkPad 390E Celeron Series IBM - ThinkPad 390E Pentium II Series IBM - ThinkPad 390X Celeron 2626-9xx,Bxx,Fxx IBM - ThinkPad 390X Pentium II 2626-A,C,D,E,F,H,Jxx IBM - ThinkPad 390X Pentium III 2626-Lxx, Mxx IBM - ThinkPad 570 (2644-1xx, 2xx, 3xx) IBM - ThinkPad 570E Pentium III 2644-5xx, 6xx IBM - ThinkPad 600 2645-21U/31U IBM - ThinkPad 600 2645-35U/41U/51U/A1U IBM - ThinkPad 600 2645-45U/85U IBM - ThinkPad 600E 2645-3AU/4AU/5AU/Cxx IBM - ThinkPad 600E 2645-4BU/5BU/8BU/Bxx IBM - ThinkPad 600E 2645-8AU/AAU IBM - ThinkPad 600E 2645-A5U/55U/Bxx IBM - ThinkPad 600X (2645-3xx,4xx,7xx) IBM - ThinkPad 600X (2645-5xx,8xx,9xx) IBM - ThinkPad 770 9548-3xx, 9548-4xx IBM - ThinkPad 770 9549-1xx IBM - ThinkPad 770E 9548-5xx IBM - ThinkPad 770ED 9549-5xx IBM - ThinkPad 770X 9549-7xU IBM - ThinkPad 770Z 9549-8xU IBM - ThinkPad A20 series IBM - ThinkPad A21 series IBM - ThinkPad A22 series IBM - ThinkPad 1200 i Series IBM - ThinkPad 1300 i Series IBM - ThinkPad 1400 Series IBM - ThinkPad i Series 1410 IBM - ThinkPad i Series 1411 IBM - ThinkPad i Series 1412 IBM - ThinkPad i Series 1420 IBM - ThinkPad i Series 1421 IBM - ThinkPad i Series 1422 IBM - ThinkPad i Series 1441 IBM - ThinkPad i Series 1442 IBM - ThinkPad i Series 1450 IBM - ThinkPad i Series 1451 IBM - ThinkPad i Series 1452 IBM - ThinkPad i Series 1460 IBM - ThinkPad i Series 1472 IBM - ThinkPad i Series 1480 IBM - ThinkPad i Series 1482 IBM - ThinkPad i Series 1483 IBM - ThinkPad i Series 1492 IBM - ThinkPad i Series 14E2 IBM - ThinkPad 1500 i Series IBM - ThinkPad i Series 1512 IBM - ThinkPad i Series 1540 IBM - ThinkPad i Series 1541 IBM - ThinkPad i Series 1542 IBM - ThinkPad i Series 1550 IBM - ThinkPad i Series 1552 IBM - ThinkPad i Series 1560 IBM - ThinkPad i Series 1562 IBM - ThinkPad i Series 1592 IBM - ThinkPad i Series 1720 IBM - ThinkPad i Series 1721 IBM - ThinkPad T20 Series IBM - ThinkPad T21 Series IBM - ThinkPad T22 Series IBM - ThinkPad TransNote IBM - ThinkPad X20 IBM - ALL PENTIUM III _ PAYMENT, SHIPPING, HANDLING AND INSURANCE TERMS: ___ _ For S&amp;H US States only : Buyer agrees to pays $10.00 . For International Buyers only : Buyer agrees to pays $16.00 Usually we ship USPS First Class Mail with delivery confirmation all order at 2/7 business day after receiving payment Methods of payment: VISA and MasterCard via PayPal (your shipping address must be verified). eBay Online Payments by Billpoint Checks/Money Orders: We will hold the check for up to 10 business days to allow for check to clear Payment is expected within 10 days after the auction. Please do not BID If you don't except the above terms and conditions for Payment, shipping and handling.(NO exceptions) Warranty : One year replacement/repair. All sales are final. No return. This warranty applies only to the original end user purchaser and does not cover any damage to a product which results from accident, abuse, misuse, natural or personal disaster, or any unauthorized disassembly, repair or modifications. Note : This is bulk product , not retail pack. No pickup. No escrow. Please do not bid If you don't except the above terms and conditions for shipping and handling. (do not email us after you have won the auction and ask us to reduce the price of the item.) Please provide these information when you make payment: Quantity and Auction Item Number. First and Last Name. Complete Shipping Address Email Address Any Question Please Contact: ironhorse949@yahoo.com _ _ 2001 AwesomeAuction. All rights reserved.</Description></Item><Item ItemID="5755"><Name>Kingston 128 Mem Upgrade for HP OB &amp; PN</Name><Category>Computers</Category><Category>Laptops &amp; Accessories</Category><Category>Accessories</Category><Category>Memory Upgrades</Category><Currently>$9.99</Currently><Buy_Price>$34.51</Buy_Price><First_Bid>$9.99</First_Bid><Number_of_Bids>1</Number_of_Bids><Bids><Bid><Bidder Rating="31" UserID="trlifesaver"><Location>Venezia</Location><Country>Italy</Country></Bidder><Time>Dec-17-01 21:33:21</Time><Amount>$9.99</Amount></Bid></Bids><Location>Edmonton,AB,CA</Location><Country>Canada</Country><Started>Dec-17-01 04:44:28</Started><Ends>Dec-24-01 04:44:28</Ends><Seller Rating="53" UserID="sonofsam-tkc"/><Description>This auction is for one stick of 128MB SODIMM PC100 Kingston RAM. The part # is: KTH-OB4150 This RAM is for use in Hewlett Packard OmniBook and Hewlett Packard Pavillion Notebook, for a complete list of supported products visit this link: http://www.ec.kingston.com/ecom/kepler/PartsInfo_Bod.asp?ktcpartno=KTH-OB4150/128 Here is a pic of the RAM, all RAM is in closed packaging and is BRAND NEW, it comes with full Kingston LIFETIME warranty. For shipping please add $6, if you require urgent delivery it can be done at your cost. Paypal only please. Thankyou for looking and good luck! Free Honesty Counters powered by Andale! Payment Details See item description and Payment Instructions, or contact seller for more information. Payment Instructions Paypal only please.</Description></Item><Item ItemID="5757"><Name>STRATHMORE LEGACY LASER PAPER 8 ? X 11</Name><Category>Computers</Category><Category>Printers &amp; Supplies</Category><Category>Laser Printers</Category><Category>B&amp;W</Category><Category>Other</Category><Currently>$2.0</Currently><First_Bid>$2.0</First_Bid><Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids><Bids/><Location Latitude="36.235252" Longitude="-80.38089">NORTH CAROLINA</Location><Country>USA</Country><Started>Dec-17-01 06:26:42</Started><Ends>Dec-22-01 06:26:42</Ends><Seller Rating="5629" UserID="qsalvage"/><Description>PLEASE VISIT THE QSI HOME PAGE SITE STRATHMORE LEGACY LASER PAPER 8 _ X 11 STRATHMORE LEGACY LASER PAPER 8 _ X 11 100 SHEETS 100 SHEETS OF EXTRA SMOOTH SURFACE PROVIDES HIGHER CONTRAST AND DENSER GRAPHICS FOR OUTSTANDING LASER PRINTING AND COLOR COPYING. HEAVY WEIGHT (24LBS.) FOX EXTRA FEEL AND DURABILITY. FOR USE WITH ALL COPIERS AND LASER PRINTERS PLEASE NOTE:: BUSINESS HOURS ARE 8:00AM _ 4:30PM EASTERN STANDARD TIME MONDAY-FRIDAY. ANY QUESTIONS OR EMAILS ON WEEKENDS WILL BE ANSWERED ON MONDAY. ITEMS PAID BY PERSONAL/BUSINESS CHECK WILL BE HELD FOR 10 DAYS BEFORE SHIPPING. WE DO NOT ACCEPT CHECKS ISSUED ON NON-US BANKS. PLEASE ADDRESS ANY QUESTIONS REGUARDING THIS ITEM BEFORE YOU PLACE YOUR BID. PLEASE BE SURE YOU KNOW EXACTLY WHAT YOU ARE BIDDING ON. ALL ITEMS ARE SOLD AS IS. ANY EXCHANGES OR PRODUCT ISSUES MUST BE ADDRESSED WITHIN 3 DAYS OF RECIEPT. ALL REFUNDS ARE SUBJECT TO A 10% RESTOCKING FEE.. BUYER TO PAY 3.50 SHIPPING PPD INSIDE THE CONTINENTAL US. OUTSIDE THE CONTINENTAL US BUYER TO PAY ACTUAL SHIPPING COSTS. IF YOU ARE A NORTH CAROLINA RESIDENT PLEASE ADD IN A 6% SALES TAX TO YOUR PAYMENT. I ACCEPT MONEY FROM ANYONE WITH A CREDIT CARD THROUGH PAYPAL, ALWAYS FAST, ALWAYS FREE!! PLEASE MAKE PAYMENT WITHIN 10 DAYS OF THE AUCTIONS END OR NEGATIVE FEEDBACK WILL BE LEFT FOR YOU: PER EBAY'S SAFE HARBOR RULES. ANYONE SENDING A PERSONAL CHECK WILL HAVE TO WAIT 10 DAYS FOR THE CHECK TO CLEAR BEFORE I SHIP THE ITEM AND UNDER NO CIRCUMSTANCES WILL I ACCEPT A PERSONAL CHECK FROM ANYONE OUT OF THE COUNTRY. Free counters provided by Honesty.com This HTML automatically generated with AuctionAssistant from Blackthorne Software. I prefer PayPal, the payment choice of 10,000,000 auction buyers! function dw(nu){document.write(s1+"ppslv"+nu+".gif"+s2+sA[nu]);}f1="document.links";s1="\ ","\"I prefer PayPal, the payment choice of 10,000,000 auction buyers!\"\","\"Winning bidder, click here to pay with PayPal!\"\");c1=c2=c3=c4=0;for(i=0;i =0){c1++;}else if((eval(f1+"["+i+"].search")).indexOf("BetterSeller")=0){c2++;}else if((eval(f1+"["+i+"].search")).indexOf("ListItemForSaleShow")=0){c3++;}else if((eval(f1+"["+i+"].hash")).indexOf("ListItemForSaleAutosShow")=0){c4++;}}if((c1=2)||(c20)||(c30)||(c40)){dw(3);}else{dw(2);}f11="xclick-auction";f13="item=";f14="";for(i=0;i 0){s11=document.links[i].search;j=s11.indexOf(f13);if(j0){s11=s11.slice((j+(f13.length)));for(k=0;k =0){document.links[i].href=((document.links[i].href)+"&amp;jitem_id="+f14+"&amp;jmagic=1");}} Payment Details See item description and Payment Instructions, or contact seller for more information. Payment Instructions See item description or contact seller for more information.</Description></Item><Item ItemID="5758"><Name>FIX HP LaserJet 1100/3200 Laser Printer</Name><Category>Computers</Category><Category>Printers &amp; Supplies</Category><Category>Laser Printers</Category><Category>B&amp;W</Category><Category>HP</Category><Currently>$5.75</Currently><First_Bid>$5.75</First_Bid><Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids><Bids/><Location Latitude="40.679845" Longitude="-73.986415">New York City</Location><Country>USA</Country><Started>Dec-17-01 06:48:26</Started><Ends>Dec-22-01 06:48:26</Ends><Seller Rating="1163" UserID="janjiang"/><Description>If your HP 1100/3200 laser printer is picking up multiple pages or misfeed. You need to install the HP "Customer Replaceable Seperation Pad" kit and your printer will be as good as new. This kit is brand NEW from HP in a factory sealed box. It requires NO disassembly and takes less than 3 minutes to install for everyone. Easy to follow instructions are included. Buyer pays for the S/H. All major credit card accepted. I prefer PayPal or Billpoint. Check &amp; Money order is acceptable. Check my feedback and bid with confident. Check my eBay Store for other items on sale. []</Description></Item><Item ItemID="5759"><Name>ESI 2876 Combo Network MIO</Name><Category>Computers</Category><Category>Printers &amp; Supplies</Category><Category>Laser Printers</Category><Category>B&amp;W</Category><Category>Other</Category><Currently>$24.99</Currently><First_Bid>$24.99</First_Bid><Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids><Bids/><Location>Bonham</Location><Country>USA</Country><Started>Dec-17-01 07:38:26</Started><Ends>Dec-24-01 07:38:26</Ends><Seller Rating="3244" UserID="sales@bigkey.com"/><Description>ESI 2876 Combo Network MIO Our warehouse will be closed Dec. 22nd - Jan. 1st for the holidays. We will NOT be shipping any products during this time. If payment is not received by Dec. 20th, then product will not ship until Jan. 2nd. Please don't bid if this will be a problem for you. HAPPY HOLIDAYS! You are bidding on an Extended Systems ESI 2876 MIO Card. It has serial, aut, RJ45, and BNC interfaces. It is in excellent, working condition. It does NOT include books, software, or cables. Estimated shipping weight is 1 lb. Thank you! (CES) 2924 TNS This will ship Priority Mail with confirmation within the U.S. Please send $5.65 for shipping and handling along with winning bid amount. TX residents please include 8.25% sales tax to bid amount. If insurance is wanted, please email for information. If you live outside of the continental U.S., please email for shipping and handling information. ALL SALES ARE FINAL! PAYMENT TERMS: money orders cashiers checks personal checks- item held 7 business days before shipment for check to clear company checks (with favorable feedback of 25+) Credit Cards - We accept credit cards only through Bidpay (www.bidpay.com) Payment must be received within 10 days after notification of total payment due. High bidder must pay shipping and handling. Texas residents will be charged 8.25% sales tax unless you can provide a resale certificate. CONTACT INFO: EMAIL us with item number, shipping address, and phone number (if you live outside of the U.S.) after auction ends. We will then EMAIL you with payment total, including shipping and handling, as well as our address to mail payment to. If you do not hear from us within 48 hours, please call us. BUSINESS HOURS: Monday-Friday, 8:00 a.m.-5:00 p.m. PHONE: (903)640-4928 WE ARE CLOSED ON THE WEEKENDS AND DO NOT RESPOND TO EMAILS DURING THIS TIME. NO RESERVE Created by eBay Seller's Assistant Pro Free Honesty Counters powered by Andale! Visit Bigkey.com today! Payment Details See item description and Payment Instructions, or contact seller for more information. Payment Instructions See item description or contact seller for more information.</Description></Item><Item ItemID="5767"><Name>KDS RAD-5 LCD FLAT SCREEN MONITOR NEW</Name><Category>Computers</Category><Category>Monitors</Category><Category>Flat Panel</Category><Currently>$152.5</Currently><First_Bid>$0.01</First_Bid><Number_of_Bids>6</Number_of_Bids><Bids><Bid><Bidder Rating="2" UserID="mestar2k1"><Location>Venezia</Location><Country>Italy</Country></Bidder><Time>Dec-17-01 17:37:21</Time><Amount>$25.43</Amount></Bid><Bid><Bidder Rating="349" UserID="moosemilk"><Location>Venezia</Location><Country>Italy</Country></Bidder><Time>Dec-18-01 00:25:11</Time><Amount>$50.84</Amount></Bid><Bid><Bidder Rating="688" UserID="ether-sales"><Location>Venezia</Location><Country>Italy</Country></Bidder><Time>Dec-18-01 07:13:01</Time><Amount>$76.26</Amount></Bid><Bid><Bidder Rating="859" UserID="djmugabi"><Location>Venezia</Location><Country>Italy</Country></Bidder><Time>Dec-18-01 14:00:51</Time><Amount>$101.67</Amount></Bid><Bid><Bidder Rating="2294" UserID="mrbd"><Location>Venezia</Location><Country>Italy</Country></Bidder><Time>Dec-18-01 20:48:41</Time><Amount>$127.09</Amount></Bid><Bid><Bidder Rating="472" UserID="sewsewsew@aol.com"><Location>Venezia</Location><Country>Italy</Country></Bidder><Time>Dec-19-01 03:36:31</Time><Amount>$152.5</Amount></Bid></Bids><Location Latitude="42.831686" Longitude="-71.66743">NEW ENGLAND</Location><Country>USA</Country><Started>Dec-17-01 10:49:32</Started><Ends>Dec-20-01 10:49:32</Ends><Seller Rating="1533" UserID="kevspy@aol.com"/><Description>Auctiva FastPix Click for full image Auctiva FastPix Click for full image REFERENCE # BBE 12 CMT 15 GG KDS RAD-5 LCD FLAT SCREEN MONITOR NEW REFERENCE # BBE 12 CMT 15 GG I have set the buy it now price for this item lower than the auctions for these usually end at here on eBay and almost half off of the retail price. Like most of my items, this one will be purchased using the buy it now feature, so dont delay as when you check back, it will be gone!!!! This auction is for one brand new KDS RAD-5 Flat screen monitor that is new and still sealed in it's box!!. It comes complete with a matching Mouse. KDS RAD-5 ( 15" Ultra-Thin LCD Display (Designer Mouse Included) The beautifully designed yet affordable RAD-5 analog LCD panel is perfect for replacing your old conventional CRT monitor. It is an "a-Si TFT LCD panel" with a 15.0 diagonal panel size. The RAD-5 features a maximum resolution of 1024 x 768 @ 75Hz for outstanding brightness and incredible color. This LCD panel may also be taken off the stand and wall-mounted. ... LCD Panel Type : a-Si TFT LCD Pixel Pitch : .297(H)mm x .297(V)mm Max Color : 16.7 Million displayable colors Contrast Ratio : 300:1 (typical) Brightness : 250 cd/m2 (typical) Viewing Angle: 55_ /60_/ 70_/ (T/B/L/R) Video Video Input Analog : R, G, B Synchronization Frequency : 30-61 kHz (horizontal) 50-75 Hz (vertical) Raster Specifications Max Resolution : 1024 x 768 @75Hz Electrical Voltage : Universal Input Voltage, 12Vdc Output On Working : 34W Max Standby,Suspend,Off : Less than 5W, Regulation EPA Physical Dimensions : Panel:14.9"(W) x 14.0"(H) x 6.2"(D) Box: 20.6"(W) x 20.0"(H) x 11.3"(D) Weight : 8.58 lbs(Net) / 14.99lbs(Gross) Features General : On-screen, digital control VESA DDC 1/2B Plug&amp;Play, Wall mount capability OSD Controls : Auto tune, Contrast/Brightness, H/V Position, H-Size, Phase, Sharpness, Color Control, Auto Level, OSD Position, Language and Recall Safety : NRTL c CE (EN60950), SEMKO EMI : FCC, CE (EN50082-1), VCCI Low Radiation : TCO 99 Sync Type : Separate, Composite, SOG, Input Terminal D-SUB 15Pin Tilt Angle : -5, +15 Thanks for your interest in my listing! Below, I have outlined a little bit about me and the terms under which I sell my items. Please take a moment to look them over and I hope you enjoy bidding. WHERE DO MY ITEMS COME FROM ? I spend my time searching high and low looking for great deals that I can pass on to the nice people on eBay. The items come from Auctions, Flea Markets, Tag Sales, Going out of Business Liquidations, Second Hand and Pawn Shops. I check all of the items once and twice over before investing my hard earned money into them because these are usually one of a kind and all sales final. On the more expensive and technical items, I always have them checked over by professionals before the listing is made. HOW DO I SHIP, AND WHEN WILL YOU GET IT ? Like you, I buy lots of things on eBay and I know that when I do I want to receive the item as soon as possible, know that it is on its way, and get it in one piece. To this end, I use UPS ground. They may not be as cheap as some others, but they get the job done consistently and allow me to ship almost every day. Also, when I ship items, the recipients get a email that provides them with a tracking # and link to track their item. This tracking system is very accurate and in my opinion is far superior to the one that the Post Office uses. FLAT RATE SHIPPING AND HANDLING FOR THIS ITEM IS $22.30 The price that I am charging for the shipping is Flat Rate for the Continental United States and constitutes all of the costs of shipping and handling the package. That includes, not only the postage fee, but the box, packing media, tape, labels, printer supplies, and labor to pay someone to pack your item with the care that you can expect from me Buyers outside of the continental US must pay one and a half % of the stated shipping price to cover the higher price of shipping to those locations. I will ship to Canada, but be aware that I will not submit documents with false item descriptions or values to save you money on taxes, or be responsible for brokerage fees and delays. HOW DO I ACCEPT PAYMENTS ? I accept Credit Cards through Pay Pal, Money Orders &amp; Cashiers Checks. I give my buyers up to 7 days to get their payment to me after the auction ends. I reserve the right to resell items not paid for by that time and return late payments CREDIT CARD CUSTOMERS PLEASE NOTE If you are not already a registered PayPal user, please note that PayPal allows credit card transactions up to only $250.00 until your account is verified. After that, you can charge more. The verification process usually takes 2 days. If you are bidding on this item and your bid will total over $250.00 including shipping, you may want to sign up for PayPal now to expedite your order. There is no purchase or obligation necessary WHAT HAPPENS IF THERE IS A PROBLEM WITH THE ITEM THAT YOU BUY I give buyers 7 days to inspect their purchase. In the unlikley event that there is a problem with it, I will either fix the item or refund your money upon the prompt return of the item. New items are sold as new and as I am not a dealer defects must be taken up through the product warranty. View and search all the items in my picture gallery Auctiva PowerTools . Create, Schedule, Manage your auctions Free Trial!</Description></Item><Item ItemID="5768"><Name>IBM 4039 12R Plus Laser Printer</Name><Category>Computers</Category><Category>Printers &amp; Supplies</Category><Category>Laser Printers</Category><Category>B&amp;W</Category><Category>Lexmark</Category><Currently>$60.0</Currently><First_Bid>$60.0</First_Bid><Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids><Bids/><Location Latitude="40.298988" Longitude="-76.847194">Harrisburg, PA</Location><Country>USA</Country><Started>Dec-17-01 11:42:27</Started><Ends>Dec-20-01 11:42:27</Ends><Seller Rating="141" UserID="cpitech"/><Description>This laser printer is in really great shape. It is a IBM 4039 12R Plus (made by Lexmark) with 2MB of installed memory and a page count of 118600 pages. We will include a power cord with the sale. We also offer two additional options with this printer for an extra $25.00 each. These options are: an extra 500-page paper tray, and an envelope feeder. These options can be discussed with the winning bidder after the close of the auction. Payment is accepted by PayPal. Please email payment to payment@cpitech.com . If you don_t want to go through PayPal, we also accept Visa, MasterCard, American Express or pre-paid by check or moneyorder. If you choose to pay by check, we wait until the check clears _ usually about a week _ before shipping, otherwise, shipment goes out the day after receipt of payment via FedEx Ground. Please note that another $35.00 is required in addition to the bid cost for shipping and handling purposes. (Orders will be shipped to continental U.S. only). Also note that PA residents should add 6% sales tax to the final bid cost before adding the shipping charge. Any questions can be directed to kerry@cpitech.com . Free Honesty Counters powered by Andale! Payment Details U.S. Shipping and Handling $35.00 Shipping Insurance per item - Sales Tax (6.000% if shipped to PA) _ Learn more about checkout Payment Instructions 30 day return policy on any product we sell.</Description></Item><Item ItemID="5769"><Name>Seagate 2.5 SCSI HD &amp; NEC CD-ROM Combo</Name><Category>Computers</Category><Category>Apple, Macintosh</Category><Category>Drives-Internal</Category><Currently>$33.77</Currently><First_Bid>$33.77</First_Bid><Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids><Bids/><Location Latitude="40.298988" Longitude="-76.847194">Harrisburg PA</Location><Country>USA</Country><Started>Dec-17-01 00:16:33</Started><Ends>Dec-20-01 00:16:33</Ends><Seller Rating="623" UserID="mlujanac@paonline.com"/><Description>WE DO NOT ACCEPT PAYPAL!! Seagate 2.5 SCSI HD &amp; NEC CD-ROM Combo Nice clean units are tested, working, and as always, guaranteed not DOA. Seagate Barracuda model ST32550N 50 pin 7200RPM SCSI hard drive and NEC 8X SCSI 50 pin CD-ROM are both nice clean working pulls and as a pair, will save you a bundle on shipping! Buyer pays just 8.95 shipping USA, and 12.00 to Canada. Thanks, and happy bidding! NO RESERVE We accept Ebay Payments, Bidpay, money orders, and US personal checks. MAILING ADDRESS IS MICHAEL LUJANAC 1777 SHEEPFORD RD MECHANICSBURG PA 17055 USA. Please include item number and ship to address on separate sheet. Thanks for looking and happy bidding! Buyer to pay $8.95 for shipping and handling. WE DO NOT ACCEPT PAYPAL!! Click here to view my other auctions. This listing created by eBay Seller's Assistant Pro Visit Parts Unlimited today! Payment Details U.S. Shipping and Handling $8.95 Shipping Insurance per item - Sales Tax (none) _ Learn more about checkout Payment Instructions All items are tested and working, and are guaranteed not DOA. Shipper must be notified within 24 hours of any DOA claim. Item must be returned prepaid to shipper for full refund. Does not cover cosmetic imperfections, compatibility or user installation issues.</Description></Item><Item ItemID="5770"><Name>Kyocera DK-2 Drum Kit F-3000 F-3010</Name><Category>Computers</Category><Category>Printers &amp; Supplies</Category><Category>Laser Printers</Category><Category>B&amp;W</Category><Category>Other</Category><Currently>$9.99</Currently><Buy_Price>$25.96</Buy_Price><First_Bid>$9.99</First_Bid><Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids><Bids/><Location Latitude="39.737104" Longitude="-79.83613">Pennsylvania</Location><Country>USA</Country><Started>Dec-17-01 13:01:35</Started><Ends>Dec-24-01 13:01:35</Ends><Seller Rating="388" UserID="make7-up-yours"/><Description>.titledata { font-family: verdana, sans-serif; font-size:17px; color:#6A5B44; font-weight : bold; } .description { font-family: verdana, sans-serif; color:#6A5B44; } .link { font-family: verdana, sans-serif; font-size:12px; underline; } HR { color: #000000; } Kyocera DK-2 Drum Kit F-3000 F-3010 Click image to view larger version Click image to view larger version Kyocera DK-2 Drum Kit F-3000 F-3010 This auction is for a genuine Kyocera DRUM Kit DK-2 for use in the Kyocera F-3000 and F-3010 Laser Printers. These are BRAND SPANKING NEW in the box! Shipping on this item will be $10.00 If you have any questions, please email prior to bidding. PAYMENT TERMS We accept all major credit cards through Pay Pal, US Postal Money orders, Money Orders and Cashiers Checks. These are the only acceptable forms of payment. All other forms of payment will be rejected and the sale will be considered null and void. We require all auctions to be paid in full within ten days of the close of the auction. There are no exceptions. If payment is not made within ten days of the close of the auction the sale will be considered null and void. SHIPPING All items will be shipped with tracking information. Items will be shipped either US Mail, UPS or FED EX, some items will also be shipped via Common Carrier truck freight. All shipping decisions will be made at our discretion and those decisions will be final. All items are priced with flat rate shipping. This shipping price is for the contiguous United States (The lower 48, not including Alaska and Hawaii). Shipping prices will vary drastically for out of country packages. Do not assume this flat rate shipping charge applies to you unless you are located in the lower 48 states. If you need a shipping quote anywhere else in the world please contact us prior to bidding. Shipping discounts are available to customers who purchase more than one item. If you are the successful bidder on three or more items there will be a 10% shipping discount. If you are the successful bidder on more than five items there will be a 15% shipping discount. This discount will only apply to the shipping charges it will have no effect on the winning bid for the item. ***Pay Pal customers, please note that we will only ship your items to the Pay Pal confirmed address. There are no exceptions to this policy. *** INSURANCE All items will be shipped with no insurance unless the customer requests insurance. We recommend that all customers take insurance on their products. Items that are shipped with no insurance are done so at the buyers sole risk. We will have no liability for lost or damaged packages that are sent with no insurance by the buyer. SALES TAX Pennsylvania state residents are required to add 6% sales tax to any purchase. DESCRIPTIONS It is our goal to describe the item in our advertisements to the best of our ability. We use all the qualified sources that are available to us in order to give you the most thorough description. However, we are not infallible and so we recommend that all customers do their own research prior to bidding on any item. NOTEBOOKS, COMPUTER SYSTEMS, INKJETS, LASER PRINTERS Systems, notebooks, hard drives and the like may from time to time have software on them. We are not selling any software whatsoever unless it is clearly advertised in the advertisement and contains the users license and agreement. In the event that you receive a system, notebook or hard drive or any other media that contains any software it is your sole responsibility to either delete, erase or license said software. We are in no way giving you any right to use any software whatsoever. Notebooks contain batteries so that they may function without their power packs. These batteries are considered a consumable that is replaceable by the user. These batteries and any other consumables (printer ribbons, toner cartridges, etc.) on any device we sell are not covered under any warranty. Simply put, notebook batteries are not covered under our warranty even if the advertisement says that the product is guaranteed working. Unless the notebook specifically states that the battery is in working order it will not be covered under warranty. Laser printers and inkjets have the same limitations as above. We do not guarantee the ink supply or the laser toner cartridge even when the item is guaranteed working. These toner cartridges and ink cartridges are considered consumables and must be replaced by the user. PICTURES All auctions where possible contain as many detailed pictures as we have available. These pictures are there to help you decide condition and quality. We attempt to provide as much graphic information as is humanly possible. Please look at the picture carefully in determining what may or may not come with the item. If there is an item that you believe should come with the item being auctioned is not visible in a picture it is more than likely that item is not included. In other words, if the item is not pictured then it is not being sold in the auction. Once again, if there is a question please feel free to email us prior to placing a bid. WARRANTY Unless stated above in the description for the auction all items are sold as is where is with no warranty expressed or implied. This means that unless the advertisement specifically states that we guarantee the product working then there is no guarantee from us whatsoever. Many products that we will sell will have a manufacturers warranty and we will attempt to list that in the advertisement as well. RETURN POLICY All sales are final. No returns, exchanges, credits or any other offsets. The only exception to this policy is an item that is guaranteed working. In the event that an item that was guaranteed working arrives non-working that item may be returned for replacement. In the event that there are no more of that item we will issue a merchandise credit for the total of the auction. That credit may be used on any item in any future auction and that credit will not expire. This does not include items that are damaged in shipping. All items that are damaged in shipping must go through the shipping carriers claim procedure. Our warranty does not include lost or damaged packages. FEEDBACK Feedback is left for customers as we check our feedback. Customers who have left feedback for us will have feedback left for them. If you do not leave us feedback we will not leave feedback for you. In this manner all our feedback can be handled automatically by our system. If you have any problem whatsoever please make sure to contact us so that we may attempt to resolve whatever issue you may have. Please make sure to contact us prior to leaving any negative feedback as once you have left negative feedback we will consider the transaction complete. Low cost image hosting and full service auction management solutions: AuctionWatch</Description></Item><Item ItemID="5771"><Name>HP LaserJet 8000/8100 MFP Upgrade Kit, C4166A</Name><Category>Computers</Category><Category>Printers &amp; Supplies</Category><Category>Laser Printers</Category><Category>B&amp;W</Category><Category>HP</Category><Currently>$1050.0</Currently><First_Bid>$1050.0</First_Bid><Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids><Bids/><Location Latitude="33.640302" Longitude="-117.769442">SANTA ANA WAREHOUSE</Location><Country>USA</Country><Started>Dec-17-01 14:01:25</Started><Ends>Dec-24-01 14:01:25</Ends><Seller Rating="84" UserID="ficompinc"/><Description>YOU'RE BIDDING ON A BRAND NEW MFP UPGRADE KIT FOR HP LASERJET 8000 AND/OR LASERJET 8100, P/N C4166A. THIS PRODUCT IS THE RESULT OF EXCESS INVENTORY DIRECTLY FROM HEWLETT-PACKARD COMPANY. IT CARRIES A 90-DAY WARRANTY WITH THE SELLER, FICOMP INC. EXTENDED WARRANTY MAY BE PURCHASED WITH HP FOR NEXT-DAY ONSITE SERVICE BY CALLING 1-800-743-8305. BUYER PAYS FLAT SHIPPING CHARGE OF $95 VIA GROUND TO 48 STATES. 7.5% CA SALES TAX APPLIED TO CA RESIDENTS ONLY. WE ACCEPT ALL MAJOR CREDIT CARDS AND PAYPAL. Shipping contents of the MFP Upgrade Kit (part number C4166A) Digital Copy Module Automatic document feeder Installation instructions (Hard Copy) Three control panel overlays (French, Italian, Spanish) Y power cord HP Digital Sender module CD (software for the upgrade) HP LaserJet MFP Upgrade User's Guide CD 2.1 GB hard disk Copy Connect EIO Board (J3286-60002) High speed Copy Connect cable 32 MB memory DIMM HP LaserJet 8000 firmware upgrade DIMM v 4.54 (C4085-60008) HP LaserJet 8100 firmware upgrade DIMM v 5.54 (C4214-60008) Scan-to-E-mail license (Scan-to-Fax and NT Authentication licenses must be purchased separately)</Description></Item><Item ItemID="5783"><Name>IBM ThinkPad 64MB RAM Module, KTM-TP770/64</Name><Category>Computers</Category><Category>Laptops &amp; Accessories</Category><Category>Accessories</Category><Category>Memory Upgrades</Category><Currently>$1.0</Currently><First_Bid>$1.0</First_Bid><Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids><Bids/><Location Latitude="32.751575" Longitude="-117.191848">San Diego, CA</Location><Country>USA</Country><Started>Dec-17-01 21:14:56</Started><Ends>Dec-27-01 21:14:56</Ends><Seller Rating="5" UserID="honestoceantrader"/><Description>New Page 1 Kingston 64MB Memory Module KTM-TP770/64 This auction is for a brand new, never used (except for being tested once to ensure it works) 64MB memory module, compatible with multiple laptops._ Please double check for compatibility with the list provided below. Buyer pays shipping. Secure online credit card payments accepted via http://www.c2it.com and http://www.paypal.com . If you have any questions, please email me prior to bidding. _ IBM- ThinkPad 240 (2609-xxx) IBM- ThinkPad 770 9549-1xx IBM- ThinkPad i 1400 (2621) Series 1421 IBM- ThinkPad 390 Pentium Series 2626-2xx,5xx,7xx IBM- ThinkPad 770E 9548-5xx IBM- ThinkPad i 1400 (2621) Series 1441 IBM- ThinkPad 390E Celeron Series IBM- ThinkPad 770ED 9549-5xx IBM- ThinkPad i 1400 (2621) Series 1460 IBM- ThinkPad 390E Pentium II Series IBM- ThinkPad 770X 9549-7xU IBM- ThinkPad i 1400 (2621) Series 1480 IBM- ThinkPad 570 (2644-1xx, 2xx, 3xx) IBM- ThinkPad 770Z 9549-8xU IBM- ThinkPad i 1500 (2611) Series 1512 IBM- ThinkPad 600 2645-21U/31U IBM- ThinkPad i 1400 (2611) Series 1410 IBM- ThinkPad i 1500 (2611) Series 1552 IBM- ThinkPad 600 2645-35U/41U/51U/A1U IBM- ThinkPad i 1400 (2611) Series 1411 IBM- ThinkPad i 1500 (2621) Series 1540 IBM- ThinkPad 600 2645-45U/85U IBM- ThinkPad i 1400 (2611) Series 1412 IBM- ThinkPad i 1500 (2621) Series 1541 IBM- ThinkPad 600E 2645-3AU/4AU/5AU/Cxx IBM- ThinkPad i 1400 (2611) Series 1450 IBM- ThinkPad i 1500 (2621) Series 1560 IBM- ThinkPad 600E 2645-4BU/5BU/8BU/Bxx IBM- ThinkPad i 1400 (2611) Series 1451 IBM- ThinkPad i 1700 Series 1720 IBM- ThinkPad 600E 2645-8AU/AAU IBM- ThinkPad i 1400 (2611) Series 1452 IBM- ThinkPad i 1700 Series 1721 IBM- ThinkPad 600E 2645-A5U/55U/Bxx IBM- ThinkPad i 1400 (2611) Series 1472 IBM- ThinkPad 770 9548-3xx, 9548-4xx IBM- ThinkPad i 1400 (2621) Series 1420 Free Honesty Counters powered by Andale! Payment Details See item description and Payment Instructions, or contact seller for more information. Payment Instructions After you have won, please email me your desired method of payment and shipping along with shipping address. Thank you.</Description></Item><Item ItemID="5784"><Name>32mb Memory 4 AST Ascentia J series</Name><Category>Computers</Category><Category>Laptops &amp; Accessories</Category><Category>Accessories</Category><Category>Memory Upgrades</Category><Currently>$9.0</Currently><First_Bid>$9.0</First_Bid><Number_of_Bids>1</Number_of_Bids><Bids><Bid><Bidder Rating="1172" UserID="northdoorway"><Location>Venezia</Location><Country>Italy</Country></Bidder><Time>Dec-18-01 11:17:58</Time><Amount>$9.0</Amount></Bid></Bids><Location Latitude="33.967562" Longitude="-118.03384">CA</Location><Country>USA</Country><Started>Dec-17-01 23:03:57</Started><Ends>Dec-24-01 23:03:57</Ends><Seller Rating="3359" UserID="sunguk"/><Description>You are bidding on a GoldenRam 32mb upgrade for AST Ascentai J sereis. (MFG#:501986001-GR). Buyer prepay with s/h ($5.00 ) within 10 days after the end of the auction. US bidder only.</Description></Item><Item ItemID="5786"><Name>Lot of 2 Compaq 32 Meg Memory # 262261-002</Name><Category>Computers</Category><Category>Laptops &amp; Accessories</Category><Category>Accessories</Category><Category>Memory Upgrades</Category><Currently>$16.0</Currently><First_Bid>$16.0</First_Bid><Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids><Bids/><Location Latitude="32.767268" Longitude="-96.777626">Grand Prairie</Location><Country>USA</Country><Started>Dec-18-01 02:15:22</Started><Ends>Dec-21-01 02:15:22</Ends><Seller Rating="13" UserID="hemigraphis"/><Description>Lot of 2 Compaq 32meg Memory #262261-002 LOT OF 2 Compaq 32meg Memory The spare number for the Compaq 32 meg EDO memory module is 262261-002.This memory is compatible with the Compaq Armada and LTE notebooks. It also works on the Torshiba 610, 470, 430, 400, 410, and 740 notebooks. This memory is tested and in good working order. Payments by Money Order, Certified Check, Ebay Payments or PayPal. Payment must be received, before the product is shipped Buyer pays $4.50 for shipping and handling. Free Honesty Counters powered by Andale! Payment Details U.S. Shipping and Handling $4.50 Shipping Insurance per item - Sales Tax (none) _ Learn more about checkout Payment Instructions See item description or contact seller for more information.</Description></Item><Item ItemID="5787"><Name>Compaq LTE 5000 series laptop 32meg upgrade</Name><Category>Computers</Category><Category>Laptops &amp; Accessories</Category><Category>Accessories</Category><Category>Memory Upgrades</Category><Currently>$1.0</Currently><First_Bid>$1.0</First_Bid><Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids><Bids/><Location>Pacific Northwest</Location><Country>USA</Country><Started>Dec-18-01 08:02:01</Started><Ends>Dec-21-01 08:02:01</Ends><Seller Rating="25" UserID="yesterdayspc"/><Description>Kingston 32 MB ram upgrade Kit (2 pieces) NEW in the Box!! Kingston #: KTC-E5000/32 Compaq Equiv #: 213515-003, 213515-293 Description: 32MB Kit Form Factor: Module kit #Pieces/Unit: 2 Warranty: Lifetime from Kingston. Fits Compaq 5000 series of laptops: 5000 CX/CD, 5100, 5150,5200, 5250, 5280, 5300, 5350, 5380, 5400. Kingston lists the suggested retail price at $144.00 Have a LTE 5000 series laptop that could use a boost in the memory department? Here is a Brand new kit that could help. Terms: Since this item is new in the box and UNTESTED, It is being sold AS IS!! We accept : Money Orders, Cashiers Checks , Visa or Mastercard via Paypal. Washington State Residents: add 8.8 % sales tax Sorry NO International sales NO COD's Shipping is $5.00 in the continental US, Shipping via USPS Priority Mail. Insurance available upon request. Please email with any questions. Pay me securely with your Visa or MasterCard through PayPal! function dw(nu){document.write(s1+"ppsl"+nu+".gif"+s2+sA[nu]);}f1="document.links";s1="\ ","\"Winning bidder, click here to pay instantly by credit card!\"\","\"Winning bidder, click here to pay instantly by credit card!\"\");c1=c2=c3=c4=0;for(i=0;i =0){c1++;}else if((eval(f1+"["+i+"].search")).indexOf("BetterSeller")=0){c2++;}else if((eval(f1+"["+i+"].search")).indexOf("ListItemForSaleShow")=0){c3++;}else if((eval(f1+"["+i+"].hash")).indexOf("ListItemForSaleAutosShow")=0){c4++;}}if((c1=2)||(c20)||(c30)||(c40)){dw(3);}else{dw(2);}f11="xclick-auction";f13="iid=";f14="";for(i=0;i 0){s11=document.links[i].search;j=s11.indexOf(f13);if(j0){s11=s11.slice((j+(f13.length)));for(k=0;k =0){var p=new Array();p[0]=document.links[i].protocol;p[1]=document.links[i].hostname;p[2]=document.links[i].pathname;for(j=0;j Free Honesty Counters powered by Andale! Payment Details U.S. Shipping and Handling $5.00 Shipping Insurance per item - Sales Tax (8.800% if shipped to WA) _ Learn more about checkout Payment Instructions See item description or contact seller for more information.</Description></Item><Item ItemID="5788"><Name>HP1100 Printer</Name><Category>Computers</Category><Category>Printers &amp; Supplies</Category><Category>Laser Printers</Category><Category>B&amp;W</Category><Category>HP</Category><Currently>$125.0</Currently><First_Bid>$125.0</First_Bid><Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids><Bids/><Location Latitude="40.821799" Longitude="-74.30477">Roseland, New Jersey</Location><Country>USA</Country><Started>Dec-18-01 09:28:59</Started><Ends>Dec-25-01 09:28:59</Ends><Seller Rating="0" UserID="fedsysgrp"/><Description>HP1100 Printer in Roseland, New Jersey ready for pick up or ship you pay costs. http://www.fedsysgrp.com Free Honesty Counters powered by Andale! Payment Details See item description and Payment Instructions, or contact seller for more information. Payment Instructions PAYPAL MEMBER</Description></Item><Item ItemID="9770"><Name>Russian Stickers for Keyboard</Name><Category>Computers</Category><Category>Printers &amp; Supplies</Category><Category>Laser Printers</Category><Category>B&amp;W</Category><Category>HP</Category><Currently>$6.47</Currently><First_Bid>$5.97</First_Bid><Number_of_Bids>2</Number_of_Bids><Bids><Bid><Bidder Rating="1151" UserID="h-r-r-j@msn.com"><Location>Venezia</Location><Country>Italy</Country></Bidder><Time>Dec-16-01 11:07:26</Time><Amount>$6.22</Amount></Bid><Bid><Bidder Rating="385" UserID="athomeresalewithcandi"><Location>Venezia</Location><Country>Italy</Country></Bidder><Time>Dec-17-01 01:31:26</Time><Amount>$6.47</Amount></Bid></Bids><Location Latitude="38.377411" Longitude="-121.444429">SAC-TO .CA.</Location><Country>USA</Country><Started>Dec-15-01 20:43:26</Started><Ends>Dec-18-01 20:43:26</Ends><Seller Rating="13" UserID="reachmen"/><Description>Russian stickers for Pc keyboard . Red color . Put Russian Alphabet on your favorite hi- end Russian Pc keyboard stickers are suitable to use on any desktop or notebook keyboard. They could be an excellent alternative to purchasing of factory -stenciled Keyboards . Shipping $ free In USA . Canada $ 1, all other countries $ 1.50 dollars. Payment only by (Money Order) And certified check, Personal Check .Payment is expected within 11 days of our notification to you at the end of the action. Questions are Welcomed but must be asked before the auction ends Email me at Sergey113@hotmail.com. THANKS Free Honesty Counters powered by Andale! Payment Details U.S. Shipping and Handling $1.00 Shipping Insurance per item - Sales Tax (0.000% if shipped to none) _ Learn more about checkout Payment Instructions Congratulations on winning our auction. you can send us a money order. or personal check, please click the winning bidder checkout link below. You can email us for Address or payment information At . Sergey113@hotmail.com , Thank you !!!</Description></Item><Item ItemID="16598"><Name>Ricoh 1000/4000/7000 Series Fax Toner - NEW</Name><Category>Computers</Category><Category>Printers &amp; Supplies</Category><Category>Laser Printers</Category><Category>B&amp;W</Category><Category>Other</Category><Currently>$5.99</Currently><First_Bid>$5.99</First_Bid><Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids><Bids/><Location Latitude="43.286024" Longitude="-77.684264">Rochester, NY</Location><Country>USA</Country><Started>Dec-14-01 10:43:10</Started><Ends>Dec-17-01 10:43:10</Ends><Seller Rating="2097" UserID="mav01"/><Description>eBay Template Ricoh 1000/4000/7000 Series Fax Toner - NEW This auction is for Ricoh Fax Toner for 1000/4000/7000 series fax machines. Pictured here, 4 cartridges are included in the box, all new. Item is covered under our normal shipping policy (see below) and are "sold as is". Thank You for Considering Maven Technologies! mem Shipping &amp; Handling There is a $10 shipping and handling charge within the continental United States. Please contact us for additional shipping information, including other shipping destinations. Most items are typically shipped within 48 business hours of settlement. International shipments may require an additional 24 business hours to process. Payment We accept Visa, MasterCard, Discover, Money Orders and PayPal Warranty 30 Day Warranty, excluding items which are "sold as is". Defective items will be repaired or replaced at no charge. If we deem an item as unrepairable and/or replacement is not available, a refund will be issued. If we determine that the malfunction was caused by hardware or software not provided by us, including software conflicts, repairs will be subject to our service fee. There is a 20% restocking fee for all non-defective equipment returns. Rules and Limitations (DISCLAIMER) Winning bidders who decide to cancel their orders shall be charged all applicable eBay fees. Defective parts/systems will be exchanged with the same parts/systems. Shipping is non-refundable. If any item becomes unexpectedly out of stock, we reserve the right to substitute an item of equal or greater value. Technical Support is responsible for handling all technically related problems and questions. Normal business hours are Monday - Friday, 8:00am - 5:00pm. Residents of New York will incur Sales Tax. Items can be picked up at our retail store location with prior notification, a $10 handling fee will be assessed in addition the purchase price and applicable taxes. If this auction is not settled within 10 business days of auction close, the sale will be considered void and the high bidder will receive negative feedback. By bidding, you hereby agree to these conditions Please E-Mail any questions to Auction@maventech.com Mavens other Auctions This listing created by eBay Seller's Assistant Pro</Description></Item></Items>